[[{"No": 1, "Stem": "The conflict ended with a rebellion against the East India Company in 1857, and the firm ____ was nationalized.", "Opt_1": "eventually", "Opt_2": "gradually", "Opt_3": "roughly", "Opt_4": "simply", "Answer": "eventually", "Opt_1_def": "in the end", "Opt_2_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_3_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_4_def": "completely; just; only"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The entire ____ of Iraqi military and civil society collapsed so completely as the war ended, leaving a vast problem for American troops to handle.", "Opt_1": "expert", "Opt_2": "feature", "Opt_3": "growth", "Opt_4": "structure", "Answer": "structure", "Opt_1_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_2_def": "part, aspect", "Opt_3_def": "development, increase", "Opt_4_def": "the way something is made or organized"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Many shops these days have ____ doors. They open as soon as you approach.", "Opt_1": "harsh", "Opt_2": "valid", "Opt_3": "automatic", "Opt_4": "efficient", "Answer": "automatic", "Opt_1_def": "hard, unfair", "Opt_2_def": "correct", "Opt_3_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually", "Opt_4_def": "working quickly and easily"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The ____ authority in the country is the President.", "Opt_1": "arbitrary", "Opt_2": "ultimate", "Opt_3": "homogeneous", "Opt_4": "rapid", "Answer": "ultimate", "Opt_1_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others", "Opt_2_def": "final or most important", "Opt_3_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics", "Opt_4_def": "quick"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "In general, when you paraphrase, you use about the same number of words to ____ the idea that the writer uses in the text.", "Opt_1": "prevail", "Opt_2": "convey", "Opt_3": "confine", "Opt_4": "collaborate", "Answer": "convey", "Opt_1_def": "to succeed; to overcome", "Opt_2_def": "to pass on to another person (often by speaking)", "Opt_3_def": "to limit", "Opt_4_def": "to work together"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The company's ____ for the year was to expand sales by \ufffd\ufffd2 million. Now they expect to exceed this figure by 40%.", "Opt_1": "target", "Opt_2": "object", "Opt_3": "precaution", "Opt_4": "detail", "Answer": "target", "Opt_1_def": "aim, goal", "Opt_2_def": "thing", "Opt_3_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_4_def": "a small piece of information"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "There is a ____ difference between the sports of mountain-climbing and table tennis. In the first you can get killed; in the second usually not.", "Opt_1": "radical", "Opt_2": "wise", "Opt_3": "available", "Opt_4": "crucial", "Answer": "crucial", "Opt_1_def": "extreme, strong", "Opt_2_def": "intelligent; sensible", "Opt_3_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_4_def": "extremely important"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "I tried to ____ the information on the internet, but could find nothing useful.", "Opt_1": "acquire", "Opt_2": "manifest", "Opt_3": "owe", "Opt_4": "exploit", "Answer": "acquire", "Opt_1_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_2_def": "show", "Opt_3_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)", "Opt_4_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "There will not be representative democracy in Iraq. Instead, there will be a long US-led ____ occupation that will incite resistance.", "Opt_1": "logical", "Opt_2": "verbal", "Opt_3": "military", "Opt_4": "flexible", "Answer": "military", "Opt_1_def": "making sense", "Opt_2_def": "to do with words and language (especially the spoken language)", "Opt_3_def": "to do with army", "Opt_4_def": "can be changed or bent"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is a common belief that the universe is infinite. But who knows? Maybe one day we will ____ it has an edge or end.", "Opt_1": "exchange", "Opt_2": "underlie", "Opt_3": "transmit", "Opt_4": "discover", "Answer": "discover", "Opt_1_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing", "Opt_2_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something", "Opt_3_def": "to send or convey", "Opt_4_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The doctor examined the patient carefully, ____ that he forgot to check blood pressure.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Her grades will start to ____ unless she cuts back on the number of after-school activities she does.", "Opt_1": "integrate", "Opt_2": "exist", "Opt_3": "involve", "Opt_4": "suffer", "Answer": "suffer", "Opt_1_def": "to fit into a new situation", "Opt_2_def": "to be alive, to be in the world", "Opt_3_def": "to include or mean", "Opt_4_def": "to experience something bad or painful"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If authors realize there is a significant ____ in a published paper, they may correct their paper by submitting a short correction notice.", "Opt_1": "domain", "Opt_2": "support", "Opt_3": "error", "Opt_4": "obstacle", "Answer": "error", "Opt_1_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_2_def": "help", "Opt_3_def": "a mistake", "Opt_4_def": "barrier; problem"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Calderone's insistence that sex ____ should begin as early as kindergarten did not impress religious conservative groups.", "Opt_1": "circumstances", "Opt_2": "opinion", "Opt_3": "event", "Opt_4": "education", "Answer": "education", "Opt_1_def": "situation", "Opt_2_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "a happening", "Opt_4_def": "schooling"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "This unnecessary ____ would adversely impact the existing review system that ensures the high quality of scientific research in the United States.", "Opt_1": "innovation", "Opt_2": "legislation", "Opt_3": "exhibit", "Opt_4": "role", "Answer": "legislation", "Opt_1_def": "new object or idea", "Opt_2_def": "governmental rule; law", "Opt_3_def": "to show", "Opt_4_def": "job or function"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Omitting the transportation costs would ____ the company's financial position.", "Opt_1": "blame", "Opt_2": "accelerate", "Opt_3": "distort", "Opt_4": "collaborate", "Answer": "distort", "Opt_1_def": "to accuse", "Opt_2_def": "to get or make faster", "Opt_3_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)", "Opt_4_def": "to work together"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The head teacher could not assure parents that there would be no ____ in school fees.", "Opt_1": "isolate", "Opt_2": "enhance", "Opt_3": "identify", "Opt_4": "increase", "Answer": "increase", "Opt_1_def": "to separate something or someone from others", "Opt_2_def": "to make something better", "Opt_3_def": "to know or say who or what something is", "Opt_4_def": "to get bigger"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "I ____ vocabulary as the single most important aspect of learning English.", "Opt_1": "regard", "Opt_2": "define", "Opt_3": "analyze", "Opt_4": "reflect", "Answer": "regard", "Opt_1_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to state what something is or means", "Opt_3_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it", "Opt_4_def": "to think or consider"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government is bringing in a new law to ____ food manufacturers to label their products as high-, low- or medium fat.", "Opt_1": "require", "Opt_2": "collapse", "Opt_3": "insist", "Opt_4": "qualify", "Answer": "require", "Opt_1_def": "to need", "Opt_2_def": "to fall down completely and heavily; to fail", "Opt_3_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim", "Opt_4_def": "to become eligible"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "On your first day in a new school it is difficult to ____ all the information that you are given.", "Opt_1": "contemplate", "Opt_2": "assimilate", "Opt_3": "violate", "Opt_4": "illuminate", "Answer": "assimilate", "Opt_1_def": "to think about; to consider", "Opt_2_def": "to take in", "Opt_3_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_4_def": "to show clearly; to light up"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This is NOT a reliable ____ and you should simply ignore it.", "Opt_1": "statistic", "Opt_2": "plenty", "Opt_3": "innovation", "Opt_4": "effort", "Answer": "statistic", "Opt_1_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_2_def": "many, lots of", "Opt_3_def": "new object or idea", "Opt_4_def": "hard work; attempt"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Our ____ surveys did not differentiate between different types of questions, so we were unable to explore this issue.", "Opt_1": "exact", "Opt_2": "commercial", "Opt_3": "subjective", "Opt_4": "preliminary", "Answer": "preliminary", "Opt_1_def": "precise, opposite of approximate", "Opt_2_def": "to do with business", "Opt_3_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_4_def": "first; initial"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Most educational institutions have a required ____ for citations and references.", "Opt_1": "format", "Opt_2": "generation", "Opt_3": "incentive", "Opt_4": "concern", "Answer": "format", "Opt_1_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting", "Opt_2_def": "group of people all born around the same time", "Opt_3_def": "reason to do something", "Opt_4_def": "worry, fear"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The ____ I liked best in ESL class this year was Cultural Differences.", "Opt_1": "committee", "Opt_2": "topic", "Opt_3": "fee", "Opt_4": "staff", "Answer": "topic", "Opt_1_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue", "Opt_2_def": "area of interest or discussion", "Opt_3_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)", "Opt_4_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Traditional social skills strategies (such as board games about friendships and ____ classroom behavior) tend to be too subtle for many children.", "Opt_1": "ideal", "Opt_2": "appropriate", "Opt_3": "tough", "Opt_4": "widespread", "Answer": "appropriate", "Opt_1_def": "best, optimal", "Opt_2_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable", "Opt_3_def": "difficult, strong", "Opt_4_def": "common"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "I think we should ____ her work more closely for the next few weeks. She needs to know that we are concerned about her progress.", "Opt_1": "monitor", "Opt_2": "negotiate", "Opt_3": "achieve", "Opt_4": "repeat", "Answer": "monitor", "Opt_1_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )", "Opt_2_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)", "Opt_3_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)", "Opt_4_def": "to do or say again"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "In order to match you up with the most ____ roommate we can, please fill out the Housing Intake Questionaire.", "Opt_1": "utter", "Opt_2": "apparent", "Opt_3": "compatible", "Opt_4": "characteristic", "Answer": "compatible", "Opt_1_def": "complete, total", "Opt_2_def": "clear; obvious", "Opt_3_def": "able to work with someone or something else", "Opt_4_def": "typical"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If the student contacts you before or after the ____ with a valid excuse, you can cancel the appointment without penalty.", "Opt_1": "experiment", "Opt_2": "experience", "Opt_3": "dimension", "Opt_4": "deal", "Answer": "experiment", "Opt_1_def": "test", "Opt_2_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_3_def": "importance; amount", "Opt_4_def": "agreement"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The first ____ change in the business model came with Henry Ford's move toward standardization and applying the concepts of a production line to the car.", "Opt_1": "immense", "Opt_2": "subsequent", "Opt_3": "major", "Opt_4": "radical", "Answer": "radical", "Opt_1_def": "very large", "Opt_2_def": "next, following", "Opt_3_def": "important, large", "Opt_4_def": "extreme, strong"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The machine did not work properly because the person installing it did not ____ the instructions.", "Opt_1": "advocate", "Opt_2": "combine", "Opt_3": "assert", "Opt_4": "obey", "Answer": "obey", "Opt_1_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to put or go together", "Opt_3_def": "to claim, to say strongly", "Opt_4_def": "to do as commanded or expected"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The time has come, however, to quit spending time and money supporting ____ technologies and to concentrate on delivering better service.", "Opt_1": "remote", "Opt_2": "rapid", "Opt_3": "obsolete", "Opt_4": "elaborate", "Answer": "obsolete", "Opt_1_def": "far, distant, small", "Opt_2_def": "quick", "Opt_3_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date", "Opt_4_def": "detailed; complex"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "In this problem you have to ____ that x=7.", "Opt_1": "infer", "Opt_2": "behave", "Opt_3": "proceed", "Opt_4": "prove", "Answer": "prove", "Opt_1_def": "to come to a conclusion about something", "Opt_2_def": "to act or do things in a certain way", "Opt_3_def": "to go forward (and do ..)", "Opt_4_def": "to show to be true"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "He is an American citizen which obviously puts him in a different ____ from the kinds of individuals that the president has suggested might be suitable.", "Opt_1": "aid", "Opt_2": "point", "Opt_3": "event", "Opt_4": "category", "Answer": "category", "Opt_1_def": "help (often financial help)", "Opt_2_def": "purpose; reason; value", "Opt_3_def": "a happening", "Opt_4_def": "group of similar items"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "They sit there in every meeting but they never ____ their own ideas.", "Opt_1": "contribute", "Opt_2": "neglect", "Opt_3": "interrupt", "Opt_4": "refute", "Answer": "contribute", "Opt_1_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_2_def": "to not think about or care for", "Opt_3_def": "to stop something from happening", "Opt_4_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "This assignment is ____ on September 23.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The outcome of our ____ is that most students are against school uniform.", "Opt_1": "source", "Opt_2": "field", "Opt_3": "survey", "Opt_4": "policy", "Answer": "survey", "Opt_1_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_2_def": "area of interest or study", "Opt_3_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data", "Opt_4_def": "formal rules"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "My biggest regret about the book is that Gruchy did not ____ his personal experiences explicitly into the text.", "Opt_1": "revise", "Opt_2": "disturb", "Opt_3": "insert", "Opt_4": "request", "Answer": "insert", "Opt_1_def": "to change (in order to improve)", "Opt_2_def": "to interrupt, stop from working", "Opt_3_def": "to put in", "Opt_4_def": "to ask politely"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "There is not a ____ answer to your question. The most complete explanation I have found is at the Howstuffworks site.", "Opt_1": "dense", "Opt_2": "concise", "Opt_3": "anonymous", "Opt_4": "diverse", "Answer": "concise", "Opt_1_def": "thick; full; detailed", "Opt_2_def": "short, not detailed", "Opt_3_def": "having no name or known author", "Opt_4_def": "many and different"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "A student seeking a career in this ____ of study will have abundant opportunities to develop personal and professional skills.", "Opt_1": "objective", "Opt_2": "field", "Opt_3": "penalty", "Opt_4": "volume", "Answer": "field", "Opt_1_def": "aim or goal", "Opt_2_def": "area of interest or study", "Opt_3_def": "negative consequence; punishment", "Opt_4_def": "amount"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "What is your interpretation of his recent ____ behaviour?", "Opt_1": "odd", "Opt_2": "perpetual", "Opt_3": "forthcoming", "Opt_4": "sufficient", "Answer": "odd", "Opt_1_def": "strange, unusual", "Opt_2_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing", "Opt_3_def": "coming soon", "Opt_4_def": "enough"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The first ____ on the agenda is the proposal to increase working hours to 42 per work.", "Opt_1": "item", "Opt_2": "province", "Opt_3": "instinct", "Opt_4": "conflict", "Answer": "item", "Opt_1_def": "thing, element", "Opt_2_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_3_def": "natural feeling or reaction", "Opt_4_def": "problem, struggle or battle"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Recent research has investigated the traits that may ____ the development of drug addiction.", "Opt_1": "omit", "Opt_2": "affect", "Opt_3": "attend", "Opt_4": "underlie", "Answer": "underlie", "Opt_1_def": "to leave something out or not do something", "Opt_2_def": "to have an influence on", "Opt_3_def": "to go to, to be present at", "Opt_4_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "In the 1850s, texts did not circulate widely enough to ____ a revolution.", "Opt_1": "exceed", "Opt_2": "embody", "Opt_3": "react", "Opt_4": "provoke", "Answer": "provoke", "Opt_1_def": "to be more than or better than", "Opt_2_def": "to be a good example of ..", "Opt_3_def": "to respond", "Opt_4_def": "to cause to happen"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The CLAS Institute identifies, evaluates, and promotes ____ and appropriate early intervention and preschool practices that are sensitive to diverse cultural and linguistic backgrounds.", "Opt_1": "effective", "Opt_2": "numerous", "Opt_3": "consistent", "Opt_4": "genuine", "Answer": "effective", "Opt_1_def": "good, working well", "Opt_2_def": "very many", "Opt_3_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_4_def": "real and authentic"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The Supreme Court held that the free ____ of religion did not entitle an Orthodox Jew to wear a yarmulke when he was on duty as an officer of law.", "Opt_1": "theory", "Opt_2": "quantity", "Opt_3": "point", "Opt_4": "exercise", "Answer": "exercise", "Opt_1_def": "idea or hypothesis", "Opt_2_def": "amount", "Opt_3_def": "purpose; reason; value", "Opt_4_def": "a piece of work, activity"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "New challenges, opportunities, and demands are necessary to ensure that creativity and motivation do not ____ away.", "Opt_1": "exist", "Opt_2": "fulfill", "Opt_3": "fade", "Opt_4": "create", "Answer": "fade", "Opt_1_def": "to be alive, to be in the world", "Opt_2_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_3_def": "to disappear slowly", "Opt_4_def": "to make; to use your imagination to make something new"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Giuliani's leadership during New York City's darkest hours of the September 11th terrorist attacks earned him ____ praise and admiration.", "Opt_1": "logical", "Opt_2": "global", "Opt_3": "homogeneous", "Opt_4": "fortunate", "Answer": "global", "Opt_1_def": "making sense", "Opt_2_def": "world", "Opt_3_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics", "Opt_4_def": "lucky"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This note describes a scoring ____ for the co-reference task in MUC6.", "Opt_1": "instruction", "Opt_2": "scheme", "Opt_3": "means", "Opt_4": "substitute", "Answer": "scheme", "Opt_1_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something", "Opt_2_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_3_def": "way", "Opt_4_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "I was surprised that ____ me there were only about three or four people in favour of the proposal.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Sunnis believe that the Prophet Mohammed did not appoint a successor and therefore gave permission to Muslims to ____ or choose their own leader after his death.", "Opt_1": "belong", "Opt_2": "elect", "Opt_3": "fear", "Opt_4": "compile", "Answer": "elect", "Opt_1_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone", "Opt_2_def": "to choose by voting", "Opt_3_def": "to be concerned or frightened about", "Opt_4_def": "to put together (often in a list"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This is NOT a reliable ____ and you should simply ignore it.", "Opt_1": "survey", "Opt_2": "potential", "Opt_3": "statistic", "Opt_4": "strategy", "Answer": "statistic", "Opt_1_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data", "Opt_2_def": "good possibility", "Opt_3_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_4_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "With noise levels of this magnitude, hearing damage is a ____ problem unless some sort of hearing protection is used.", "Opt_1": "mobile", "Opt_2": "distinct", "Opt_3": "credible", "Opt_4": "legitimate", "Answer": "distinct", "Opt_1_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_2_def": "clear and strong", "Opt_3_def": "believable", "Opt_4_def": "correct; allowed"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Traditional social skills strategies (such as board games about friendships and appropriate classroom behavior) ____ to be too subtle for many children.", "Opt_1": "tend", "Opt_2": "block", "Opt_3": "qualify", "Opt_4": "accuse", "Answer": "tend", "Opt_1_def": "to often behave in a certain way", "Opt_2_def": "to not allow; to stop or prevent", "Opt_3_def": "to become eligible", "Opt_4_def": "to blame"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The monks found it difficult to adapt to changes in ____ and in the economy, and they also found it difficult to adapt to challenges presented by the new learning made available through translations of ancient Greek texts by way of Arabic.", "Opt_1": "victory", "Opt_2": "society", "Opt_3": "environment", "Opt_4": "proportion", "Answer": "society", "Opt_1_def": "win", "Opt_2_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country", "Opt_3_def": "the world around us", "Opt_4_def": "amount; number; percentage"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The 9-11 Commission failed to ____ or address the multiple war game exercises that were being conducted that day, out of the White House.", "Opt_1": "estimate", "Opt_2": "mention", "Opt_3": "trigger", "Opt_4": "accumulate", "Answer": "mention", "Opt_1_def": "to make an intelligent guess", "Opt_2_def": "to say; state", "Opt_3_def": "to (cause to) start", "Opt_4_def": "to grow; to gather together"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "While a considerable degree of agreement was attained, a ____ approach to food policy could not be reached.", "Opt_1": "overall", "Opt_2": "uniform", "Opt_3": "entire", "Opt_4": "chief", "Answer": "uniform", "Opt_1_def": "general", "Opt_2_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_3_def": "whole, all", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Most people who use a wheelchair or mobility devices do not ____ them as confining. They are viewed as liberating; a means of getting around.", "Opt_1": "deserve", "Opt_2": "consent", "Opt_3": "claim", "Opt_4": "regard", "Answer": "regard", "Opt_1_def": "to have the right to something", "Opt_2_def": "to agree", "Opt_3_def": "to state to be true", "Opt_4_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The lack of ____ parking spaces is a significant detriment to faculty and students.", "Opt_1": "main", "Opt_2": "radical", "Opt_3": "available", "Opt_4": "temporary", "Answer": "available", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "extreme, strong", "Opt_3_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_4_def": "for a short or limited time"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The assignments and quizzes form an integral part of the ____ grade and you may not obtain a good grade if you ignore them.", "Opt_1": "impact", "Opt_2": "range", "Opt_3": "course", "Opt_4": "circumstances", "Answer": "course", "Opt_1_def": "effect", "Opt_2_def": "extent, distance between two points", "Opt_3_def": "a subject or period of study", "Opt_4_def": "situation"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If you saved a file to a library PC running Windows ____ to a crash or being logged out, you should be able to recover it.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Storage of personal information not ____ to university business must be limited and must not interfere in any way with the storage and maintenance of university data.", "Opt_1": "valid", "Opt_2": "related", "Opt_3": "unique", "Opt_4": "likely", "Answer": "related", "Opt_1_def": "correct", "Opt_2_def": "connected; having something to do with each other", "Opt_3_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind", "Opt_4_def": "probable"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "We need to put our minds together and decide if we need to ____ among our institutions to provide a new service.", "Opt_1": "collaborate", "Opt_2": "view", "Opt_3": "solve", "Opt_4": "label", "Answer": "collaborate", "Opt_1_def": "to work together", "Opt_2_def": "to have an opinion", "Opt_3_def": "to find an answer", "Opt_4_def": "to give a name to someone or something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Financial ____ is the term we use to describe a variety of funds available to help students and their families finance the cost of a Berry College education.", "Opt_1": "career", "Opt_2": "range", "Opt_3": "aid", "Opt_4": "debt", "Answer": "aid", "Opt_1_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_2_def": "extent, distance between two points", "Opt_3_def": "help (often financial help)", "Opt_4_def": "something owed to another person (often money)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If breastfeeding is not possible, ____ infant milk formulas are a good alternative.", "Opt_1": "commercial", "Opt_2": "concise", "Opt_3": "forthcoming", "Opt_4": "permanent", "Answer": "commercial", "Opt_1_def": "to do with business", "Opt_2_def": "short, not detailed", "Opt_3_def": "coming soon", "Opt_4_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Knowing when to seek ____ for mental health disorders is important for parents and families.", "Opt_1": "treatment", "Opt_2": "stereotype", "Opt_3": "level", "Opt_4": "insight", "Answer": "treatment", "Opt_1_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)", "Opt_2_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)", "Opt_3_def": "standard; layer; amount", "Opt_4_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Smith starts out with a ____ idea of what she wants to achieve.", "Opt_1": "loose", "Opt_2": "adjacent", "Opt_3": "drastic", "Opt_4": "infinite", "Answer": "loose", "Opt_1_def": "not firm or finished", "Opt_2_def": "next to", "Opt_3_def": "severe; great", "Opt_4_def": "without an end"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The winner of the competition must devise a plan to remove greenhouse gases from the ____ without creating adverse effects.", "Opt_1": "forecast", "Opt_2": "manner", "Opt_3": "advantage", "Opt_4": "atmosphere", "Answer": "atmosphere", "Opt_1_def": "prediction", "Opt_2_def": "way of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "benefit", "Opt_4_def": "mood among people or groups"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The combination of natural and human systems adds an additional ____ of complexity to the interactions.", "Opt_1": "district", "Opt_2": "command", "Opt_3": "interior", "Opt_4": "layer", "Answer": "layer", "Opt_1_def": "region of a city", "Opt_2_def": "control", "Opt_3_def": "inside", "Opt_4_def": "level"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "In an article in the March 11, 2004 issue of Nature, the investigators report that female mice ____ the ability to make new egg cells well into adulthood.", "Opt_1": "retain", "Opt_2": "risk", "Opt_3": "isolate", "Opt_4": "detect", "Answer": "retain", "Opt_1_def": "to keep", "Opt_2_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure", "Opt_3_def": "to separate something or someone from others", "Opt_4_def": "to see, find or notice"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "He did not ____ to develop a particularly good balance in his own life until he was able to stop worrying about what others thought of him.", "Opt_1": "adjust", "Opt_2": "anticipate", "Opt_3": "manage", "Opt_4": "pursue", "Answer": "manage", "Opt_1_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)", "Opt_2_def": "to expect", "Opt_3_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to follow (or do)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "We had to make sure that our customers in China knew that what we were doing was not an attack on Chinese industry, but a dispute over a ____ issue.", "Opt_1": "legitimate", "Opt_2": "actual", "Opt_3": "adequate", "Opt_4": "spare", "Answer": "legitimate", "Opt_1_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_2_def": "real", "Opt_3_def": "good enough; ok", "Opt_4_def": "not needed"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "My overall impression is that this plan describes a very ambitious attempt to ____ an important issue in a scientifically credible manner.", "Opt_1": "involve", "Opt_2": "suffer", "Opt_3": "address", "Opt_4": "enforce", "Answer": "address", "Opt_1_def": "to include or mean", "Opt_2_def": "to experience something bad or painful", "Opt_3_def": "to give attention to (an issue)", "Opt_4_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The book focuses on the key ____ the family plays as teenagers navigate the difficult transition from childhood to adulthood.", "Opt_1": "role", "Opt_2": "fallacy", "Opt_3": "layer", "Opt_4": "constraint", "Answer": "role", "Opt_1_def": "job or function", "Opt_2_def": "mistake; false belief", "Opt_3_def": "level", "Opt_4_def": "to hold back; to prevent"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Through much of the War, the U.S. and its Allies could not ____ a fully effective blockade against Germany.", "Opt_1": "attain", "Opt_2": "enforce", "Opt_3": "violate", "Opt_4": "occupy", "Answer": "enforce", "Opt_1_def": "to get, achieve", "Opt_2_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)", "Opt_3_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_4_def": "to up space or time"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "There will be a ____ class after school today for those who want extra practice for the test.", "Opt_1": "concise", "Opt_2": "supplementary", "Opt_3": "global", "Opt_4": "overall", "Answer": "supplementary", "Opt_1_def": "short, not detailed", "Opt_2_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_3_def": "world", "Opt_4_def": "general"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Therefore, if a calf has not received an ____ amount of quality colostrum, the calf may not be able to resist disease.", "Opt_1": "elementary", "Opt_2": "crucial", "Opt_3": "adequate", "Opt_4": "compatible", "Answer": "adequate", "Opt_1_def": "easy", "Opt_2_def": "extremely important", "Opt_3_def": "good enough; ok", "Opt_4_def": "able to work with someone or something else"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Your low grades will ____ you of the chance of taking part in sports trips.", "Opt_1": "oppose", "Opt_2": "absorb", "Opt_3": "protect", "Opt_4": "deprive", "Answer": "deprive", "Opt_1_def": "to be against or fight against something", "Opt_2_def": "to take in; to take up", "Opt_3_def": "to keep something out of danger", "Opt_4_def": "to take away (the opportunity)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "ESL students fare better in classrooms where the teacher is ____ of their special needs.", "Opt_1": "efficient", "Opt_2": "aware", "Opt_3": "initial", "Opt_4": "current", "Answer": "aware", "Opt_1_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_2_def": "knowing", "Opt_3_def": "starting, first", "Opt_4_def": "happening now"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It's good that the school ____s ____ new, young teachers every year. They can stimulate discussions about teaching methods.", "Opt_1": "employ", "Opt_2": "assist", "Opt_3": "assume", "Opt_4": "obtain", "Answer": "employ", "Opt_1_def": "to give a job to someone; to use", "Opt_2_def": "to help", "Opt_3_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict", "Opt_4_def": "to get"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Plants that possess certain traits or characteristics not common to the ____ species are referred to as biotypes.", "Opt_1": "entire", "Opt_2": "voluntary", "Opt_3": "former", "Opt_4": "vital", "Answer": "entire", "Opt_1_def": "whole, all", "Opt_2_def": "done freely; from personal choice", "Opt_3_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two", "Opt_4_def": "very important"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This widespread ____ was caused by the insufficient amount of media coverage on topic.", "Opt_1": "quality", "Opt_2": "ignorance", "Opt_3": "procedure", "Opt_4": "revolution", "Answer": "ignorance", "Opt_1_def": "worth or value", "Opt_2_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_3_def": "the way to do something", "Opt_4_def": "a time of great change"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The only ____ of some people is to accumulate as much money as possible.", "Opt_1": "ability", "Opt_2": "route", "Opt_3": "goal", "Opt_4": "area", "Answer": "goal", "Opt_1_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well", "Opt_2_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing", "Opt_3_def": "aim or intention", "Opt_4_def": "field, sphere"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The ____ put forward in this paper depends in no degree upon the completeness of our knowledge of the former condition of the organic world.", "Opt_1": "comment", "Opt_2": "disaster", "Opt_3": "legislation", "Opt_4": "hypothesis", "Answer": "hypothesis", "Opt_1_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion", "Opt_2_def": "a huge problem or failure", "Opt_3_def": "governmental rule; law", "Opt_4_def": "idea or prediction"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Frankfurt International School needs to ____ its curriculum with that of German state schools.", "Opt_1": "appear", "Opt_2": "create", "Opt_3": "approach", "Opt_4": "align", "Answer": "align", "Opt_1_def": "to come, be seen", "Opt_2_def": "to make; to use your imagination to make something new", "Opt_3_def": "to near; to get closer", "Opt_4_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Her problems are close to the ____ and tend to be expressed in more direct, less symbolic, behavioral and emotional terms.", "Opt_1": "prejudice", "Opt_2": "delay", "Opt_3": "detriment", "Opt_4": "surface", "Answer": "surface", "Opt_1_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background", "Opt_2_def": "lateness", "Opt_3_def": "disadvantage", "Opt_4_def": "the outside layer of an object"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The reduced rainfall of recent years will ____ large parts of the country into desert.", "Opt_1": "transform", "Opt_2": "fear", "Opt_3": "attain", "Opt_4": "request", "Answer": "transform", "Opt_1_def": "to change (often completely)", "Opt_2_def": "to be concerned or frightened about", "Opt_3_def": "to get, achieve", "Opt_4_def": "to ask politely"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The cyclist tried to ____ that he had not used drugs, but the blood tests proved the opposite.", "Opt_1": "examine", "Opt_2": "discuss", "Opt_3": "own", "Opt_4": "claim", "Answer": "claim", "Opt_1_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_2_def": "to talk about", "Opt_3_def": "to have or possess", "Opt_4_def": "to state to be true"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Your writing shows a ____ lack of care or thought.", "Opt_1": "basic", "Opt_2": "deliberate", "Opt_3": "secure", "Opt_4": "hostile", "Answer": "basic", "Opt_1_def": "first or easy", "Opt_2_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_3_def": "safe", "Opt_4_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Dairy farmers have led the latest in a long series of protests by agricultural associations, ____ the record high prices for farm products.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If you can't do your homework, you should ask your parents to ____ you.", "Opt_1": "assist", "Opt_2": "block", "Opt_3": "append", "Opt_4": "interact", "Answer": "assist", "Opt_1_def": "to help", "Opt_2_def": "to not allow; to stop or prevent", "Opt_3_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)", "Opt_4_def": "to react, to affect and be affected"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Much of the literature reviewed by the ____ failed to specify in sufficient detail the definition of a medication error used in the study.", "Opt_1": "revolution", "Opt_2": "penalty", "Opt_3": "committee", "Opt_4": "instruction", "Answer": "committee", "Opt_1_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_2_def": "negative consequence; punishment", "Opt_3_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue", "Opt_4_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "My ____ does not require contacting people because I intend to use existing or archived material.", "Opt_1": "surface", "Opt_2": "lack", "Opt_3": "research", "Opt_4": "legislation", "Answer": "research", "Opt_1_def": "the outside layer of an object", "Opt_2_def": "absence of a thing", "Opt_3_def": "study; the finding of information", "Opt_4_def": "governmental rule; law"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "What might cause my computer to ____ oddly and even insult me, and how can I fix it?", "Opt_1": "monitor", "Opt_2": "override", "Opt_3": "manipulate", "Opt_4": "behave", "Answer": "behave", "Opt_1_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )", "Opt_2_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard", "Opt_3_def": "to (use and) change", "Opt_4_def": "to act or do things in a certain way"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Some countries, such as Switzerland, remained ____ in the last world war.", "Opt_1": "vast", "Opt_2": "final", "Opt_3": "confident", "Opt_4": "neutral", "Answer": "neutral", "Opt_1_def": "very large", "Opt_2_def": "last", "Opt_3_def": "sure that something will happen", "Opt_4_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "To include an image on your website, you will need to ____ the image into your webpage using an HTML editor.", "Opt_1": "cover", "Opt_2": "owe", "Opt_3": "broadcast", "Opt_4": "insert", "Answer": "insert", "Opt_1_def": "to do; to complete", "Opt_2_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)", "Opt_3_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)", "Opt_4_def": "to put in"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It is not difficult to speculate on what could happen to these laws if the computer really does change our ____ to knowledge.", "Opt_1": "attitude", "Opt_2": "area", "Opt_3": "location", "Opt_4": "aim", "Answer": "attitude", "Opt_1_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)", "Opt_2_def": "field, sphere", "Opt_3_def": "place, where something or someone is", "Opt_4_def": "goal or intention"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "You can be fairly certain what you read at the government ____ is accurate and up-to-date.", "Opt_1": "attack", "Opt_2": "mechanism", "Opt_3": "stereotype", "Opt_4": "site", "Answer": "site", "Opt_1_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage", "Opt_2_def": "procedure, process", "Opt_3_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)", "Opt_4_def": "place"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Typically held the 3rd week of February, this is an annual event that helps College of Fine Arts students explore ____s, develop strategies to pursue ____ and artistic goals successfully.", "Opt_1": "doubt", "Opt_2": "objection", "Opt_3": "career", "Opt_4": "state", "Answer": "career", "Opt_1_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_2_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval", "Opt_3_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_4_def": "condition, situation"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "In many cases, ____ stating to the student that the behavior is unacceptable and must not occur again is sufficient.", "Opt_1": "eventually", "Opt_2": "largely", "Opt_3": "simply", "Opt_4": "thereby", "Answer": "simply", "Opt_1_def": "in the end", "Opt_2_def": "mostly", "Opt_3_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_4_def": "by doing this"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "This also helps you determine which variables it is essential to ____ to avoid an ambiguous answer.", "Opt_1": "control", "Opt_2": "suspect", "Opt_3": "condemn", "Opt_4": "identify", "Answer": "control", "Opt_1_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to believe", "Opt_3_def": "to express strong disapproval", "Opt_4_def": "to know or say who or what something is"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Future research would need to ensure that participants did not engage in any other activities immediately ____ to the study at hand.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "You are advised to undertake serious language study both before and during the course of the program but ____ language study is not a criterion for selection.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Some environmental scientists ____ that the dangers of global warming are even greater than most people suppose.", "Opt_1": "deviate", "Opt_2": "signify", "Opt_3": "claim", "Opt_4": "assume", "Answer": "claim", "Opt_1_def": "to be different", "Opt_2_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_3_def": "to state to be true", "Opt_4_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If you are applying from a country in which English is not the official language, you are required to submit ____ of English language proficiency.", "Opt_1": "growth", "Opt_2": "prospect", "Opt_3": "prestige", "Opt_4": "evidence", "Answer": "evidence", "Opt_1_def": "development, increase", "Opt_2_def": "chance, likelihood", "Opt_3_def": "fame and respect", "Opt_4_def": "proof, signs"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Please write a ____ of the most important causes of the French Revolution.", "Opt_1": "justice", "Opt_2": "summary", "Opt_3": "fund", "Opt_4": "behalf", "Answer": "summary", "Opt_1_def": "fairness in law", "Opt_2_def": "a short account of the most important details", "Opt_3_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_4_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government has announced its ____ for the introduction of the new tax system over the next 5 years.", "Opt_1": "attention", "Opt_2": "schedule", "Opt_3": "survey", "Opt_4": "statistic", "Answer": "schedule", "Opt_1_def": "focus", "Opt_2_def": "timetable", "Opt_3_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data", "Opt_4_def": "mathematical number"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Many universities make their materials ____ to students online.", "Opt_1": "smooth", "Opt_2": "available", "Opt_3": "pure", "Opt_4": "visual", "Answer": "available", "Opt_1_def": "easy, unproblematic", "Opt_2_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_3_def": "complete, 100%", "Opt_4_def": "to do with sight and seeing"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "We should never praise or ____ any person on account of outward actions that are common to all; but only on account of their principles.", "Opt_1": "extend", "Opt_2": "blame", "Opt_3": "modify", "Opt_4": "condemn", "Answer": "blame", "Opt_1_def": "to make longer in time or space", "Opt_2_def": "to accuse", "Opt_3_def": "to change", "Opt_4_def": "to express strong disapproval"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government has come under ____ to reduce the tax on petrol because of the high cost of oil.", "Opt_1": "pressure", "Opt_2": "disaster", "Opt_3": "portion", "Opt_4": "license", "Answer": "pressure", "Opt_1_def": "force; influence; stress", "Opt_2_def": "a huge problem or failure", "Opt_3_def": "part, amount", "Opt_4_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "In this particular poem, Dalton, while asking what woman's ____ is, also advises man on woman's potential and her proper place in life.", "Opt_1": "sphere", "Opt_2": "image", "Opt_3": "environment", "Opt_4": "reluctance", "Answer": "sphere", "Opt_1_def": "area of interest", "Opt_2_def": "picture", "Opt_3_def": "the world around us", "Opt_4_def": "unwillingness; hesitation"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The first section of this course is concerned with understanding the basic concepts of design: How to ____ and talk about visual material.", "Opt_1": "ensure", "Opt_2": "correlate", "Opt_3": "attract", "Opt_4": "analyze", "Answer": "analyze", "Opt_1_def": "to make sure (of)", "Opt_2_def": "to have a close connection", "Opt_3_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like", "Opt_4_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The Euro has taken on a ____ far greater than its economic substance.", "Opt_1": "notion", "Opt_2": "argument", "Opt_3": "fault", "Opt_4": "dimension", "Answer": "dimension", "Opt_1_def": "idea; concept", "Opt_2_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)", "Opt_3_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem", "Opt_4_def": "importance; amount"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The students began to ____ when their teacher told them they would have a test on the last day before Christmas.", "Opt_1": "insert", "Opt_2": "coordinate", "Opt_3": "protest", "Opt_4": "displace", "Answer": "protest", "Opt_1_def": "to put in", "Opt_2_def": "to bring things or people together so that they work well", "Opt_3_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_4_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The system uses a novel inference engine that does not ____ users to explicitly provide information about the start or ending points of their journeys.", "Opt_1": "achieve", "Opt_2": "add", "Opt_3": "require", "Opt_4": "refuse", "Answer": "require", "Opt_1_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)", "Opt_2_def": "to include; to give or say extra", "Opt_3_def": "to need", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Art is every artist's attempt to communicate in a way ____ words what they feel, see, and think about life.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The school wanted to raise money from its ex-students, but the ____ was an utter failure.", "Opt_1": "stimulate", "Opt_2": "attempt", "Opt_3": "emerge", "Opt_4": "depend", "Answer": "attempt", "Opt_1_def": "to interest, make grow or encourage", "Opt_2_def": "to try", "Opt_3_def": "to come out; to become known", "Opt_4_def": "be influenced (by)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Arming the Bosnian Serbs was regarded as a political rather than a ____ issue.", "Opt_1": "dynamic", "Opt_2": "fundamental", "Opt_3": "military", "Opt_4": "positive", "Answer": "military", "Opt_1_def": "changing; growing; energetic", "Opt_2_def": "very important", "Opt_3_def": "to do with army", "Opt_4_def": "good; optimistic"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Among male baboons, dominance rank is ____ of maternal rank, and changes markedly with age; males reach their highest rank between 8 and 10 years of age.", "Opt_1": "considerable", "Opt_2": "official", "Opt_3": "independent", "Opt_4": "competent", "Answer": "independent", "Opt_1_def": "very big; very much", "Opt_2_def": "approved by an authority", "Opt_3_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else", "Opt_4_def": "good at something (often a job)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The doctor examined the patient carefully, ____ that he forgot to check blood pressure.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Newspapers employ people to ____ the articles submitted by their journalists, but not all mistakes are found.", "Opt_1": "prefer", "Opt_2": "override", "Opt_3": "enhance", "Opt_4": "edit", "Answer": "edit", "Opt_1_def": "to like better", "Opt_2_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard", "Opt_3_def": "to make something better", "Opt_4_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "They were small-minded people and could not ____ students who were superior them.", "Opt_1": "exist", "Opt_2": "integrate", "Opt_3": "measure", "Opt_4": "tolerate", "Answer": "tolerate", "Opt_1_def": "to be alive, to be in the world", "Opt_2_def": "to fit into a new situation", "Opt_3_def": "to find out how much there is of something", "Opt_4_def": "to allow to happen; to bear"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Edwards ruled on the evidence presented and said Gary Edwards was not ____ to play.", "Opt_1": "annual", "Opt_2": "explicit", "Opt_3": "substantial", "Opt_4": "eligible", "Answer": "eligible", "Opt_1_def": "yearly", "Opt_2_def": "clearly and openly expressed", "Opt_3_def": "large", "Opt_4_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The purpose of this study was to explore the internal and ____ factors influencing the career development of first generation Filipina Americans.", "Opt_1": "initial", "Opt_2": "external", "Opt_3": "various", "Opt_4": "main", "Answer": "external", "Opt_1_def": "starting, first", "Opt_2_def": "outside", "Opt_3_def": "several, of different kinds", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Following today's meeting the headmaster will ____ to parents that they do not send their children to school with junk food.", "Opt_1": "propose", "Opt_2": "inspect", "Opt_3": "conceal", "Opt_4": "oppose", "Answer": "propose", "Opt_1_def": "to suggest", "Opt_2_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_3_def": "to hide", "Opt_4_def": "to be against or fight against something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Antarctica is a very ____ environment. Many explorers have lost their lives there.", "Opt_1": "hostile", "Opt_2": "physical", "Opt_3": "spontaneous", "Opt_4": "uniform", "Answer": "hostile", "Opt_1_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to", "Opt_2_def": "of the body", "Opt_3_def": "happening without warning or planning", "Opt_4_def": "having the same qualities"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "A small apartment in the middle of a busy city is not a ____ place to keep a large dog.", "Opt_1": "annual", "Opt_2": "uniform", "Opt_3": "sole", "Opt_4": "suitable", "Answer": "suitable", "Opt_1_def": "yearly", "Opt_2_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_3_def": "only", "Opt_4_def": "good for a particular job or purpose"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Farmers rotate their crops. This ____ that they do not grow the same thing on the same field for more than one year.", "Opt_1": "region", "Opt_2": "course", "Opt_3": "interior", "Opt_4": "means", "Answer": "means", "Opt_1_def": "part of a place", "Opt_2_def": "a subject or period of study", "Opt_3_def": "inside", "Opt_4_def": "way"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Sometimes it is necessary to impose a ____ on the number of solutions searched for, since in general the number of such solutions could be infinite.", "Opt_1": "hierarchy", "Opt_2": "constraint", "Opt_3": "limit", "Opt_4": "profit", "Answer": "limit", "Opt_1_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_2_def": "to hold back; to prevent", "Opt_3_def": "extent, boundary", "Opt_4_def": "money gained"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "How can I ____ access to my Web pages?", "Opt_1": "restrict", "Opt_2": "undergo", "Opt_3": "motivate", "Opt_4": "underlie", "Answer": "restrict", "Opt_1_def": "to limit", "Opt_2_def": "to receive or experience", "Opt_3_def": "to get someone interested enough to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Blair will need to ____ the Americans that Europeans will no longer permit Saddam to play games with the inspectors.", "Opt_1": "persuade", "Opt_2": "illustrate", "Opt_3": "exclude", "Opt_4": "improve", "Answer": "persuade", "Opt_1_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something", "Opt_2_def": "to show; to make clear", "Opt_3_def": "to leave out; opposite of include", "Opt_4_def": "to get better"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The data is ambiguous as some analysts measure this ____ according to different moments of the year, geographic regions and other variables.", "Opt_1": "authority", "Opt_2": "format", "Opt_3": "staff", "Opt_4": "figure", "Answer": "figure", "Opt_1_def": "control (right to control)", "Opt_2_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting", "Opt_3_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)", "Opt_4_def": "number"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Governments are considering how to exploit the ____ mineral resources buried under the ice in Antarctica.", "Opt_1": "substantial", "Opt_2": "forthcoming", "Opt_3": "vast", "Opt_4": "smooth", "Answer": "vast", "Opt_1_def": "large", "Opt_2_def": "coming soon", "Opt_3_def": "very large", "Opt_4_def": "easy, unproblematic"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Strong families ____ the ability to manage both daily stressors and difficult life crises creatively and effectively.", "Opt_1": "deserve", "Opt_2": "possess", "Opt_3": "fear", "Opt_4": "include", "Answer": "possess", "Opt_1_def": "to have the right to something", "Opt_2_def": "to have or own", "Opt_3_def": "to be concerned or frightened about", "Opt_4_def": "to put in; to have in"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The ____ of the aid money that has been allocated to Afghanistan has been wasted.", "Opt_1": "minimum", "Opt_2": "bulk", "Opt_3": "point", "Opt_4": "benefit", "Answer": "bulk", "Opt_1_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_2_def": "majority; largest part", "Opt_3_def": "purpose; reason; value", "Opt_4_def": "advantage"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If we learn to communicate effectively with others and are willing to risk sharing our own feelings and ____ other's feelings, many rewards will await us.", "Opt_1": "correspond", "Opt_2": "respect", "Opt_3": "avoid", "Opt_4": "acknowledge", "Answer": "respect", "Opt_1_def": "to be related to", "Opt_2_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something", "Opt_3_def": "to not do something or go somewhere", "Opt_4_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Parents often ____ their children's choice of clothes or music..", "Opt_1": "impose", "Opt_2": "possess", "Opt_3": "criticize", "Opt_4": "anticipate", "Answer": "criticize", "Opt_1_def": "to force; to require to happen", "Opt_2_def": "to have or own", "Opt_3_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "to expect"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "They faced problems for which they did not have the ____ or the training.", "Opt_1": "equipment", "Opt_2": "trait", "Opt_3": "rise", "Opt_4": "event", "Answer": "equipment", "Opt_1_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)", "Opt_2_def": "characteristic; aspect", "Opt_3_def": "to go up", "Opt_4_def": "a happening"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Teachers and parents can learn and ____ ideas for helping to work for more successful outcomes in the transition from school to adult life.", "Opt_1": "train", "Opt_2": "share", "Opt_3": "qualify", "Opt_4": "recur", "Answer": "share", "Opt_1_def": "to teach someone how to do a job", "Opt_2_def": "to exchange; to give", "Opt_3_def": "to become eligible", "Opt_4_def": "to happen again"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "She says she's not a very good pianist, but I know that the ____ is true and she's just being modest.", "Opt_1": "phase", "Opt_2": "target", "Opt_3": "detriment", "Opt_4": "contrary", "Answer": "contrary", "Opt_1_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_2_def": "aim, goal", "Opt_3_def": "disadvantage", "Opt_4_def": "opposite"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Until ____ there have been few sources of information about the morphological and syntactic structure of the Kam language.", "Opt_1": "fairly", "Opt_2": "largely", "Opt_3": "recently", "Opt_4": "merely", "Answer": "recently", "Opt_1_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_2_def": "mostly", "Opt_3_def": "in the near past", "Opt_4_def": "only, just, simply"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The writer was not careful when taking notes because he does not understand what plagiarism is, or because he is not ____ of what he is doing.", "Opt_1": "compatible", "Opt_2": "verbal", "Opt_3": "conscious", "Opt_4": "positive", "Answer": "conscious", "Opt_1_def": "able to work with someone or something else", "Opt_2_def": "to do with words and language (especially the spoken language)", "Opt_3_def": "aware, knowing", "Opt_4_def": "good; optimistic"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The only ____ of having computers in the classroom is that they are loud and make the room hot.", "Opt_1": "evidence", "Opt_2": "drawback", "Opt_3": "access", "Opt_4": "choice", "Answer": "drawback", "Opt_1_def": "proof, signs", "Opt_2_def": "disadvantage, problem", "Opt_3_def": "the right to enter or use", "Opt_4_def": "decision, selection"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The additional time is necessary to ____ him to make a sound decision on an Alaska natural gas transportation system.", "Opt_1": "trigger", "Opt_2": "transmit", "Opt_3": "disrupt", "Opt_4": "enable", "Answer": "enable", "Opt_1_def": "to (cause to) start", "Opt_2_def": "to send or convey", "Opt_3_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage", "Opt_4_def": "to make something or someone able to do something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Over the course of the period there is a ____ rise in the status of the painter, sculptor, and architect and a growing sympathy expressed for the visual arts.", "Opt_1": "optional", "Opt_2": "steady", "Opt_3": "suitable", "Opt_4": "subsequent", "Answer": "steady", "Opt_1_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want", "Opt_2_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm", "Opt_3_def": "good for a particular job or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "next, following"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Students who take the class are expected to choose a ____ problem they would like to address and collaborate with each other in researching it.", "Opt_1": "ancient", "Opt_2": "identical", "Opt_3": "comprehensive", "Opt_4": "contemporary", "Answer": "contemporary", "Opt_1_def": "very old", "Opt_2_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_3_def": "full, complete", "Opt_4_def": "of this time, happening now"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Some subjects in our school have a higher ____ than others. Everyone wants to take science, but few want to study a second language.", "Opt_1": "mixture", "Opt_2": "status", "Opt_3": "exponent", "Opt_4": "access", "Answer": "status", "Opt_1_def": "combination", "Opt_2_def": "position, standing", "Opt_3_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion", "Opt_4_def": "the right to enter or use"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "This is not a defect in the notion of ____ development as much as it is a problem with the fiscal structure of Alaska.", "Opt_1": "available", "Opt_2": "economic", "Opt_3": "likely", "Opt_4": "accurate", "Answer": "economic", "Opt_1_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_2_def": "financial; to do with money", "Opt_3_def": "probable", "Opt_4_def": "exact, containing no mistakes"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "You ____ us all an apology for using this forum for your personal beliefs when it is a forum for scientific reasoning.", "Opt_1": "suppress", "Opt_2": "owe", "Opt_3": "impress", "Opt_4": "absorb", "Answer": "owe", "Opt_1_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen", "Opt_2_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)", "Opt_3_def": "to create a favourable reaction", "Opt_4_def": "to take in; to take up"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Although two weeks are dedicated to its development at the end of the semester you should not conclude that this is enough time for the ____ project.", "Opt_1": "entire", "Opt_2": "chief", "Opt_3": "firm", "Opt_4": "remote", "Answer": "entire", "Opt_1_def": "whole, all", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "strong, cannot be changed", "Opt_4_def": "far, distant, small"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The lawyer was acting on ____ of the two children who had lost their parents in a car accident.", "Opt_1": "behalf", "Opt_2": "custom", "Opt_3": "dispute", "Opt_4": "coincidence", "Answer": "behalf", "Opt_1_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of", "Opt_2_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)", "Opt_3_def": "argument; conflict", "Opt_4_def": "an uncommon happening of two things"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Counselors will begin on-going sessions with a student only after having obtained signed assent of the student and signed ____ of the parent.", "Opt_1": "overcome", "Opt_2": "preserve", "Opt_3": "assert", "Opt_4": "consent", "Answer": "consent", "Opt_1_def": "to conquer, defeat", "Opt_2_def": "forward,\" said Michele Gougeon.", "Opt_3_def": "to claim, to say strongly", "Opt_4_def": "to agree"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "This paper documents ____ findings from a nationwide survey that investigates substance abuse.", "Opt_1": "precise", "Opt_2": "cautious", "Opt_3": "wise", "Opt_4": "preliminary", "Answer": "preliminary", "Opt_1_def": "exact", "Opt_2_def": "careful", "Opt_3_def": "intelligent; sensible", "Opt_4_def": "first; initial"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Plants that ____ certain traits or characteristics not common to the entire species are referred to as biotypes.", "Opt_1": "devote", "Opt_2": "dictate", "Opt_3": "possess", "Opt_4": "revise", "Answer": "possess", "Opt_1_def": "to give (time) to", "Opt_2_def": "to tell someone what to do", "Opt_3_def": "to have or own", "Opt_4_def": "to change (in order to improve)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The current ____ of our anatomy information system has evolved from several previous systems.", "Opt_1": "category", "Opt_2": "victory", "Opt_3": "version", "Opt_4": "contrary", "Answer": "version", "Opt_1_def": "group of similar items", "Opt_2_def": "win", "Opt_3_def": "form", "Opt_4_def": "opposite"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The headmaster's decision is sure to ____ much discussion among teachers and students at the school.", "Opt_1": "provoke", "Opt_2": "prepare", "Opt_3": "assess", "Opt_4": "depend", "Answer": "provoke", "Opt_1_def": "to cause to happen", "Opt_2_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)", "Opt_3_def": "to judge or test", "Opt_4_def": "be influenced (by)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Students are encouraged to ____ not only on the skills and knowledge related to the high stakes tests but also the skills and knowledge to perform more authentic tasks.", "Opt_1": "deprive", "Opt_2": "focus", "Opt_3": "absorb", "Opt_4": "appeal", "Answer": "focus", "Opt_1_def": "to take away (the opportunity)", "Opt_2_def": "to direct attention (on an issue)", "Opt_3_def": "to take in; to take up", "Opt_4_def": "to complain against an official judgment; to make a strong request"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The school is constructing a new science block ____ the sports field.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "A common ____ of dispute between the teacher and a student is when the student comes late to class for no good reason.", "Opt_1": "scheme", "Opt_2": "territory", "Opt_3": "cause", "Opt_4": "bias", "Answer": "cause", "Opt_1_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_2_def": "land; area (of interest)", "Opt_3_def": "the reason why something happens", "Opt_4_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "She said sorry to the teacher and ____ avoided a detention.", "Opt_1": "barely", "Opt_2": "perhaps", "Opt_3": "thereby", "Opt_4": "simultaneously", "Answer": "thereby", "Opt_1_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_2_def": "maybe, possibly", "Opt_3_def": "by doing this", "Opt_4_def": "at the same time"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Mrs. Cassells did not view us as young children in need of constant guidance, but instead thought we should have the ____ to make our own decisions.", "Opt_1": "habit", "Opt_2": "opportunity", "Opt_3": "background", "Opt_4": "fallacy", "Answer": "opportunity", "Opt_1_def": "something you do regularly", "Opt_2_def": "chance", "Opt_3_def": "family experiences; circumstances", "Opt_4_def": "mistake; false belief"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "US companies have too often viewed the social sector as a dumping ground for their spare cash, ____ equipment, and tired executives.", "Opt_1": "odd", "Opt_2": "ancient", "Opt_3": "obsolete", "Opt_4": "significant", "Answer": "obsolete", "Opt_1_def": "strange, unusual", "Opt_2_def": "very old", "Opt_3_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date", "Opt_4_def": "important, large"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "There is very little difference in the quality of learning received by ____ education students and regular students, according to a study.", "Opt_1": "distance", "Opt_2": "contrary", "Opt_3": "authority", "Opt_4": "struggle", "Answer": "distance", "Opt_1_def": "how far it is from one place to another", "Opt_2_def": "opposite", "Opt_3_def": "control (right to control)", "Opt_4_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government needs to ____ its tax proposals. They are less than clear to most people.", "Opt_1": "conclude", "Opt_2": "assemble", "Opt_3": "clarify", "Opt_4": "eliminate", "Answer": "clarify", "Opt_1_def": "to finish; to make a judgment", "Opt_2_def": "to get, put or bring together", "Opt_3_def": "to make something clear, explain", "Opt_4_def": "to dispose of"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Internet businesses will only be successful if they use the ____ of clear, easy, cheap, safe shopping.", "Opt_1": "phrase", "Opt_2": "formula", "Opt_3": "response", "Opt_4": "anomaly", "Answer": "formula", "Opt_1_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure.", "Opt_2_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "answer or reply; reaction", "Opt_4_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government needs to make a more ____ effort to ensure that all school-leavers have a job.", "Opt_1": "current", "Opt_2": "inherent", "Opt_3": "serious", "Opt_4": "anonymous", "Answer": "serious", "Opt_1_def": "happening now", "Opt_2_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_3_def": "severe, large", "Opt_4_def": "having no name or known author"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The ____ assumes a single step - that life originated on Earth - ahead of the more elaborate idea that life formed elsewhere and was subsequently transported to Earth.", "Opt_1": "confident", "Opt_2": "former", "Opt_3": "characteristic", "Opt_4": "absent", "Answer": "former", "Opt_1_def": "sure that something will happen", "Opt_2_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two", "Opt_3_def": "typical", "Opt_4_def": "being not there; missing"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "You are advised to undertake serious language study both before and during the course of the program but prior language study is not a ____ for selection.", "Opt_1": "code", "Opt_2": "region", "Opt_3": "hypothesis", "Opt_4": "criterion", "Answer": "criterion", "Opt_1_def": "a set of rules", "Opt_2_def": "part of a place", "Opt_3_def": "idea or prediction", "Opt_4_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The information that you receive in today's lesson will ____ you to complete your project on nuclear energy.", "Opt_1": "inspect", "Opt_2": "shrink", "Opt_3": "produce", "Opt_4": "enable", "Answer": "enable", "Opt_1_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_2_def": "to get smaller", "Opt_3_def": "to make or create", "Opt_4_def": "to make something or someone able to do something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "For the first time, satellite imagery has allowed scientists to observe how icebergs in a remote corner of Antarctica can disrupt an ____ marine ecosystem.", "Opt_1": "entire", "Opt_2": "subjective", "Opt_3": "prompt", "Opt_4": "serious", "Answer": "entire", "Opt_1_def": "whole, all", "Opt_2_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_3_def": "quick; on or before time", "Opt_4_def": "severe, large"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government survey produced a wide ____ of responses.", "Opt_1": "instance", "Opt_2": "range", "Opt_3": "quantity", "Opt_4": "route", "Answer": "range", "Opt_1_def": "example", "Opt_2_def": "extent, distance between two points", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The ____ is preferable for a field of inquiry that is still in its infancy, whereas the latter is suitable for fields that have a developed theory.", "Opt_1": "former", "Opt_2": "vital", "Opt_3": "similar", "Opt_4": "technical", "Answer": "former", "Opt_1_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two", "Opt_2_def": "very important", "Opt_3_def": "like, almost the same as", "Opt_4_def": "to do with machines or the way things work"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "These results are interesting, though not ____ to interpret.", "Opt_1": "adjacent", "Opt_2": "latter", "Opt_3": "economic", "Opt_4": "straightforward", "Answer": "straightforward", "Opt_1_def": "next to", "Opt_2_def": "the second of two things mentioned", "Opt_3_def": "financial; to do with money", "Opt_4_def": "easy"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "However, because The Dream intends to interest both lay and professional readers, it is unfortunate that she failed to append a glossary of ____ terms.", "Opt_1": "reasonable", "Opt_2": "certain", "Opt_3": "principal", "Opt_4": "significant", "Answer": "significant", "Opt_1_def": "acceptable, quite good", "Opt_2_def": "sure", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "important, large"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "I gave you ____ instructions not to open the box. Why did you disobey me?", "Opt_1": "poor", "Opt_2": "mental", "Opt_3": "perpetual", "Opt_4": "explicit", "Answer": "explicit", "Opt_1_def": "bad, unsatisfactory", "Opt_2_def": "of the brain or mind", "Opt_3_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing", "Opt_4_def": "clearly and openly expressed"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If your ____ is temporary and is impacting only attendance, make sure you follow up with your professors and contact the Dean of Students Office.", "Opt_1": "progress", "Opt_2": "detriment", "Opt_3": "condition", "Opt_4": "programme", "Answer": "condition", "Opt_1_def": "improvement or development", "Opt_2_def": "disadvantage", "Opt_3_def": "state", "Opt_4_def": "a course of lessons; a project"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This year you cannot choose which science course to do, but when you are in grade 9 you can ____ chemistry, physics or biology.", "Opt_1": "precede", "Opt_2": "exhaust", "Opt_3": "negotiate", "Opt_4": "select", "Answer": "select", "Opt_1_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to use up", "Opt_3_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)", "Opt_4_def": "to choose"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Through appointments and ____ the President was able to drain the Constitution of much of its meaning, with no public reaction.", "Opt_1": "decision", "Opt_2": "legislation", "Opt_3": "exponent", "Opt_4": "prestige", "Answer": "legislation", "Opt_1_def": "intention to do something, choice", "Opt_2_def": "governmental rule; law", "Opt_3_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion", "Opt_4_def": "fame and respect"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Although nuclear power does not pollute the air, many people are ____ it because they fear an accident or terrorist attack on a nuclear power station.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The partners realized that their small fund was not sufficient to support early stage start-ups in the ____ of the early 2000s.", "Opt_1": "fallacy", "Opt_2": "environment", "Opt_3": "reluctance", "Opt_4": "potential", "Answer": "environment", "Opt_1_def": "mistake; false belief", "Opt_2_def": "the world around us", "Opt_3_def": "unwillingness; hesitation", "Opt_4_def": "good possibility"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Water is a useful and ____ thing, but it is not a commodity until someone builds a fence around the water source.", "Opt_1": "radical", "Opt_2": "necessary", "Opt_3": "previous", "Opt_4": "exact", "Answer": "necessary", "Opt_1_def": "extreme, strong", "Opt_2_def": "needed; very important", "Opt_3_def": "the one before", "Opt_4_def": "precise, opposite of approximate"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It is often impossible to ____ the pronunciation of a word from its spelling alone.", "Opt_1": "imply", "Opt_2": "exist", "Opt_3": "combine", "Opt_4": "infer", "Answer": "infer", "Opt_1_def": "to mean; to give to understand", "Opt_2_def": "to be alive, to be in the world", "Opt_3_def": "to put or go together", "Opt_4_def": "to come to a conclusion about something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "He has only ____ control of basic verb grammar. He quite often chooses the wrong tense or forgets the -s ending.", "Opt_1": "credible", "Opt_2": "loose", "Opt_3": "verbal", "Opt_4": "substantial", "Answer": "loose", "Opt_1_def": "believable", "Opt_2_def": "not firm or finished", "Opt_3_def": "to do with words and language (especially the spoken language)", "Opt_4_def": "large"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It's a complex problem, and its solutions will ____ new technology, policy, awareness and education.", "Opt_1": "attain", "Opt_2": "require", "Opt_3": "prefer", "Opt_4": "conserve", "Answer": "require", "Opt_1_def": "to get, achieve", "Opt_2_def": "to need", "Opt_3_def": "to like better", "Opt_4_def": "to preserve; to not use"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government ____ was cleared of protesters by riot police and police horses.", "Opt_1": "period", "Opt_2": "income", "Opt_3": "district", "Opt_4": "means", "Answer": "district", "Opt_1_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)", "Opt_2_def": "money earned", "Opt_3_def": "region of a city", "Opt_4_def": "way"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The university follows a strict ____ of expelling any student caught plagiarizing.", "Opt_1": "individual", "Opt_2": "transition", "Opt_3": "policy", "Opt_4": "industry", "Answer": "policy", "Opt_1_def": "one person", "Opt_2_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_3_def": "formal rules", "Opt_4_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government received information but did not consider it reliable and ____ decided to ignore it.", "Opt_1": "hence", "Opt_2": "furthermore", "Opt_3": "absolutely", "Opt_4": "therefore", "Answer": "therefore", "Opt_1_def": "so, therefore", "Opt_2_def": "also, in addition", "Opt_3_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_4_def": "so, as a result"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The final event of the day was an ____ tour of the Single Sisters House, which is in the process of restoration.", "Opt_1": "optional", "Opt_2": "vague", "Opt_3": "overall", "Opt_4": "smooth", "Answer": "optional", "Opt_1_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want", "Opt_2_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_3_def": "general", "Opt_4_def": "easy, unproblematic"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The best remedy is to change the nutrient solution every week ____ of every two weeks.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Some scientists believe that genetically modified food can ____ people's health.", "Opt_1": "impress", "Opt_2": "trigger", "Opt_3": "harm", "Opt_4": "establish", "Answer": "harm", "Opt_1_def": "to create a favourable reaction", "Opt_2_def": "to (cause to) start", "Opt_3_def": "to damage or injure", "Opt_4_def": "to begin or set up"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Many large companies employ people to analyze a ____ such as the way people spend their money on holiday, etc.", "Opt_1": "attribute", "Opt_2": "trend", "Opt_3": "point", "Opt_4": "profession", "Answer": "trend", "Opt_1_def": "characteristic; property", "Opt_2_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "purpose; reason; value", "Opt_4_def": "job; occupation"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Musical ____ is a trait that some people are born with, but no-one succeeds as a musician without an enormous amount of practice.", "Opt_1": "lecture", "Opt_2": "ability", "Opt_3": "interpretation", "Opt_4": "interior", "Answer": "ability", "Opt_1_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well", "Opt_3_def": "explanation; assessment", "Opt_4_def": "inside"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government needs to change its policies ____ the punishment of young criminals.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "A regular driving license does not ____ the license holder to drive a bus or a truck.", "Opt_1": "entitle", "Opt_2": "exert", "Opt_3": "possess", "Opt_4": "provoke", "Answer": "entitle", "Opt_1_def": "to give the right to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to use", "Opt_3_def": "to have or own", "Opt_4_def": "to cause to happen"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "He was unable to ____ the methods and texts advocated by these educators with the powerful ideas of the critical pedagogues shaping his opinions.", "Opt_1": "denote", "Opt_2": "retain", "Opt_3": "align", "Opt_4": "focus", "Answer": "align", "Opt_1_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_2_def": "to keep", "Opt_3_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar", "Opt_4_def": "to direct attention (on an issue)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The ____ of weight change through pregnancy was similar across the 3 projects.", "Opt_1": "journey", "Opt_2": "objection", "Opt_3": "ignorance", "Opt_4": "pattern", "Answer": "pattern", "Opt_1_def": "a long trip to a different place", "Opt_2_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval", "Opt_3_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_4_def": "clear and consistent behaviour"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The school is looking for students who would like to do ____ work at the local old people's home.", "Opt_1": "voluntary", "Opt_2": "evident", "Opt_3": "trivial", "Opt_4": "considerable", "Answer": "voluntary", "Opt_1_def": "done freely; from personal choice", "Opt_2_def": "clear", "Opt_3_def": "not important", "Opt_4_def": "very big; very much"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "These two-word verbs present one other problem, ____ not appearing as separate entries in the dictionary.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "My ____ impression of him is that he is very intelligent and that his poor behaviour is because of boredom.", "Opt_1": "outstanding", "Opt_2": "ambitious", "Opt_3": "chief", "Opt_4": "preliminary", "Answer": "preliminary", "Opt_1_def": "excellent", "Opt_2_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "first; initial"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Many people say that he does not ____ the qualities to become president of this country.", "Opt_1": "prefer", "Opt_2": "possess", "Opt_3": "adopt", "Opt_4": "protest", "Answer": "possess", "Opt_1_def": "to like better", "Opt_2_def": "to have or own", "Opt_3_def": "to take in; to start", "Opt_4_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If your parents want to take you out of school during term time, they must have a ____ reason.", "Opt_1": "uniform", "Opt_2": "legitimate", "Opt_3": "certain", "Opt_4": "immediate", "Answer": "legitimate", "Opt_1_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_2_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_3_def": "sure", "Opt_4_def": "first (without delay)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Her mother is a ____ visitor to the school. In fact she comes two or three times a week!", "Opt_1": "frequent", "Opt_2": "discrete", "Opt_3": "consistent", "Opt_4": "typical", "Answer": "frequent", "Opt_1_def": "often", "Opt_2_def": "separate", "Opt_3_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_4_def": "usual"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Although we did train the faculty in the revised teaching methods, in hindsight our training was not ____ enough to prepare them for the new course.", "Opt_1": "drastic", "Opt_2": "thorough", "Opt_3": "slight", "Opt_4": "identical", "Answer": "thorough", "Opt_1_def": "severe; great", "Opt_2_def": "complete and careful", "Opt_3_def": "small", "Opt_4_def": "exactly the same"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The quality of your ideas and organization is much more important than the ____ of words you write.", "Opt_1": "quantity", "Opt_2": "layer", "Opt_3": "demand", "Opt_4": "prospect", "Answer": "quantity", "Opt_1_def": "amount", "Opt_2_def": "level", "Opt_3_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_4_def": "chance, likelihood"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "He may ____ to any political party he pleases, or he may ____ to none.", "Opt_1": "tend", "Opt_2": "absorb", "Opt_3": "accelerate", "Opt_4": "belong", "Answer": "belong", "Opt_1_def": "to often behave in a certain way", "Opt_2_def": "to take in; to take up", "Opt_3_def": "to get or make faster", "Opt_4_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Nine tenths of an iceberg is under water and hence ____ to ships.", "Opt_1": "global", "Opt_2": "comprehensive", "Opt_3": "optional", "Opt_4": "invisible", "Answer": "invisible", "Opt_1_def": "world", "Opt_2_def": "full, complete", "Opt_3_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want", "Opt_4_def": "cannot be seen"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "As each hydrogen only has one electron to share in the formation of chemical bonds, it is impossible to ____ more than two hydrogen atoms to each other.", "Opt_1": "install", "Opt_2": "connect", "Opt_3": "appear", "Opt_4": "label", "Answer": "connect", "Opt_1_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or put together", "Opt_3_def": "to come, be seen", "Opt_4_def": "to give a name to someone or something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Photographs ____ if they are left out in bright sunlight.", "Opt_1": "fade", "Opt_2": "intervene", "Opt_3": "import", "Opt_4": "combine", "Answer": "fade", "Opt_1_def": "to disappear slowly", "Opt_2_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)", "Opt_3_def": "to bring in (to a country)", "Opt_4_def": "to put or go together"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "I suspect that difficulties at home ____ her recent poor performance in school.", "Opt_1": "underlie", "Opt_2": "imply", "Opt_3": "participate", "Opt_4": "belong", "Answer": "underlie", "Opt_1_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something", "Opt_2_def": "to mean; to give to understand", "Opt_3_def": "to take part", "Opt_4_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "In the USA and Germany the people ____ a new government every four years; in the UK it is every five years.", "Opt_1": "preserve", "Opt_2": "elect", "Opt_3": "exploit", "Opt_4": "dispose", "Answer": "elect", "Opt_1_def": "forward,\" said Michele Gougeon.", "Opt_2_def": "to choose by voting", "Opt_3_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)", "Opt_4_def": "to get rid of"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Thousands of farm families are being forced off the land, and we are being told that it is an ____ consequence of technological progress.", "Opt_1": "former", "Opt_2": "sufficient", "Opt_3": "rapid", "Opt_4": "inevitable", "Answer": "inevitable", "Opt_1_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two", "Opt_2_def": "enough", "Opt_3_def": "quick", "Opt_4_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Studies show that parents ____ influence the development of their child in all areas.", "Opt_1": "approximately", "Opt_2": "greatly", "Opt_3": "virtually", "Opt_4": "absolutely", "Answer": "greatly", "Opt_1_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_2_def": "very much", "Opt_3_def": "almost", "Opt_4_def": "completely; 100%"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Did you ____ the book that was taken from your bag?", "Opt_1": "exaggerate", "Opt_2": "interrupt", "Opt_3": "conduct", "Opt_4": "recover", "Answer": "recover", "Opt_1_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_2_def": "to stop something from happening", "Opt_3_def": "to do or perform; to behave", "Opt_4_def": "to get back"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "These documents have an ____ stamp, but I'm not convinced they are authentic.", "Opt_1": "drastic", "Opt_2": "conscious", "Opt_3": "novel", "Opt_4": "official", "Answer": "official", "Opt_1_def": "severe; great", "Opt_2_def": "aware, knowing", "Opt_3_def": "new", "Opt_4_def": "approved by an authority"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "But it is not a ____ for comprehensive food safety programs throughout the food distribution system.", "Opt_1": "substitute", "Opt_2": "decision", "Opt_3": "feature", "Opt_4": "fragment", "Answer": "substitute", "Opt_1_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another", "Opt_2_def": "intention to do something, choice", "Opt_3_def": "part, aspect", "Opt_4_def": "part of something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "I usually keep a ____ of spare pencils in my desk, so that I can lend one to any student who comes without.", "Opt_1": "motive", "Opt_2": "credit", "Opt_3": "supply", "Opt_4": "delay", "Answer": "supply", "Opt_1_def": "reason", "Opt_2_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise", "Opt_3_def": "provision, store", "Opt_4_def": "lateness"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Due to its association with the churches and schools, the Samoan language enjoyed high ____ in Tokelau for a long time.", "Opt_1": "counsel", "Opt_2": "prestige", "Opt_3": "gain", "Opt_4": "insight", "Answer": "prestige", "Opt_1_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_2_def": "fame and respect", "Opt_3_def": "to get; to increase in ..", "Opt_4_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It explores the lives of a group of adolescent boys in the ____ between the departure of the Nazis and the arrival of the Communists.", "Opt_1": "fragment", "Opt_2": "tradition", "Opt_3": "trace", "Opt_4": "interval", "Answer": "interval", "Opt_1_def": "part of something", "Opt_2_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things", "Opt_3_def": "sign; indication; evidence", "Opt_4_def": "a period of time"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "With regret, we have had to cancel the upcoming program on \"The Nervous System\" ____ to an unavoidable change in schedules.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "On the ship, every ____ room and corner was turned into dormitory space; cots were set up to accommodate the overflow.", "Opt_1": "regular", "Opt_2": "ancient", "Opt_3": "unique", "Opt_4": "spare", "Answer": "spare", "Opt_1_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal", "Opt_2_def": "very old", "Opt_3_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind", "Opt_4_def": "not needed"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Even more extraordinary, every child ____ one was more than willing to state his or her name to the stranger.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "You ____ us all an apology for using this forum for your personal beliefs when it is a forum for scientific reasoning.", "Opt_1": "ignore", "Opt_2": "replace", "Opt_3": "protest", "Opt_4": "owe", "Answer": "owe", "Opt_1_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)", "Opt_2_def": "to put in or take the place of ..", "Opt_3_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_4_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Headaches and sleeplessness are ____ of someone suffering from culture shock.", "Opt_1": "characteristic", "Opt_2": "subjective", "Opt_3": "temporary", "Opt_4": "random", "Answer": "characteristic", "Opt_1_def": "typical", "Opt_2_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_3_def": "for a short or limited time", "Opt_4_def": "by chance; without any sequence"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The school is set to ____ the parents' request to extend their child's vacation by two days.", "Opt_1": "reject", "Opt_2": "repeat", "Opt_3": "insert", "Opt_4": "diverge", "Answer": "reject", "Opt_1_def": "to refuse", "Opt_2_def": "to do or say again", "Opt_3_def": "to put in", "Opt_4_def": "to move apart; to be different from"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "In the face of the success of industrialization, individuals must ____ and form institutions that would be in line with this task.", "Opt_1": "compel", "Opt_2": "illuminate", "Opt_3": "regard", "Opt_4": "unite", "Answer": "unite", "Opt_1_def": "to force or make happen", "Opt_2_def": "to show clearly; to light up", "Opt_3_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "to bring or get together"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "First, you will need to ____ background information about all of the supporting questions.", "Opt_1": "deteriorate", "Opt_2": "denote", "Opt_3": "gather", "Opt_4": "attract", "Answer": "gather", "Opt_1_def": "to get worse", "Opt_2_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_3_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_4_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Excellent writing with just one or two ____ mistakes!", "Opt_1": "artificial", "Opt_2": "widespread", "Opt_3": "rapid", "Opt_4": "trivial", "Answer": "trivial", "Opt_1_def": "not real or natural", "Opt_2_def": "common", "Opt_3_def": "quick", "Opt_4_def": "not important"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Many people believe that the invasion of Iraq was a ____ mistake.", "Opt_1": "ambitious", "Opt_2": "global", "Opt_3": "related", "Opt_4": "fundamental", "Answer": "fundamental", "Opt_1_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging", "Opt_2_def": "world", "Opt_3_def": "connected; having something to do with each other", "Opt_4_def": "very important"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "My regular mathematics teacher is sick so we have had a ____ for the last 2 weeks.", "Opt_1": "influence", "Opt_2": "anomaly", "Opt_3": "atmosphere", "Opt_4": "substitute", "Answer": "substitute", "Opt_1_def": "effect", "Opt_2_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data", "Opt_3_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_4_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The grade will be amended but the former grade will remain on the ____ with an appropriate notation.", "Opt_1": "objective", "Opt_2": "record", "Opt_3": "fee", "Opt_4": "figure", "Answer": "record", "Opt_1_def": "aim or goal", "Opt_2_def": "evidence; documentation", "Opt_3_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)", "Opt_4_def": "number"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Many buildings ____ during earthquakes and kill the people inside.", "Opt_1": "deliver", "Opt_2": "collapse", "Opt_3": "illustrate", "Opt_4": "realize", "Answer": "collapse", "Opt_1_def": "to provide (often by bringing to people)", "Opt_2_def": "to fall down completely and heavily; to fail", "Opt_3_def": "to show; to make clear", "Opt_4_def": "to come to know or understand"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Erving Goffman pointed out that when one person speaks on ____ of another, the former steals the latter's conversational role.", "Opt_1": "tradition", "Opt_2": "member", "Opt_3": "account", "Opt_4": "behalf", "Answer": "behalf", "Opt_1_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things", "Opt_2_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization", "Opt_3_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_4_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "China won't take strong action ____ Iran's nuclear program because China just made a deal to buy lots of Iranian oil.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "This statement does not ____ that the university will be responsible for any other expenses of the above-name student.", "Opt_1": "disperse", "Opt_2": "accept", "Opt_3": "import", "Opt_4": "imply", "Answer": "imply", "Opt_1_def": "to spread out; to move apart", "Opt_2_def": "to agree (to have)", "Opt_3_def": "to bring in (to a country)", "Opt_4_def": "to mean; to give to understand"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The police would like to ____ everyone who was in the area when the accident happened.", "Opt_1": "suggest", "Opt_2": "undergo", "Opt_3": "contact", "Opt_4": "commit", "Answer": "contact", "Opt_1_def": "to say an idea; to recommend", "Opt_2_def": "to receive or experience", "Opt_3_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)", "Opt_4_def": "to do (often an offense)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "You should follow the ____ that the doctor has given you.", "Opt_1": "status", "Opt_2": "magnitude", "Opt_3": "margin", "Opt_4": "directions", "Answer": "directions", "Opt_1_def": "position, standing", "Opt_2_def": "size; amount", "Opt_3_def": "amount; distance", "Opt_4_def": "instructions"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "What is your ____ of his recent odd behaviour?", "Opt_1": "goal", "Opt_2": "situation", "Opt_3": "decision", "Opt_4": "interpretation", "Answer": "interpretation", "Opt_1_def": "aim or intention", "Opt_2_def": "circumstances", "Opt_3_def": "intention to do something, choice", "Opt_4_def": "explanation; assessment"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If children of seven years and older will be included in the study, an ____ agreement is necessary.", "Opt_1": "assent", "Opt_2": "factor", "Opt_3": "route", "Opt_4": "evidence", "Answer": "assent", "Opt_1_def": "agreement", "Opt_2_def": "an aspect to be considered", "Opt_3_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing", "Opt_4_def": "proof, signs"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "In my ____ the government should undertake more to prevent young people drinking and driving.", "Opt_1": "opinion", "Opt_2": "objection", "Opt_3": "notion", "Opt_4": "item", "Answer": "opinion", "Opt_1_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval", "Opt_3_def": "idea; concept", "Opt_4_def": "thing, element"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The most famous ____ organization is the United Nations.", "Opt_1": "contemporary", "Opt_2": "complete", "Opt_3": "global", "Opt_4": "stable", "Answer": "global", "Opt_1_def": "of this time, happening now", "Opt_2_def": "full or finished", "Opt_3_def": "world", "Opt_4_def": "not changing; not easy to change"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Here you can recommend areas for investment of resources to ____ the University in its health sciences, education, research, service and outreach missions.", "Opt_1": "protest", "Opt_2": "advance", "Opt_3": "trust", "Opt_4": "launch", "Answer": "advance", "Opt_1_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_2_def": "to go or move forward; to get better", "Opt_3_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised", "Opt_4_def": "to begin"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government needs to ____ its reluctance to advising parents how to bring up their children.", "Opt_1": "regret", "Opt_2": "investigate", "Opt_3": "overcome", "Opt_4": "accelerate", "Answer": "overcome", "Opt_1_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)", "Opt_2_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened", "Opt_3_def": "to conquer, defeat", "Opt_4_def": "to get or make faster"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The research addresses teacher attitudes toward the ____ of homework.", "Opt_1": "assignment", "Opt_2": "description", "Opt_3": "circumstances", "Opt_4": "site", "Answer": "assignment", "Opt_1_def": "a task; the giving of a task", "Opt_2_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like", "Opt_3_def": "situation", "Opt_4_def": "place"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It was a very ____ test. Everyone got 100%.", "Opt_1": "straightforward", "Opt_2": "immense", "Opt_3": "annual", "Opt_4": "permanent", "Answer": "straightforward", "Opt_1_def": "easy", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "yearly", "Opt_4_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "He told the members that he quickly called for a car and telephoned the White House to set up an ____ meeting in order to share what he had just learned.", "Opt_1": "drastic", "Opt_2": "urgent", "Opt_3": "odd", "Opt_4": "passive", "Answer": "urgent", "Opt_1_def": "severe; great", "Opt_2_def": "very important, must be done immediately", "Opt_3_def": "strange, unusual", "Opt_4_def": "not active; unresponsive"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "By signing the pledge, students make a personal commitment to conserve energy and help ____ to Yale's goal of reducing greenhouse gases by 10 percent.", "Opt_1": "require", "Opt_2": "contribute", "Opt_3": "comply", "Opt_4": "provide", "Answer": "contribute", "Opt_1_def": "to need", "Opt_2_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_3_def": "to do what someone asks or orders", "Opt_4_def": "to give"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Experts believe that the problem will ____ until the government takes it more seriously.", "Opt_1": "fulfill", "Opt_2": "classify", "Opt_3": "involve", "Opt_4": "recur", "Answer": "recur", "Opt_1_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_2_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_3_def": "to include or mean", "Opt_4_def": "to happen again"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Advertising often tries to promote the idea that the customer deserves to buy the product because they are ____ it!", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "People with mental disabilities are so marginalized that even human rights activists have failed to ____ for them.", "Opt_1": "promote", "Opt_2": "advocate", "Opt_3": "obtain", "Opt_4": "harm", "Answer": "advocate", "Opt_1_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job", "Opt_2_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to get", "Opt_4_def": "to damage or injure"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "With her ____ it is not surprising that she has had problems in her new school.", "Opt_1": "consequence", "Opt_2": "factor", "Opt_3": "background", "Opt_4": "coincidence", "Answer": "background", "Opt_1_def": "result", "Opt_2_def": "an aspect to be considered", "Opt_3_def": "family experiences; circumstances", "Opt_4_def": "an uncommon happening of two things"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The school does a lot to ____ new families, with information meetings, translation services, etc.", "Opt_1": "dictate", "Opt_2": "integrate", "Opt_3": "oppose", "Opt_4": "derive", "Answer": "integrate", "Opt_1_def": "to tell someone what to do", "Opt_2_def": "to fit into a new situation", "Opt_3_def": "to be against or fight against something", "Opt_4_def": "to come from or get from"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If you decide to apply, you will need to ____ a full application including: cover sheet, goals and plan letter, and project statement.", "Opt_1": "estimate", "Opt_2": "compile", "Opt_3": "obey", "Opt_4": "implement", "Answer": "compile", "Opt_1_def": "to make an intelligent guess", "Opt_2_def": "to put together (often in a list", "Opt_3_def": "to do as commanded or expected", "Opt_4_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "This is NOT a reliable ____ and you should simply ignore it.", "Opt_1": "category", "Opt_2": "argument", "Opt_3": "statistic", "Opt_4": "access", "Answer": "statistic", "Opt_1_def": "group of similar items", "Opt_2_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)", "Opt_3_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_4_def": "the right to enter or use"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It is important for teachers to ____ a positive learning atmosphere in the classroom.", "Opt_1": "prevent", "Opt_2": "create", "Opt_3": "denote", "Opt_4": "share", "Answer": "create", "Opt_1_def": "to stop from doing or happening", "Opt_2_def": "to make; to use your imagination to make something new", "Opt_3_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_4_def": "to exchange; to give"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The Supreme Court held that the free exercise of religion did not entitle an Orthodox Jew to wear a yarmulke when he was on ____ as an officer of law.", "Opt_1": "detail", "Opt_2": "series", "Opt_3": "compensation", "Opt_4": "duty", "Answer": "duty", "Opt_1_def": "a small piece of information", "Opt_2_def": "a number of things, one after the other", "Opt_3_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_4_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "First, you will need to ____ background information about all of the supporting questions.", "Opt_1": "gather", "Opt_2": "conceal", "Opt_3": "receive", "Opt_4": "devise", "Answer": "gather", "Opt_1_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_2_def": "to hide", "Opt_3_def": "to get", "Opt_4_def": "to create or think up"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Each year the school has to ____ many of its textbooks from the USA or England-Germany needs to ____ more qualified computer technicians. It has failed to train enough of its own.", "Opt_1": "propose", "Opt_2": "import", "Opt_3": "contemplate", "Opt_4": "refuse", "Answer": "import", "Opt_1_def": "to suggest", "Opt_2_def": "to bring in (to a country)", "Opt_3_def": "to think about; to consider", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Most people were ____ the plan to boycott the Olympics. Nevertheless, the government decided to do so.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The teacher thought about the best opportunity to ____ that she was leaving to have a baby.", "Opt_1": "migrate", "Opt_2": "announce", "Opt_3": "raise", "Opt_4": "suspect", "Answer": "announce", "Opt_1_def": "to go to another place", "Opt_2_def": "to state (often in an official way)", "Opt_3_def": "to lift; to make higher", "Opt_4_def": "to believe"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "If we accept your request to ____ the information, we will make reasonable efforts to inform others, including people you have authorized, of the ____ment.", "Opt_1": "contact", "Opt_2": "multiply", "Opt_3": "realize", "Opt_4": "amend", "Answer": "amend", "Opt_1_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)", "Opt_2_def": "to increase greatly", "Opt_3_def": "to come to know or understand", "Opt_4_def": "to change (usually to improve something)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Smoking will probably ____ in popularity in most western countries now that smoking bans are in force.", "Opt_1": "stipulate", "Opt_2": "decline", "Opt_3": "block", "Opt_4": "suspect", "Answer": "decline", "Opt_1_def": "to require", "Opt_2_def": "to go down or get worse", "Opt_3_def": "to not allow; to stop or prevent", "Opt_4_def": "to believe"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The White House has been engaged in an image war, trying to ____ the motives and strategies of the real war on Iraq.", "Opt_1": "possess", "Opt_2": "reward", "Opt_3": "conceal", "Opt_4": "approve", "Answer": "conceal", "Opt_1_def": "to have or own", "Opt_2_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "to hide", "Opt_4_def": "to agree to"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The administration is planning to ____ the school day until 4pm.", "Opt_1": "notice", "Opt_2": "exist", "Opt_3": "extend", "Opt_4": "dedicate", "Answer": "extend", "Opt_1_def": "to see or realize", "Opt_2_def": "to be alive, to be in the world", "Opt_3_def": "to make longer in time or space", "Opt_4_def": "to devote (time and attention)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Rubin did not suffer ____ but learned to use anger and pride to fight for what was right.", "Opt_1": "resident", "Opt_2": "defeat", "Opt_3": "element", "Opt_4": "volume", "Answer": "defeat", "Opt_1_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_2_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)", "Opt_3_def": "aspect, part", "Opt_4_def": "amount"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Counselors will begin on-going sessions with a student only after having obtained signed assent of the student and signed ____ of the parent.", "Opt_1": "migrate", "Opt_2": "detect", "Opt_3": "deduce", "Opt_4": "consent", "Answer": "consent", "Opt_1_def": "to go to another place", "Opt_2_def": "to see, find or notice", "Opt_3_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to agree"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "An athlete may begin training at age 6 but cannot ____ until age 8.", "Opt_1": "deteriorate", "Opt_2": "maintain", "Opt_3": "utilize", "Opt_4": "compete", "Answer": "compete", "Opt_1_def": "to get worse", "Opt_2_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_3_def": "to use", "Opt_4_def": "to try and win against someone or something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The committee was asked to ____ a report listing the reasons in favour of invading Iraq.", "Opt_1": "purchase", "Opt_2": "attempt", "Opt_3": "compile", "Opt_4": "permit", "Answer": "compile", "Opt_1_def": "to buy", "Opt_2_def": "to try", "Opt_3_def": "to put together (often in a list", "Opt_4_def": "to allow"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "He is an American citizen which obviously puts him in a different ____ from the kinds of individuals that the president has suggested might be suitable.", "Opt_1": "drawback", "Opt_2": "revolution", "Opt_3": "directions", "Opt_4": "category", "Answer": "category", "Opt_1_def": "disadvantage, problem", "Opt_2_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_3_def": "instructions", "Opt_4_def": "group of similar items"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "You need to know a little more about the ____ before you criticize the government's decision.", "Opt_1": "limit", "Opt_2": "criterion", "Opt_3": "background", "Opt_4": "forecast", "Answer": "background", "Opt_1_def": "extent, boundary", "Opt_2_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something", "Opt_3_def": "family experiences; circumstances", "Opt_4_def": "prediction"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Errors in grammar and vocabulary may, but do not always, ____ with comprehensibility.", "Opt_1": "interfere", "Opt_2": "occupy", "Opt_3": "proceed", "Opt_4": "postpone", "Answer": "interfere", "Opt_1_def": "to prevent; to harm", "Opt_2_def": "to up space or time", "Opt_3_def": "to go forward (and do ..)", "Opt_4_def": "to put back in time"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The teacher had to ____ the boy from the rest of the class. His bad behaviour was disrupting their learning.", "Opt_1": "convert", "Opt_2": "compile", "Opt_3": "isolate", "Opt_4": "halt", "Answer": "isolate", "Opt_1_def": "to change from one thing to another", "Opt_2_def": "to put together (often in a list", "Opt_3_def": "to separate something or someone from others", "Opt_4_def": "to stop"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "These ever-changing factors necessitate the creation of a flexible ____ that can respond and adapt to the needs of our library users.", "Opt_1": "insight", "Opt_2": "symbol", "Opt_3": "intention", "Opt_4": "policy", "Answer": "policy", "Opt_1_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_2_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea", "Opt_3_def": "plan, aim", "Opt_4_def": "formal rules"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The producer of these webpages has long been an ____ of the value of computers in language teaching.", "Opt_1": "decade", "Opt_2": "vary", "Opt_3": "goal", "Opt_4": "exponent", "Answer": "exponent", "Opt_1_def": "a period of ten years", "Opt_2_def": "to change or be different", "Opt_3_def": "aim or intention", "Opt_4_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government is thinking of passing a law that will require all house owners to ____ their oil heating system for one that runs on gas.", "Opt_1": "exchange", "Opt_2": "correspond", "Opt_3": "accuse", "Opt_4": "precede", "Answer": "exchange", "Opt_1_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing", "Opt_2_def": "to be related to", "Opt_3_def": "to blame", "Opt_4_def": "to go or be before someone or something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If a person tends to be ____ in relationships or at work, it is likely that her investment decisions will also be ____.", "Opt_1": "strict", "Opt_2": "inevitable", "Opt_3": "dynamic", "Opt_4": "cautious", "Answer": "cautious", "Opt_1_def": "hard, not changeable", "Opt_2_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious", "Opt_3_def": "changing; growing; energetic", "Opt_4_def": "careful"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The father stated he was from the neighbourhood of Bandon, where he had been unable to ____ any employment.", "Opt_1": "conserve", "Opt_2": "procure", "Opt_3": "found", "Opt_4": "identify", "Answer": "procure", "Opt_1_def": "to preserve; to not use", "Opt_2_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_3_def": "to begin (often an organization)", "Opt_4_def": "to know or say who or what something is"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "A student seeking a career in this ____ of study will have abundant opportunities to develop personal and professional skills.", "Opt_1": "structure", "Opt_2": "prejudice", "Opt_3": "exercise", "Opt_4": "field", "Answer": "field", "Opt_1_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_2_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background", "Opt_3_def": "a piece of work, activity", "Opt_4_def": "area of interest or study"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The school sports ____ is not a public facility. Only students, parents or teachers are allowed to use it.", "Opt_1": "obligation", "Opt_2": "comparison", "Opt_3": "interior", "Opt_4": "field", "Answer": "field", "Opt_1_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_2_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different", "Opt_3_def": "inside", "Opt_4_def": "area of interest or study"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The police were unable to ____ the demonstrators from the town square.", "Opt_1": "forego", "Opt_2": "praise", "Opt_3": "expel", "Opt_4": "blame", "Answer": "expel", "Opt_1_def": "to do without; to give up", "Opt_2_def": "to express approval about something someone has done", "Opt_3_def": "to drive or push out", "Opt_4_def": "to accuse"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "My father's company is going to facilitate our move to Germany by employing an ____ to help us find a house here.", "Opt_1": "agent", "Opt_2": "phenomenon", "Opt_3": "crisis", "Opt_4": "district", "Answer": "agent", "Opt_1_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_2_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)", "Opt_3_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe", "Opt_4_def": "region of a city"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government generally did not take steps to ____ or punish the most serious cases of abuse.", "Opt_1": "investigate", "Opt_2": "accuse", "Opt_3": "exhaust", "Opt_4": "prevail", "Answer": "investigate", "Opt_1_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened", "Opt_2_def": "to blame", "Opt_3_def": "to use up", "Opt_4_def": "to succeed; to overcome"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "When the earth is closest to the sun, the ____ between the earth and sun is 147000000k.", "Opt_1": "mixture", "Opt_2": "distance", "Opt_3": "interior", "Opt_4": "rise", "Answer": "distance", "Opt_1_def": "combination", "Opt_2_def": "how far it is from one place to another", "Opt_3_def": "inside", "Opt_4_def": "to go up"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The teachers ____ that the school administration is secretly planning to increase working hours.", "Opt_1": "predict", "Opt_2": "intervene", "Opt_3": "allege", "Opt_4": "restrict", "Answer": "allege", "Opt_1_def": "to say what will happen in the future", "Opt_2_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)", "Opt_3_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_4_def": "to limit"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government has invested little money in the health system. The quality of hospital care is sure to ____ more and more.", "Opt_1": "determine", "Opt_2": "found", "Opt_3": "deteriorate", "Opt_4": "manipulate", "Answer": "deteriorate", "Opt_1_def": "to find out; to establish or identify; state", "Opt_2_def": "to begin (often an organization)", "Opt_3_def": "to get worse", "Opt_4_def": "to (use and) change"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This could substantially change the nature of the Internet we have come to know, to the ____ of both the consumers and the providers of information.", "Opt_1": "justice", "Opt_2": "detriment", "Opt_3": "finance", "Opt_4": "majority", "Answer": "detriment", "Opt_1_def": "fairness in law", "Opt_2_def": "disadvantage", "Opt_3_def": "to do with money and payment", "Opt_4_def": "more than 50%"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "She is having serious problems in her mathematics class. She cannot even ____ two numbers using a calculator.", "Opt_1": "fade", "Opt_2": "donate", "Opt_3": "multiply", "Opt_4": "protect", "Answer": "multiply", "Opt_1_def": "to disappear slowly", "Opt_2_def": "to give (usually money)", "Opt_3_def": "to increase greatly", "Opt_4_def": "to keep something out of danger"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Some types of ____ are dirty, dangerous or not well-paid. It is often poor immigrants to a country who take such jobs.", "Opt_1": "atmosphere", "Opt_2": "exponent", "Opt_3": "labour", "Opt_4": "means", "Answer": "labour", "Opt_1_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_2_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion", "Opt_3_def": "work", "Opt_4_def": "way"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The school wanted to set up a new computer lab, but the ____ would have been too high.", "Opt_1": "bulk", "Opt_2": "propensity", "Opt_3": "agent", "Opt_4": "expense", "Answer": "expense", "Opt_1_def": "majority; largest part", "Opt_2_def": "tendency; desire", "Opt_3_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_4_def": "cost"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government is set to suffer a heavy ____ in the vote to approve its new tax policy.", "Opt_1": "device", "Opt_2": "society", "Opt_3": "topic", "Opt_4": "defeat", "Answer": "defeat", "Opt_1_def": "object; method", "Opt_2_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country", "Opt_3_def": "area of interest or discussion", "Opt_4_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It was an ____ conservative institution, and did not enlarge its business to any extent.", "Opt_1": "recently", "Opt_2": "extremely", "Opt_3": "dramatically", "Opt_4": "thereby", "Answer": "extremely", "Opt_1_def": "in the near past", "Opt_2_def": "very", "Opt_3_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_4_def": "by doing this"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "This is not a defect in the ____ of economic development as much as it is a problem with the fiscal structure of Alaska.", "Opt_1": "gain", "Opt_2": "domain", "Opt_3": "notion", "Opt_4": "manner", "Answer": "notion", "Opt_1_def": "to get; to increase in ..", "Opt_2_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_3_def": "idea; concept", "Opt_4_def": "way of doing something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The CLAS Institute identifies, evaluates, and promotes ____ and appropriate early intervention and preschool practices that are sensitive to diverse cultural and linguistic backgrounds.", "Opt_1": "effective", "Opt_2": "inherent", "Opt_3": "firm", "Opt_4": "proper", "Answer": "effective", "Opt_1_def": "good, working well", "Opt_2_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_3_def": "strong, cannot be changed", "Opt_4_def": "correct, appropriate"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "This finding may ____ why increasing numbers of people in the United States lack the natural ability to regulate food intake and body weight.", "Opt_1": "explain", "Opt_2": "exhaust", "Opt_3": "contact", "Opt_4": "increase", "Answer": "explain", "Opt_1_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to use up", "Opt_3_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)", "Opt_4_def": "to get bigger"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Every ____ effort will be made to accommodate properly documented special needs.", "Opt_1": "reasonable", "Opt_2": "feasible", "Opt_3": "characteristic", "Opt_4": "various", "Answer": "reasonable", "Opt_1_def": "acceptable, quite good", "Opt_2_def": "possible", "Opt_3_def": "typical", "Opt_4_def": "several, of different kinds"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The precise answer is not at all straightforward, unless the uncertainty itself is related in a particular way to the ____ of time.", "Opt_1": "remedy", "Opt_2": "fault", "Opt_3": "passage", "Opt_4": "priority", "Answer": "passage", "Opt_1_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_2_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem", "Opt_3_def": "a piece of written or spoken text", "Opt_4_def": "first and most important task"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "To test for a ____ sentence, see if it can stand alone and still mean something.", "Opt_1": "fragment", "Opt_2": "reluctance", "Opt_3": "region", "Opt_4": "formula", "Answer": "fragment", "Opt_1_def": "part of something", "Opt_2_def": "unwillingness; hesitation", "Opt_3_def": "part of a place", "Opt_4_def": "a method of doing something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Rexhepi said the incident damaged the atmosphere for the upcoming talks on ____ matters between Kosovar and Serbian officials.", "Opt_1": "rare", "Opt_2": "characteristic", "Opt_3": "practical", "Opt_4": "abstract", "Answer": "practical", "Opt_1_def": "unusual", "Opt_2_def": "typical", "Opt_3_def": "useful; possible", "Opt_4_def": "not specific or concrete"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Another well-known effect of marijuana is its ____ to increase appetite.", "Opt_1": "passage", "Opt_2": "ability", "Opt_3": "strategy", "Opt_4": "gain", "Answer": "ability", "Opt_1_def": "a piece of written or spoken text", "Opt_2_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well", "Opt_3_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_4_def": "to get; to increase in .."}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Nature was an ____ part of ancient Chinese, Japanese, and Indian literature.", "Opt_1": "massive", "Opt_2": "valid", "Opt_3": "stable", "Opt_4": "intrinsic", "Answer": "intrinsic", "Opt_1_def": "very large", "Opt_2_def": "correct", "Opt_3_def": "not changing; not easy to change", "Opt_4_def": "belonging to; inherent in"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The results represented an unusual ____ of old and modern practices.", "Opt_1": "responsibility", "Opt_2": "liberty", "Opt_3": "mixture", "Opt_4": "apparatus", "Answer": "mixture", "Opt_1_def": "job, duty to do something", "Opt_2_def": "freedom", "Opt_3_def": "combination", "Opt_4_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The project itself may grow out of course work, but it must ____ achievement that is over and above regular course activities.", "Opt_1": "postpone", "Opt_2": "yield", "Opt_3": "comprise", "Opt_4": "insist", "Answer": "comprise", "Opt_1_def": "to put back in time", "Opt_2_def": "to produce", "Opt_3_def": "to be made up of; to include", "Opt_4_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government has the ____ of protecting its citizens from terrorist attack, but many people do not agree with the way it is trying to do this.", "Opt_1": "research", "Opt_2": "duty", "Opt_3": "opportunity", "Opt_4": "custom", "Answer": "duty", "Opt_1_def": "study; the finding of information", "Opt_2_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do", "Opt_3_def": "chance", "Opt_4_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The proponents of disability rights and ____ professionals have come to realize that the concept of accessible ____ has to be rethought.", "Opt_1": "circumstances", "Opt_2": "design", "Opt_3": "goal", "Opt_4": "atmosphere", "Answer": "design", "Opt_1_def": "situation", "Opt_2_def": "planning (drawing)", "Opt_3_def": "aim or intention", "Opt_4_def": "mood among people or groups"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Almost everyone believes that terrorism should be fought, but there is little agreement about the ____ in which it should be done.", "Opt_1": "manner", "Opt_2": "minimum", "Opt_3": "prestige", "Opt_4": "decade", "Answer": "manner", "Opt_1_def": "way of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_3_def": "fame and respect", "Opt_4_def": "a period of ten years"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "A student who fails to cite sources in a ____ attempt to conceal the source of the work should be considered to be cheating.", "Opt_1": "poor", "Opt_2": "deliberate", "Opt_3": "final", "Opt_4": "ambiguous", "Answer": "deliberate", "Opt_1_def": "bad, unsatisfactory", "Opt_2_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_3_def": "last", "Opt_4_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Sometimes it is necessary to exert force in ____ to achieve peace in a troubled region.", "Opt_1": "order", "Opt_2": "standard", "Opt_3": "opinion", "Opt_4": "condition", "Answer": "order", "Opt_1_def": "sequence, place", "Opt_2_def": "quality", "Opt_3_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "state"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The US, which by this time was paying most of France's war expenses, was unable to ____ the French to fight on.", "Opt_1": "consent", "Opt_2": "declare", "Opt_3": "persuade", "Opt_4": "protest", "Answer": "persuade", "Opt_1_def": "to agree", "Opt_2_def": "to state", "Opt_3_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something", "Opt_4_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "You ____ yourself to unnecessary danger if you drive a car without wearing a seat belt.", "Opt_1": "expose", "Opt_2": "commit", "Opt_3": "disrupt", "Opt_4": "fail", "Answer": "expose", "Opt_1_def": "to uncover, reveal", "Opt_2_def": "to do (often an offense)", "Opt_3_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "We engage outside ____ to work on particular matters when considerations such as cost and highly specialized subject matter make it appropriate to do so.", "Opt_1": "battle", "Opt_2": "counsel", "Opt_3": "crisis", "Opt_4": "policy", "Answer": "counsel", "Opt_1_def": "fight, part of a war", "Opt_2_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_3_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe", "Opt_4_def": "formal rules"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "You can't always control what happens to you, but you can always control how you ____ to what happens to you.", "Opt_1": "depend", "Opt_2": "train", "Opt_3": "react", "Opt_4": "enumerate", "Answer": "react", "Opt_1_def": "be influenced (by)", "Opt_2_def": "to teach someone how to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "to respond", "Opt_4_def": "to list"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The 9-11 Commission failed to ____ or address the multiple war game exercises that were being conducted that day, out of the White House.", "Opt_1": "oppose", "Opt_2": "advance", "Opt_3": "mention", "Opt_4": "provoke", "Answer": "mention", "Opt_1_def": "to be against or fight against something", "Opt_2_def": "to go or move forward; to get better", "Opt_3_def": "to say; state", "Opt_4_def": "to cause to happen"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It was an ____ idea to allow the students to write their own test.", "Opt_1": "extraordinary", "Opt_2": "sufficient", "Opt_3": "typical", "Opt_4": "consistent", "Answer": "extraordinary", "Opt_1_def": "very unusual", "Opt_2_def": "enough", "Opt_3_def": "usual", "Opt_4_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Her work has continued to ____ since the divorce of her parents.", "Opt_1": "unite", "Opt_2": "rotate", "Opt_3": "degenerate", "Opt_4": "diminish", "Answer": "degenerate", "Opt_1_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_2_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_3_def": "to get worse", "Opt_4_def": "to get smaller or less important"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Shortage of research space remains a ____ constraint for future development.", "Opt_1": "sufficient", "Opt_2": "vital", "Opt_3": "significant", "Opt_4": "annual", "Answer": "significant", "Opt_1_def": "enough", "Opt_2_def": "very important", "Opt_3_def": "important, large", "Opt_4_def": "yearly"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "He also was able to assist in identifying ____ science curriculum materials for the teachers in the district to review.", "Opt_1": "arbitrary", "Opt_2": "domestic", "Opt_3": "outstanding", "Opt_4": "elaborate", "Answer": "outstanding", "Opt_1_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others", "Opt_2_def": "home", "Opt_3_def": "excellent", "Opt_4_def": "detailed; complex"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The current program review process is not very ____ because there are neither rewards nor punishments for outcomes.", "Opt_1": "automatic", "Opt_2": "elementary", "Opt_3": "valuable", "Opt_4": "inherent", "Answer": "valuable", "Opt_1_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually", "Opt_2_def": "easy", "Opt_3_def": "worth a lot of money; important", "Opt_4_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "There is a serious shortage of workers in the ____ of computer science. The government is hoping to attract qualified workers from overseas to fill the vacancies.", "Opt_1": "delay", "Opt_2": "potential", "Opt_3": "operation", "Opt_4": "profession", "Answer": "profession", "Opt_1_def": "lateness", "Opt_2_def": "good possibility", "Opt_3_def": "procedure; happening; process", "Opt_4_def": "job; occupation"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government has made ____ any progress towards reducing environmental pollution.", "Opt_1": "occasionally", "Opt_2": "merely", "Opt_3": "overly", "Opt_4": "barely", "Answer": "barely", "Opt_1_def": "sometimes", "Opt_2_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_3_def": "too", "Opt_4_def": "not very much; hardly"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "In other words, his father did not invest the ____ of resources, whether they be human or monetary, necessary for success.", "Opt_1": "scale", "Opt_2": "term", "Opt_3": "level", "Opt_4": "item", "Answer": "level", "Opt_1_def": "extent", "Opt_2_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_3_def": "standard; layer; amount", "Opt_4_def": "thing, element"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Turkish law requires foreign scholars to ____ formal permission to carry out research at institutions in Turkey.", "Opt_1": "ban", "Opt_2": "measure", "Opt_3": "decrease", "Opt_4": "obtain", "Answer": "obtain", "Opt_1_def": "to prohibit or forbid", "Opt_2_def": "to find out how much there is of something", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller, to go down", "Opt_4_def": "to get"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The teachers are not universally in favour of the school's plan to introduce ____ working times.", "Opt_1": "immense", "Opt_2": "flexible", "Opt_3": "elementary", "Opt_4": "apart", "Answer": "flexible", "Opt_1_def": "very large", "Opt_2_def": "can be changed or bent", "Opt_3_def": "easy", "Opt_4_def": "not together, separate"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The headmaster's decision is sure to ____ much discussion among teachers and students at the school.", "Opt_1": "provoke", "Opt_2": "introduce", "Opt_3": "prosper", "Opt_4": "harm", "Answer": "provoke", "Opt_1_def": "to cause to happen", "Opt_2_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time", "Opt_3_def": "to do well; to become rich", "Opt_4_def": "to damage or injure"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "When societies collapse into violence the ____ is all too familiar: the destruction of life and infrastructure, gross abuses of human rights.", "Opt_1": "result", "Opt_2": "generation", "Opt_3": "status", "Opt_4": "notion", "Answer": "result", "Opt_1_def": "outcome, effect", "Opt_2_def": "group of people all born around the same time", "Opt_3_def": "position, standing", "Opt_4_def": "idea; concept"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The nine women here say the ____ treatment of domestic workers is an apartheid-era relic that has no place in democratic South Africa.", "Opt_1": "poor", "Opt_2": "dense", "Opt_3": "pure", "Opt_4": "straightforward", "Answer": "poor", "Opt_1_def": "bad, unsatisfactory", "Opt_2_def": "thick; full; detailed", "Opt_3_def": "complete, 100%", "Opt_4_def": "easy"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Groups should advise the instructor if a member is unexpectedly ____ and try to save materials for that person.", "Opt_1": "averse", "Opt_2": "necessary", "Opt_3": "final", "Opt_4": "absent", "Answer": "absent", "Opt_1_def": "against", "Opt_2_def": "needed; very important", "Opt_3_def": "last", "Opt_4_def": "being not there; missing"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The ____ of applications will continue until all positions are filled.", "Opt_1": "review", "Opt_2": "retreat", "Opt_3": "seek", "Opt_4": "harm", "Answer": "review", "Opt_1_def": "to check over (and make changes)", "Opt_2_def": "to go back", "Opt_3_def": "to look for or want", "Opt_4_def": "to damage or injure"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The water ____ is one of the natural processes that are familiar to most students.", "Opt_1": "detail", "Opt_2": "cycle", "Opt_3": "prestige", "Opt_4": "phenomenon", "Answer": "cycle", "Opt_1_def": "a small piece of information", "Opt_2_def": "a complete series of events or processes", "Opt_3_def": "fame and respect", "Opt_4_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The Commission was unable to estimate the cost of complying with new requirements ____ data recording.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "A hunt for hazardous asteroids by University of Hawaii astronomers who use a unique search ____ has paid off.", "Opt_1": "structure", "Opt_2": "level", "Opt_3": "stage", "Opt_4": "strategy", "Answer": "strategy", "Opt_1_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_2_def": "standard; layer; amount", "Opt_3_def": "period of time, part of a process", "Opt_4_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "They felt this was an unreliable forecast due to ____ data and that the harvest could in fact increase.", "Opt_1": "poor", "Opt_2": "ambiguous", "Opt_3": "substantial", "Opt_4": "widespread", "Answer": "poor", "Opt_1_def": "bad, unsatisfactory", "Opt_2_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation", "Opt_3_def": "large", "Opt_4_def": "common"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Advertising marketed directly to the consumer may minimize the risks and ____ the benefits of medications.", "Opt_1": "devise", "Opt_2": "exaggerate", "Opt_3": "separate", "Opt_4": "settle", "Answer": "exaggerate", "Opt_1_def": "to create or think up", "Opt_2_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_3_def": "to pull or put apart", "Opt_4_def": "to solve a problem or dispute"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "APA offers specific recommendations for eliminating ____ in language concerning race, disability, and sexuality.", "Opt_1": "design", "Opt_2": "facilities", "Opt_3": "bias", "Opt_4": "result", "Answer": "bias", "Opt_1_def": "planning (drawing)", "Opt_2_def": "buildings and other places that can be used by people", "Opt_3_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice", "Opt_4_def": "outcome, effect"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It is ____ that any complex society will have some sort of taxation system.", "Opt_1": "fortunate", "Opt_2": "basic", "Opt_3": "flexible", "Opt_4": "inevitable", "Answer": "inevitable", "Opt_1_def": "lucky", "Opt_2_def": "first or easy", "Opt_3_def": "can be changed or bent", "Opt_4_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The school has employed an ____ to advise on the best way to use computer technology in the classroom.", "Opt_1": "expert", "Opt_2": "decision", "Opt_3": "staff", "Opt_4": "structure", "Answer": "expert", "Opt_1_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_2_def": "intention to do something, choice", "Opt_3_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)", "Opt_4_def": "the way something is made or organized"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This is the completely rational response of a country that has no hope of defeating the United States in ____ but nevertheless wants to insure that it isn't attacked.", "Opt_1": "interval", "Opt_2": "hypothesis", "Opt_3": "innovation", "Opt_4": "battle", "Answer": "battle", "Opt_1_def": "a period of time", "Opt_2_def": "idea or prediction", "Opt_3_def": "new object or idea", "Opt_4_def": "fight, part of a war"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The school needs to ____ the students' project work to the examination board before the end of the month.", "Opt_1": "assimilate", "Opt_2": "deliver", "Opt_3": "facilitate", "Opt_4": "proceed", "Answer": "deliver", "Opt_1_def": "to take in", "Opt_2_def": "to provide (often by bringing to people)", "Opt_3_def": "to make something easier", "Opt_4_def": "to go forward (and do ..)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The school received an anonymous email with complaints ____ one of the teachers.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government has passed laws to give equal rights to minority groups, but it can do nothing to remove the ____ that exists inside some people's heads.", "Opt_1": "controversy", "Opt_2": "ratio", "Opt_3": "advantage", "Opt_4": "prejudice", "Answer": "prejudice", "Opt_1_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions", "Opt_2_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount", "Opt_3_def": "benefit", "Opt_4_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "His written work is actually very good, but he has ____ problems with the difficult English spelling system.", "Opt_1": "annual", "Opt_2": "immense", "Opt_3": "apparent", "Opt_4": "intrinsic", "Answer": "immense", "Opt_1_def": "yearly", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "clear; obvious", "Opt_4_def": "belonging to; inherent in"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Your grades will continue to ____ unless you start working harder.", "Opt_1": "deteriorate", "Opt_2": "appoint", "Opt_3": "tend", "Opt_4": "undertake", "Answer": "deteriorate", "Opt_1_def": "to get worse", "Opt_2_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_3_def": "to often behave in a certain way", "Opt_4_def": "to (plan to) do"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Even with support, because of his health and limits on the hours he could work, he was unable to fulfill the duties of the ____ teaching job.", "Opt_1": "abundant", "Opt_2": "prompt", "Opt_3": "optional", "Opt_4": "typical", "Answer": "typical", "Opt_1_def": "existing in large quantities", "Opt_2_def": "quick; on or before time", "Opt_3_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want", "Opt_4_def": "usual"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The (German) invention of the dynamo brought a ____ in electrical energy leading to the construction of power stations serving cities and towns.", "Opt_1": "technique", "Opt_2": "exponent", "Opt_3": "revolution", "Opt_4": "challenge", "Answer": "revolution", "Opt_1_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion", "Opt_3_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_4_def": "difficult situation; problem"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "When dealing with a real, physical system such as a robot, however, this ____ is simply not practical.", "Opt_1": "approach", "Opt_2": "suppose", "Opt_3": "inhibit", "Opt_4": "recover", "Answer": "approach", "Opt_1_def": "to near; to get closer", "Opt_2_def": "to think, imagine", "Opt_3_def": "to prevent or stop", "Opt_4_def": "to get back"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "China is able to ____ goods cheaply because labour costs are low.", "Opt_1": "analyze", "Opt_2": "manufacture", "Opt_3": "associate", "Opt_4": "fare", "Answer": "manufacture", "Opt_1_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it", "Opt_2_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_3_def": "to link to; to make a connection to", "Opt_4_def": "to do or succeed"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Medical scientists have done extensive research on ____ drugs but they do not know so much how drugs interact with each other.", "Opt_1": "device", "Opt_2": "agent", "Opt_3": "volume", "Opt_4": "individual", "Answer": "individual", "Opt_1_def": "object; method", "Opt_2_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "one person"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "She has learned from her mother's experience, however, and does not ____ the error her mother made.", "Opt_1": "propose", "Opt_2": "attempt", "Opt_3": "detect", "Opt_4": "repeat", "Answer": "repeat", "Opt_1_def": "to suggest", "Opt_2_def": "to try", "Opt_3_def": "to see, find or notice", "Opt_4_def": "to do or say again"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Follow these recommended times for storage in the freezer to enjoy the best ____ in flavor and texture and to maintain good nutritive value.", "Opt_1": "plenty", "Opt_2": "impact", "Opt_3": "intention", "Opt_4": "quality", "Answer": "quality", "Opt_1_def": "many, lots of", "Opt_2_def": "effect", "Opt_3_def": "plan, aim", "Opt_4_def": "worth or value"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "No program has developed an approach that is ____ successful in working with the types of problems that we try to solve.", "Opt_1": "indeed", "Opt_2": "predominantly", "Opt_3": "universally", "Opt_4": "especially", "Answer": "universally", "Opt_1_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_2_def": "mostly", "Opt_3_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_4_def": "particularly"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Attendance will not constitute a specific percentage of your final grade, but if you miss more than two classes you will ____ fail this course.", "Opt_1": "recently", "Opt_2": "eventually", "Opt_3": "definitely", "Opt_4": "indeed", "Answer": "definitely", "Opt_1_def": "in the near past", "Opt_2_def": "in the end", "Opt_3_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_4_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The rules of the school ____ that you must leave your mobile phone in your locker and not bring it to class.", "Opt_1": "predict", "Opt_2": "stipulate", "Opt_3": "produce", "Opt_4": "drain", "Answer": "stipulate", "Opt_1_def": "to say what will happen in the future", "Opt_2_def": "to require", "Opt_3_def": "to make or create", "Opt_4_def": "to take away; to get rid of"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The ____ is planning to extend the school day until 4pm.", "Opt_1": "aim", "Opt_2": "defeat", "Opt_3": "surplus", "Opt_4": "administration", "Answer": "administration", "Opt_1_def": "goal or intention", "Opt_2_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)", "Opt_3_def": "to be, go or make all the way around", "Opt_4_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government has succeeded in reducing unemployment ____ older people; conversely, young people are having ever more difficulty finding a job.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The drugs are used to ____ performance artificially to the degree that they give athletes a competitive edge.", "Opt_1": "cease", "Opt_2": "provoke", "Opt_3": "deviate", "Opt_4": "enhance", "Answer": "enhance", "Opt_1_def": "to stop", "Opt_2_def": "to cause to happen", "Opt_3_def": "to be different", "Opt_4_def": "to make something better"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It's always better to be overly cautious and to ____ yourself by asking for a written contract.", "Opt_1": "magnify", "Opt_2": "construct", "Opt_3": "protect", "Opt_4": "constitute", "Answer": "protect", "Opt_1_def": "to make or show larger", "Opt_2_def": "to make", "Opt_3_def": "to keep something out of danger", "Opt_4_def": "to be; to make up"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It isn't the government's ____ if people ignore advice to live healthily.", "Opt_1": "anomaly", "Opt_2": "fault", "Opt_3": "district", "Opt_4": "citizen", "Answer": "fault", "Opt_1_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data", "Opt_2_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem", "Opt_3_def": "region of a city", "Opt_4_def": "person (member of a country)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "In this assignment, you will need to ____ an array of numbers, so that your computer code executes correctly.", "Opt_1": "manipulate", "Opt_2": "accept", "Opt_3": "determine", "Opt_4": "utilize", "Answer": "manipulate", "Opt_1_def": "to (use and) change", "Opt_2_def": "to agree (to have)", "Opt_3_def": "to find out; to establish or identify; state", "Opt_4_def": "to use"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Humans have a strong ____ to help each other, but is spite also part of the human condition?", "Opt_1": "scheme", "Opt_2": "cycle", "Opt_3": "desire", "Opt_4": "contrary", "Answer": "desire", "Opt_1_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_2_def": "a complete series of events or processes", "Opt_3_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_4_def": "opposite"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Doing so will probably ____ a strong negative response from the group's normal readership.", "Opt_1": "provoke", "Opt_2": "allege", "Opt_3": "respect", "Opt_4": "invest", "Answer": "provoke", "Opt_1_def": "to cause to happen", "Opt_2_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_3_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something", "Opt_4_def": "to put money into something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "We will not ____ unless some of you not only believe in the Constitution, but are willing to engage in public service.", "Opt_1": "underlie", "Opt_2": "depart", "Opt_3": "oppose", "Opt_4": "prevail", "Answer": "prevail", "Opt_1_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something", "Opt_2_def": "to leave; to be different from", "Opt_3_def": "to be against or fight against something", "Opt_4_def": "to succeed; to overcome"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "He was inspired by the dreams and disappointments of those individual schoolteachers who dared to challenge the ____ and follow their own visions toward a better future.", "Opt_1": "margin", "Opt_2": "hierarchy", "Opt_3": "target", "Opt_4": "lecture", "Answer": "hierarchy", "Opt_1_def": "amount; distance", "Opt_2_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_3_def": "aim, goal", "Opt_4_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "His idea is ____ not feasible - no one is going to pay that kind of money.", "Opt_1": "merely", "Opt_2": "definitely", "Opt_3": "moreover", "Opt_4": "simply", "Answer": "simply", "Opt_1_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_2_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_3_def": "also .., what is more ..", "Opt_4_def": "completely; just; only"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "By studying these financial transactions, it is possible to ____ the amount of money that people are willing to pay for the essentials.", "Opt_1": "estimate", "Opt_2": "manufacture", "Opt_3": "retreat", "Opt_4": "assist", "Answer": "estimate", "Opt_1_def": "to make an intelligent guess", "Opt_2_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_3_def": "to go back", "Opt_4_def": "to help"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The chairman needs to ____ a better meeting next time. The last one was very disorganized.", "Opt_1": "arrange", "Opt_2": "base", "Opt_3": "expose", "Opt_4": "employ", "Answer": "arrange", "Opt_1_def": "to plan to happen; to group together", "Opt_2_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_3_def": "to uncover, reveal", "Opt_4_def": "to give a job to someone; to use"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "His research helped establish that ____ DNA sequences may behave differently depending on context and condition.", "Opt_1": "final", "Opt_2": "complex", "Opt_3": "artificial", "Opt_4": "identical", "Answer": "identical", "Opt_1_def": "last", "Opt_2_def": "difficult, complicated", "Opt_3_def": "not real or natural", "Opt_4_def": "exactly the same"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Most famous footballers and film stars need an ____ to take care of their contracts.", "Opt_1": "belief", "Opt_2": "duty", "Opt_3": "margin", "Opt_4": "agent", "Answer": "agent", "Opt_1_def": "what you think; what you believe in", "Opt_2_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do", "Opt_3_def": "amount; distance", "Opt_4_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Very often, in the early summer, the hills are covered during the night by clouds, which do not always ____ until the sun has risen.", "Opt_1": "depart", "Opt_2": "harm", "Opt_3": "associate", "Opt_4": "disperse", "Answer": "disperse", "Opt_1_def": "to leave; to be different from", "Opt_2_def": "to damage or injure", "Opt_3_def": "to link to; to make a connection to", "Opt_4_def": "to spread out; to move apart"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "During the period of time that a student is on probation, any further ____ of misconduct will cause the Board seriously to consider requiring the student to withdraw from the College.", "Opt_1": "instance", "Opt_2": "ability", "Opt_3": "surface", "Opt_4": "device", "Answer": "instance", "Opt_1_def": "example", "Opt_2_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well", "Opt_3_def": "the outside layer of an object", "Opt_4_def": "object; method"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Some people use unethical methods to create a ____ that says what they want it to say.", "Opt_1": "contract", "Opt_2": "standard", "Opt_3": "means", "Opt_4": "statistic", "Answer": "statistic", "Opt_1_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_2_def": "quality", "Opt_3_def": "way", "Opt_4_def": "mathematical number"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Water is very ____ in many parts of North Africa.", "Opt_1": "scarce", "Opt_2": "ambitious", "Opt_3": "exact", "Opt_4": "faint", "Answer": "scarce", "Opt_1_def": "rare, not abundant", "Opt_2_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging", "Opt_3_def": "precise, opposite of approximate", "Opt_4_def": "not strong"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "While we were not ____ surprised by the answers to our questions, it was interesting to see the amount of uniformity in answers.", "Opt_1": "rather", "Opt_2": "overly", "Opt_3": "therefore", "Opt_4": "gradually", "Answer": "overly", "Opt_1_def": "instead", "Opt_2_def": "too", "Opt_3_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_4_def": "slowly; steadily"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It was a very ____ problem. All the students were able to solve it within 5 minutes.", "Opt_1": "prime", "Opt_2": "credible", "Opt_3": "domestic", "Opt_4": "elementary", "Answer": "elementary", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "believable", "Opt_3_def": "home", "Opt_4_def": "easy"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Unlike normal children she cannot attach its ____ meaning to the word \"blue\", so she cannot fully understand basic sentences.", "Opt_1": "ordinary", "Opt_2": "frequent", "Opt_3": "exact", "Opt_4": "positive", "Answer": "ordinary", "Opt_1_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_2_def": "often", "Opt_3_def": "precise, opposite of approximate", "Opt_4_def": "good; optimistic"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "But the mice did not ____ thorough cognitive testing, which requires intact mobility to navigate various mazes.", "Opt_1": "reinforce", "Opt_2": "revise", "Opt_3": "undergo", "Opt_4": "insist", "Answer": "undergo", "Opt_1_def": "to make something stronger", "Opt_2_def": "to change (in order to improve)", "Opt_3_def": "to receive or experience", "Opt_4_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The ____ to peace and prosperity in the region can only commence when the civic authority is brought back in.", "Opt_1": "finance", "Opt_2": "journey", "Opt_3": "guide", "Opt_4": "belief", "Answer": "journey", "Opt_1_def": "to do with money and payment", "Opt_2_def": "a long trip to a different place", "Opt_3_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)", "Opt_4_def": "what you think; what you believe in"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "People are right to be suspicious of any diet that promises ____ success.", "Opt_1": "instant", "Opt_2": "uniform", "Opt_3": "legitimate", "Opt_4": "comprehensive", "Answer": "instant", "Opt_1_def": "immediate", "Opt_2_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_3_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_4_def": "full, complete"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Even more extraordinary, every child ____ one was more than willing to state his or her name to the stranger.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Google uses a unique computer program to generate its lists of hits within a very short ____ of time.", "Opt_1": "status", "Opt_2": "period", "Opt_3": "facilities", "Opt_4": "passage", "Answer": "period", "Opt_1_def": "position, standing", "Opt_2_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)", "Opt_3_def": "buildings and other places that can be used by people", "Opt_4_def": "a piece of written or spoken text"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Greenpeace and World Wide Fund are two of the non-governmental organizations that work to ____ the environment.", "Opt_1": "explain", "Opt_2": "protect", "Opt_3": "disrupt", "Opt_4": "propose", "Answer": "protect", "Opt_1_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to keep something out of danger", "Opt_3_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage", "Opt_4_def": "to suggest"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is not enough to ____ children not to play with fireworks. It should be illegal for children to buy them.", "Opt_1": "distribute", "Opt_2": "warn", "Opt_3": "accomplish", "Opt_4": "adjust", "Answer": "warn", "Opt_1_def": "to give out", "Opt_2_def": "to notify (of possible danger)", "Opt_3_def": "to do or achieve", "Opt_4_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "If you are accepted you will need to arrange to have an ____ copy of your scores sent to the Program address below.", "Opt_1": "contemporary", "Opt_2": "loose", "Opt_3": "elaborate", "Opt_4": "official", "Answer": "official", "Opt_1_def": "of this time, happening now", "Opt_2_def": "not firm or finished", "Opt_3_def": "detailed; complex", "Opt_4_def": "approved by an authority"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The applicant's qualifications must ____ to the qualifications required to perform the duties of the position as indicated in the job description.", "Opt_1": "correlate", "Opt_2": "dominate", "Opt_3": "praise", "Opt_4": "isolate", "Answer": "correlate", "Opt_1_def": "to have a close connection", "Opt_2_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part", "Opt_3_def": "to express approval about something someone has done", "Opt_4_def": "to separate something or someone from others"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Attendance will not constitute a specific percentage of your final grade, but if you miss more than two classes you will ____ fail this course.", "Opt_1": "overly", "Opt_2": "definitely", "Opt_3": "perhaps", "Opt_4": "naturally", "Answer": "definitely", "Opt_1_def": "too", "Opt_2_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_3_def": "maybe, possibly", "Opt_4_def": "of course, obviously"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The recent conference about green energy failed to ____ the interest of the British public.", "Opt_1": "determine", "Opt_2": "engage", "Opt_3": "achieve", "Opt_4": "observe", "Answer": "engage", "Opt_1_def": "to find out; to establish or identify; state", "Opt_2_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on", "Opt_3_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)", "Opt_4_def": "to watch carefully"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "There are ____ parts of the planet that have not yet been explored. These are all on the ocean floor.", "Opt_1": "mobile", "Opt_2": "immense", "Opt_3": "reasonable", "Opt_4": "initial", "Answer": "immense", "Opt_1_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "acceptable, quite good", "Opt_4_def": "starting, first"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The ____ to the school grounds is the stream. You must not cross it.", "Opt_1": "alternative", "Opt_2": "series", "Opt_3": "boundary", "Opt_4": "schedule", "Answer": "boundary", "Opt_1_def": "other possibility", "Opt_2_def": "a number of things, one after the other", "Opt_3_def": "limit, extent", "Opt_4_def": "timetable"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Why, Graeme Newman asks, has reform after reform failed to ____ the spread of crime?", "Opt_1": "halt", "Opt_2": "establish", "Opt_3": "decline", "Opt_4": "define", "Answer": "halt", "Opt_1_def": "to stop", "Opt_2_def": "to begin or set up", "Opt_3_def": "to go down or get worse", "Opt_4_def": "to state what something is or means"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It is important that the government's proposals do not ____ the development of small businesses.", "Opt_1": "accelerate", "Opt_2": "employ", "Opt_3": "suspect", "Opt_4": "inhibit", "Answer": "inhibit", "Opt_1_def": "to get or make faster", "Opt_2_def": "to give a job to someone; to use", "Opt_3_def": "to believe", "Opt_4_def": "to prevent or stop"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Today the World Bank, which is ____ responsible for the disaster of the last thirty years, acknowledges that the standards for human development are falling in Africa.", "Opt_1": "largely", "Opt_2": "virtually", "Opt_3": "therefore", "Opt_4": "namely", "Answer": "largely", "Opt_1_def": "mostly", "Opt_2_def": "almost", "Opt_3_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_4_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The objective is to find the right ____ of materials that will result in the creation of clear electrical signals.", "Opt_1": "interior", "Opt_2": "mixture", "Opt_3": "deal", "Opt_4": "magnitude", "Answer": "mixture", "Opt_1_def": "inside", "Opt_2_def": "combination", "Opt_3_def": "agreement", "Opt_4_def": "size; amount"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It is difficult to judge how much her excellent grade is ____ to hard work and how much to natural talent.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Every necessary precaution has been taken to provide up-to-date, ____ information in this website.", "Opt_1": "accurate", "Opt_2": "tough", "Opt_3": "firm", "Opt_4": "independent", "Answer": "accurate", "Opt_1_def": "exact, containing no mistakes", "Opt_2_def": "difficult, strong", "Opt_3_def": "strong, cannot be changed", "Opt_4_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This widespread ____ was caused by the insufficient amount of media coverage on topic.", "Opt_1": "figure", "Opt_2": "resident", "Opt_3": "ignorance", "Opt_4": "environment", "Answer": "ignorance", "Opt_1_def": "number", "Opt_2_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_3_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_4_def": "the world around us"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "You are being quizzed on how well you understand the information in your required readings, so ____ your answers on what is written in the Hunt textbook.", "Opt_1": "base", "Opt_2": "fulfill", "Opt_3": "harm", "Opt_4": "condemn", "Answer": "base", "Opt_1_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_2_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_3_def": "to damage or injure", "Opt_4_def": "to express strong disapproval"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "At lunchtime students ____ to all parts of the school building and play areas.", "Opt_1": "block", "Opt_2": "disperse", "Opt_3": "regret", "Opt_4": "pursue", "Answer": "disperse", "Opt_1_def": "to not allow; to stop or prevent", "Opt_2_def": "to spread out; to move apart", "Opt_3_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)", "Opt_4_def": "to follow (or do)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Please ____ your answer to a maximum of 100 words.", "Opt_1": "confront", "Opt_2": "formulate", "Opt_3": "occur", "Opt_4": "confine", "Answer": "confine", "Opt_1_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)", "Opt_2_def": "to express", "Opt_3_def": "to happen; take place", "Opt_4_def": "to limit"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Newspapers employ people to ____ the articles submitted by their journalists, but not all mistakes are found.", "Opt_1": "edit", "Opt_2": "publish", "Opt_3": "engage", "Opt_4": "associate", "Answer": "edit", "Opt_1_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing", "Opt_2_def": "to make available in paper or online form", "Opt_3_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on", "Opt_4_def": "to link to; to make a connection to"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The ____ of this study is to investigate the stereotype that men are better in mathematics than women.", "Opt_1": "experiment", "Opt_2": "field", "Opt_3": "objective", "Opt_4": "purpose", "Answer": "purpose", "Opt_1_def": "test", "Opt_2_def": "area of interest or study", "Opt_3_def": "aim or goal", "Opt_4_def": "reason, goal"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Let's ____ the idea that you can actually teach critical thinking skills to primary school children.", "Opt_1": "inquire", "Opt_2": "dismiss", "Opt_3": "prosper", "Opt_4": "review", "Answer": "dismiss", "Opt_1_def": "to ask", "Opt_2_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant", "Opt_3_def": "to do well; to become rich", "Opt_4_def": "to check over (and make changes)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "You can be fairly certain what you read at the government site is ____ and up-to-date.", "Opt_1": "sound", "Opt_2": "available", "Opt_3": "strict", "Opt_4": "accurate", "Answer": "accurate", "Opt_1_def": "good; strong", "Opt_2_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_3_def": "hard, not changeable", "Opt_4_def": "exact, containing no mistakes"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "You will not be able to request a ____ name unless you provide the following information.", "Opt_1": "domain", "Opt_2": "compensation", "Opt_3": "duty", "Opt_4": "experiment", "Answer": "domain", "Opt_1_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_2_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_3_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do", "Opt_4_def": "test"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Many people oppose the ban on smoking in public places, but the ____ are in favour of it.", "Opt_1": "detail", "Opt_2": "majority", "Opt_3": "deed", "Opt_4": "route", "Answer": "majority", "Opt_1_def": "a small piece of information", "Opt_2_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_3_def": "an action", "Opt_4_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Science and technology are driving explosive growth in the production of new knowledge, often with the power to induce ____ changes in society.", "Opt_1": "diverse", "Opt_2": "profound", "Opt_3": "enormous", "Opt_4": "military", "Answer": "profound", "Opt_1_def": "many and different", "Opt_2_def": "deep; great; serious", "Opt_3_def": "very big", "Opt_4_def": "to do with army"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The main reason for not responding to terrorism was not an external issue, but an internal one: the government failed to ____ its duties.", "Opt_1": "threaten", "Opt_2": "achieve", "Opt_3": "involve", "Opt_4": "fulfill", "Answer": "fulfill", "Opt_1_def": "to warn or show signs of danger", "Opt_2_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)", "Opt_3_def": "to include or mean", "Opt_4_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The failures of the national soccer and tennis teams ____ all that is wrong with British sport.", "Opt_1": "differentiate", "Opt_2": "embody", "Opt_3": "store", "Opt_4": "elect", "Answer": "embody", "Opt_1_def": "to make different; to see the difference", "Opt_2_def": "to be a good example of ..", "Opt_3_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later", "Opt_4_def": "to choose by voting"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The principal made no ____ on the reasons for asking the student to leave the school.", "Opt_1": "finance", "Opt_2": "evidence", "Opt_3": "plenty", "Opt_4": "comment", "Answer": "comment", "Opt_1_def": "to do with money and payment", "Opt_2_def": "proof, signs", "Opt_3_def": "many, lots of", "Opt_4_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If the student refuses to leave after being requested to do so, the instructor may summon University Police to ____ the student.", "Opt_1": "commit", "Opt_2": "remove", "Opt_3": "replace", "Opt_4": "found", "Answer": "remove", "Opt_1_def": "to do (often an offense)", "Opt_2_def": "to take away", "Opt_3_def": "to put in or take the place of ..", "Opt_4_def": "to begin (often an organization)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The spaceship has been sending back ____ images of Jupiter as it flies past on its way to the edge of the solar system.", "Opt_1": "faint", "Opt_2": "adjacent", "Opt_3": "bold", "Opt_4": "adequate", "Answer": "faint", "Opt_1_def": "not strong", "Opt_2_def": "next to", "Opt_3_def": "brave", "Opt_4_def": "good enough; ok"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "China is, indeed, going through a ____, but it is not a ____ from capitalism to communism.", "Opt_1": "contract", "Opt_2": "transition", "Opt_3": "comment", "Opt_4": "opportunity", "Answer": "transition", "Opt_1_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_2_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_3_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion", "Opt_4_def": "chance"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Can you please ____ that you will be at the school next year?", "Opt_1": "advise", "Opt_2": "damage", "Opt_3": "own", "Opt_4": "confirm", "Answer": "confirm", "Opt_1_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice", "Opt_2_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_3_def": "to have or possess", "Opt_4_def": "to agree that something is correct"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Errors in grammar and vocabulary may, but do not always, ____ with comprehensibility.", "Opt_1": "examine", "Opt_2": "deduce", "Opt_3": "interfere", "Opt_4": "reject", "Answer": "interfere", "Opt_1_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_2_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to prevent; to harm", "Opt_4_def": "to refuse"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It operated below 60%, was generally poorly designed and therefore not ____ considering.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "During this period she developed her ideas on art, her main one being that the best art did not focus on reality but evoked the ____ of the soul.", "Opt_1": "state", "Opt_2": "shortage", "Opt_3": "account", "Opt_4": "strategy", "Answer": "state", "Opt_1_def": "condition, situation", "Opt_2_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed", "Opt_3_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_4_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "A doctor will usually ask her patient many questions in ____ to make a diagnosis of the illness.", "Opt_1": "structure", "Opt_2": "advantage", "Opt_3": "ratio", "Opt_4": "order", "Answer": "order", "Opt_1_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_2_def": "benefit", "Opt_3_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount", "Opt_4_def": "sequence, place"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Our results did not ____ us to determine whether SMR or MOEE had reached minimum values.", "Opt_1": "enable", "Opt_2": "separate", "Opt_3": "consider", "Opt_4": "utilize", "Answer": "enable", "Opt_1_def": "to make something or someone able to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to pull or put apart", "Opt_3_def": "to think", "Opt_4_def": "to use"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "As long as the person did not ____ large amounts of protein and carbohydrates, the effect on fat digestion was negated.", "Opt_1": "motivate", "Opt_2": "ignore", "Opt_3": "consume", "Opt_4": "reinforce", "Answer": "consume", "Opt_1_def": "to get someone interested enough to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)", "Opt_3_def": "to use, or use up", "Opt_4_def": "to make something stronger"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "There was also no apparent ____ of an attempt to measure the relationship between individual differences in facial shape.", "Opt_1": "record", "Opt_2": "command", "Opt_3": "scheme", "Opt_4": "prestige", "Answer": "record", "Opt_1_def": "evidence; documentation", "Opt_2_def": "control", "Opt_3_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_4_def": "fame and respect"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Due to a rapid increase in the number of students the school needs to ____ 4 new teachers.", "Opt_1": "appoint", "Opt_2": "possess", "Opt_3": "suffer", "Opt_4": "compile", "Answer": "appoint", "Opt_1_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_2_def": "to have or own", "Opt_3_def": "to experience something bad or painful", "Opt_4_def": "to put together (often in a list"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If you wish to contribute material that is copyrighted by someone ____ yourself, then you will need to document that the copyright holder has agreed.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The ultimate ____ of teaching is to teach students how to teach themselves.", "Opt_1": "attitude", "Opt_2": "transition", "Opt_3": "goal", "Opt_4": "ability", "Answer": "goal", "Opt_1_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)", "Opt_2_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_3_def": "aim or intention", "Opt_4_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Most children take a share of ____ duties such as washing the dishes.", "Opt_1": "diverse", "Opt_2": "bold", "Opt_3": "domestic", "Opt_4": "trivial", "Answer": "domestic", "Opt_1_def": "many and different", "Opt_2_def": "brave", "Opt_3_def": "home", "Opt_4_def": "not important"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Stated simply, this ____ means that averaged over large enough distances, one part of the Universe looks approximately like any other part.", "Opt_1": "reply", "Opt_2": "power", "Opt_3": "hierarchy", "Opt_4": "principle", "Answer": "principle", "Opt_1_def": "an answer", "Opt_2_def": "the right or authority to do something", "Opt_3_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_4_def": "rule"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "There is no ____ of him passing the course. He has been away too many times this year.", "Opt_1": "bulk", "Opt_2": "prospect", "Opt_3": "debate", "Opt_4": "purpose", "Answer": "prospect", "Opt_1_def": "majority; largest part", "Opt_2_def": "chance, likelihood", "Opt_3_def": "formal discussion", "Opt_4_def": "reason, goal"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Chromatography is a separation ____ that is used in virtually all branches of science and technology.", "Opt_1": "structure", "Opt_2": "technique", "Opt_3": "impact", "Opt_4": "liberty", "Answer": "technique", "Opt_1_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_2_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "effect", "Opt_4_def": "freedom"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The most basic ____ to develop is observational drawing skills.", "Opt_1": "resource", "Opt_2": "technique", "Opt_3": "skill", "Opt_4": "ignorance", "Answer": "technique", "Opt_1_def": "a source of information or material", "Opt_2_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)", "Opt_4_def": "lack of knowledge"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Please bring all your ____ to class. That includes your homework planner and dictionary.", "Opt_1": "exercise", "Opt_2": "materials", "Opt_3": "forecast", "Opt_4": "belief", "Answer": "materials", "Opt_1_def": "a piece of work, activity", "Opt_2_def": "the things you need to do something", "Opt_3_def": "prediction", "Opt_4_def": "what you think; what you believe in"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Users are guided through a complete ____ of statistical computing: preparing data, performing analysis, viewing output.", "Opt_1": "cycle", "Opt_2": "victory", "Opt_3": "license", "Opt_4": "stereotype", "Answer": "cycle", "Opt_1_def": "a complete series of events or processes", "Opt_2_def": "win", "Opt_3_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)", "Opt_4_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The doctor examined the patient carefully, ____ that he forgot to check blood pressure.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Good teachers must engage their students as they find them, as they ____ themselves, walking in the door.", "Opt_1": "spread", "Opt_2": "protect", "Opt_3": "present", "Opt_4": "manage", "Answer": "present", "Opt_1_def": "to move (over a wider area)", "Opt_2_def": "to keep something out of danger", "Opt_3_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation", "Opt_4_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Homes were built and sold to families in need at no ____ and no interest.", "Opt_1": "battle", "Opt_2": "element", "Opt_3": "stage", "Opt_4": "profit", "Answer": "profit", "Opt_1_def": "fight, part of a war", "Opt_2_def": "aspect, part", "Opt_3_def": "period of time, part of a process", "Opt_4_def": "money gained"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Many new astronomy learners, students and adults alike, are unfamiliar with the universe ____ the solar system.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "I'm trying to ____ a machine that will do my homework for me. - Good luck!", "Opt_1": "admit", "Opt_2": "invent", "Opt_3": "attempt", "Opt_4": "explain", "Answer": "invent", "Opt_1_def": "to allow to enter", "Opt_2_def": "to create (often a new object)", "Opt_3_def": "to try", "Opt_4_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Once Grace Albee arrived in New York City in 1933, she was able to ____ herself to full-time printmaking and her art began to command serious national attention.", "Opt_1": "launch", "Opt_2": "deliver", "Opt_3": "dedicate", "Opt_4": "transfer", "Answer": "dedicate", "Opt_1_def": "to begin", "Opt_2_def": "to provide (often by bringing to people)", "Opt_3_def": "to devote (time and attention)", "Opt_4_def": "to move to a different place or job"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "In infants without a family history of food allergies, there is no need to restrict or ____ any specific foods.", "Opt_1": "recognize", "Opt_2": "continue", "Opt_3": "avoid", "Opt_4": "inspect", "Answer": "avoid", "Opt_1_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)", "Opt_2_def": "to carry on, not stop", "Opt_3_def": "to not do something or go somewhere", "Opt_4_def": "to look at carefully"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The father stated he was from the neighbourhood of Bandon, where he had been unable to ____ any employment.", "Opt_1": "specify", "Opt_2": "appreciate", "Opt_3": "procure", "Opt_4": "expel", "Answer": "procure", "Opt_1_def": "to state exactly", "Opt_2_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)", "Opt_3_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_4_def": "to drive or push out"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "In other words, his father did not invest the ____ of resources, whether they be human or monetary, necessary for success.", "Opt_1": "level", "Opt_2": "element", "Opt_3": "coincidence", "Opt_4": "intention", "Answer": "level", "Opt_1_def": "standard; layer; amount", "Opt_2_def": "aspect, part", "Opt_3_def": "an uncommon happening of two things", "Opt_4_def": "plan, aim"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Most people do not ____ politicians who make promises everyone knows cannot be kept.", "Opt_1": "subsidize", "Opt_2": "respect", "Opt_3": "speculate", "Opt_4": "prevail", "Answer": "respect", "Opt_1_def": "to support financially", "Opt_2_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something", "Opt_3_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)", "Opt_4_def": "to succeed; to overcome"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "We have not made much ____ toward the fulfillment of Xabier's dream of finding a solution to world poverty.", "Opt_1": "scheme", "Opt_2": "obligation", "Opt_3": "administration", "Opt_4": "progress", "Answer": "progress", "Opt_1_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_2_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_3_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_4_def": "improvement or development"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Although consultation between students in solving problems is encouraged, ____ answers will be considered plagiarized.", "Opt_1": "final", "Opt_2": "identical", "Opt_3": "capable", "Opt_4": "preliminary", "Answer": "identical", "Opt_1_def": "last", "Opt_2_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_3_def": "able", "Opt_4_def": "first; initial"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "After massive criticism the government has decided to ____ language courses for immigrants to the country.", "Opt_1": "reward", "Opt_2": "contribute", "Opt_3": "avoid", "Opt_4": "restore", "Answer": "restore", "Opt_1_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_3_def": "to not do something or go somewhere", "Opt_4_def": "to put back, create again"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "We are often right on the ____ of warm and cold or moist and dry air masses. So we get some very difficult weather conditions to try to forecast.", "Opt_1": "boundary", "Opt_2": "opinion", "Opt_3": "device", "Opt_4": "level", "Answer": "boundary", "Opt_1_def": "limit, extent", "Opt_2_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "object; method", "Opt_4_def": "standard; layer; amount"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "While we are less concerned with the politics of Nigeria, we understand that a ____ domestic situation would be to our advantage.", "Opt_1": "stable", "Opt_2": "rational", "Opt_3": "invisible", "Opt_4": "conscious", "Answer": "stable", "Opt_1_def": "not changing; not easy to change", "Opt_2_def": "base on reason, not on emotion or instinct", "Opt_3_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_4_def": "aware, knowing"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The ____ of time that policeman spend on the streets must not diminish.", "Opt_1": "evidence", "Opt_2": "amount", "Opt_3": "margin", "Opt_4": "counsel", "Answer": "amount", "Opt_1_def": "proof, signs", "Opt_2_def": "how much there is of something", "Opt_3_def": "amount; distance", "Opt_4_def": "advice; advisor"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The ____ of applications will continue until all positions are filled.", "Opt_1": "raise", "Opt_2": "review", "Opt_3": "communicate", "Opt_4": "emphasize", "Answer": "review", "Opt_1_def": "to lift; to make higher", "Opt_2_def": "to check over (and make changes)", "Opt_3_def": "to convey information", "Opt_4_def": "to stress, to say something strongly"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "My father's company is going to ____ our move to Germany by employing an agent to help us find a house here.", "Opt_1": "facilitate", "Opt_2": "recommend", "Opt_3": "abandon", "Opt_4": "attach", "Answer": "facilitate", "Opt_1_def": "to make something easier", "Opt_2_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good", "Opt_3_def": "to leave or give up", "Opt_4_def": "to put together with"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The candidate must ____ clear written and verbal communication skills, and must be willing to work in a team project environment.", "Opt_1": "command", "Opt_2": "category", "Opt_3": "growth", "Opt_4": "truth", "Answer": "command", "Opt_1_def": "control", "Opt_2_def": "group of similar items", "Opt_3_def": "development, increase", "Opt_4_def": "actual reason or fact"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The book is at its best when it delves energetically into some particular event, and draws out its ____ meaning with reference to the grand themes.", "Opt_1": "abnormal", "Opt_2": "crucial", "Opt_3": "abstract", "Opt_4": "passive", "Answer": "abstract", "Opt_1_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_2_def": "extremely important", "Opt_3_def": "not specific or concrete", "Opt_4_def": "not active; unresponsive"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Upon completion of your program requirements, you will need to apply for a ____ to teach in the state of Ohio.", "Opt_1": "revolution", "Opt_2": "course", "Opt_3": "operation", "Opt_4": "license", "Answer": "license", "Opt_1_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_2_def": "a subject or period of study", "Opt_3_def": "procedure; happening; process", "Opt_4_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The university has no ____ to refund the fee after the second week of the semester.", "Opt_1": "obligation", "Opt_2": "deed", "Opt_3": "remedy", "Opt_4": "source", "Answer": "obligation", "Opt_1_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_2_def": "an action", "Opt_3_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_4_def": "where something begins, where you can find something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government failed to understand why the people were so unhappy with its policies, and ____ was voted out at the next election.", "Opt_1": "seldom", "Opt_2": "generally", "Opt_3": "thus", "Opt_4": "merely", "Answer": "thus", "Opt_1_def": "rare", "Opt_2_def": "usually", "Opt_3_def": "so", "Opt_4_def": "only, just, simply"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Her ____ was that the Korean people believe that the U.S. policy is to have a divided Korea and that the U.S. is the reason the two countries are not united.", "Opt_1": "situation", "Opt_2": "truth", "Opt_3": "environment", "Opt_4": "perspective", "Answer": "perspective", "Opt_1_def": "circumstances", "Opt_2_def": "actual reason or fact", "Opt_3_def": "the world around us", "Opt_4_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "We ____ his behavior as very serious and we hope this ban will serve as an example.If you violate the rules about downloading internet files, you will not be allowed to use the computer lab.", "Opt_1": "condemn", "Opt_2": "view", "Opt_3": "receive", "Opt_4": "suspend", "Answer": "view", "Opt_1_def": "to express strong disapproval", "Opt_2_def": "to have an opinion", "Opt_3_def": "to get", "Opt_4_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The report was designed to measure computer and Internet use ____ people with disabilities.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Do not ____ the period after an abbreviation such as in. (for inch), which could be confused with the word in.", "Opt_1": "compel", "Opt_2": "omit", "Opt_3": "revise", "Opt_4": "subsidize", "Answer": "omit", "Opt_1_def": "to force or make happen", "Opt_2_def": "to leave something out or not do something", "Opt_3_def": "to change (in order to improve)", "Opt_4_def": "to support financially"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Frankfurt International School has invited the ____ community to its Open Day.", "Opt_1": "intense", "Opt_2": "local", "Opt_3": "available", "Opt_4": "annual", "Answer": "local", "Opt_1_def": "strong, extreme", "Opt_2_def": "in the area where you live or work", "Opt_3_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_4_def": "yearly"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If he was ____ employed by the Grand Duke, that would account for his odd behaviour.", "Opt_1": "barely", "Opt_2": "respectively", "Opt_3": "moreover", "Opt_4": "indeed", "Answer": "indeed", "Opt_1_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_2_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_3_def": "also .., what is more ..", "Opt_4_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Children in Experiment 2 did not exhibit any ____ of recognizing the familiarized words in the passages.", "Opt_1": "stereotype", "Opt_2": "reluctance", "Opt_3": "assignment", "Opt_4": "evidence", "Answer": "evidence", "Opt_1_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)", "Opt_2_def": "unwillingness; hesitation", "Opt_3_def": "a task; the giving of a task", "Opt_4_def": "proof, signs"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It was not ____ to many people why the government had decided to ban smoking in all restaurants but to allow it in its own buildings.", "Opt_1": "imaginary", "Opt_2": "evident", "Opt_3": "unique", "Opt_4": "political", "Answer": "evident", "Opt_1_def": "not real; from the imagination", "Opt_2_def": "clear", "Opt_3_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind", "Opt_4_def": "to do government and politics"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "His concerts in the U.S. often ____ works by Scandinavian composers; conversely, he introduces American organ works to Scandinavian audiences.", "Opt_1": "infer", "Opt_2": "include", "Opt_3": "assert", "Opt_4": "separate", "Answer": "include", "Opt_1_def": "to come to a conclusion about something", "Opt_2_def": "to put in; to have in", "Opt_3_def": "to claim, to say strongly", "Opt_4_def": "to pull or put apart"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This widespread ____ was caused by the insufficient amount of media coverage on topic.", "Opt_1": "career", "Opt_2": "ignorance", "Opt_3": "ratio", "Opt_4": "background", "Answer": "ignorance", "Opt_1_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_2_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_3_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount", "Opt_4_def": "family experiences; circumstances"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The company won the contract to ____ the government with 30,000 special computers for primary schools.", "Opt_1": "version", "Opt_2": "account", "Opt_3": "rank", "Opt_4": "supply", "Answer": "supply", "Opt_1_def": "form", "Opt_2_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_3_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)", "Opt_4_def": "provision, store"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The evidence is overwhelming that prediction markets provide a more ____ prediction than polls.", "Opt_1": "military", "Opt_2": "latter", "Opt_3": "radical", "Opt_4": "accurate", "Answer": "accurate", "Opt_1_def": "to do with army", "Opt_2_def": "the second of two things mentioned", "Opt_3_def": "extreme, strong", "Opt_4_def": "exact, containing no mistakes"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The faculty member cannot refuse a ____ request for extension of the project due date.", "Opt_1": "reasonable", "Opt_2": "intense", "Opt_3": "sole", "Opt_4": "particular", "Answer": "reasonable", "Opt_1_def": "acceptable, quite good", "Opt_2_def": "strong, extreme", "Opt_3_def": "only", "Opt_4_def": "specific"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "San Francisco's justice reform program is ____ alive, says a UC Berkeley report.", "Opt_1": "extremely", "Opt_2": "indirectly", "Opt_3": "seldom", "Opt_4": "barely", "Answer": "barely", "Opt_1_def": "very", "Opt_2_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_3_def": "rare", "Opt_4_def": "not very much; hardly"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The continued presence of a huge military force in the Gulf area provides the necessary ____ of pressure to ensure implementation of obligations.", "Opt_1": "code", "Opt_2": "shortage", "Opt_3": "element", "Opt_4": "equipment", "Answer": "element", "Opt_1_def": "a set of rules", "Opt_2_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed", "Opt_3_def": "aspect, part", "Opt_4_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It is essential that governments take ____ before making the decision to go to war.", "Opt_1": "status", "Opt_2": "counsel", "Opt_3": "policy", "Opt_4": "facilities", "Answer": "counsel", "Opt_1_def": "position, standing", "Opt_2_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_3_def": "formal rules", "Opt_4_def": "buildings and other places that can be used by people"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The ____ between Russia's dominant military power and our own inferior power could not be bridged overnight.", "Opt_1": "gap", "Opt_2": "stereotype", "Opt_3": "region", "Opt_4": "detail", "Answer": "gap", "Opt_1_def": "space, opening or time between", "Opt_2_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)", "Opt_3_def": "part of a place", "Opt_4_def": "a small piece of information"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The school received an anonymous email with complaints ____ one of the teachers.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The company won the ____ to supply the government with 30,000 special computers for primary schools.", "Opt_1": "contract", "Opt_2": "generation", "Opt_3": "domain", "Opt_4": "region", "Answer": "contract", "Opt_1_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_2_def": "group of people all born around the same time", "Opt_3_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_4_def": "part of a place"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If you ____ your application in person, there will be a delay of up to 48 hours following receipt of your application before you can enroll for classes.", "Opt_1": "compel", "Opt_2": "afford", "Opt_3": "submit", "Opt_4": "separate", "Answer": "submit", "Opt_1_def": "to force or make happen", "Opt_2_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_3_def": "to give; to send", "Opt_4_def": "to pull or put apart"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "A common task in the English classroom is to ____ the parts of speech into nouns, adjectives, verbs, etc.", "Opt_1": "ruin", "Opt_2": "classify", "Opt_3": "devise", "Opt_4": "ban", "Answer": "classify", "Opt_1_def": "to spoil or damage", "Opt_2_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_3_def": "to create or think up", "Opt_4_def": "to prohibit or forbid"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "We ____ the right to refuse alcohol service to anyone who cannot provide proper identification.", "Opt_1": "insist", "Opt_2": "cover", "Opt_3": "reserve", "Opt_4": "decrease", "Answer": "reserve", "Opt_1_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim", "Opt_2_def": "to do; to complete", "Opt_3_def": "to keep", "Opt_4_def": "to get smaller, to go down"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "A serious problem of nuclear power is where and how to ____ of the radioactive waste.", "Opt_1": "annotate", "Opt_2": "dispose", "Opt_3": "contradict", "Opt_4": "predict", "Answer": "dispose", "Opt_1_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_2_def": "to get rid of", "Opt_3_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_4_def": "to say what will happen in the future"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It was a chance to try out something different and immerse myself completely in another culture and it was a ____ I did not regret.", "Opt_1": "access", "Opt_2": "episode", "Opt_3": "choice", "Opt_4": "surplus", "Answer": "choice", "Opt_1_def": "the right to enter or use", "Opt_2_def": "period of time", "Opt_3_def": "decision, selection", "Opt_4_def": "to be, go or make all the way around"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Attendance will not constitute a specific percentage of your final grade, but if you miss more than two classes you will ____ fail this course.", "Opt_1": "accordingly", "Opt_2": "definitely", "Opt_3": "approximately", "Opt_4": "recently", "Answer": "definitely", "Opt_1_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with", "Opt_2_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_3_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_4_def": "in the near past"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Nine tenths of an iceberg is under water and hence ____ to ships.", "Opt_1": "aware", "Opt_2": "invisible", "Opt_3": "widespread", "Opt_4": "passive", "Answer": "invisible", "Opt_1_def": "knowing", "Opt_2_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_3_def": "common", "Opt_4_def": "not active; unresponsive"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "In a world of ____ problems but finite resources, competition for adequate attention and funding is substantial.", "Opt_1": "permanent", "Opt_2": "evident", "Opt_3": "rare", "Opt_4": "infinite", "Answer": "infinite", "Opt_1_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time", "Opt_2_def": "clear", "Opt_3_def": "unusual", "Opt_4_def": "without an end"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "There are one or two ____ spelling problems but in general this is an excellent piece of writing.", "Opt_1": "urban", "Opt_2": "forthcoming", "Opt_3": "minor", "Opt_4": "competent", "Answer": "minor", "Opt_1_def": "of the town or city", "Opt_2_def": "coming soon", "Opt_3_def": "small, not important", "Opt_4_def": "good at something (often a job)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Groups should ____ the instructor if a member is unexpectedly absent and try to save materials for that person.", "Opt_1": "expel", "Opt_2": "degenerate", "Opt_3": "advise", "Opt_4": "reduce", "Answer": "advise", "Opt_1_def": "to drive or push out", "Opt_2_def": "to get worse", "Opt_3_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice", "Opt_4_def": "to make smaller or shorter"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Children who have no ____ to their behaviour are often unhappy.", "Opt_1": "boundary", "Opt_2": "reluctance", "Opt_3": "decision", "Opt_4": "function", "Answer": "boundary", "Opt_1_def": "limit, extent", "Opt_2_def": "unwillingness; hesitation", "Opt_3_def": "intention to do something, choice", "Opt_4_def": "job or role"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Teachers should not ____ the discussion or act as the last word on a student's artwork.", "Opt_1": "focus", "Opt_2": "judge", "Opt_3": "dominate", "Opt_4": "trade", "Answer": "dominate", "Opt_1_def": "to direct attention (on an issue)", "Opt_2_def": "to give an opinion about someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part", "Opt_4_def": "to exchange products or services"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "People with eye problems often cannot ____ the colors red and green.", "Opt_1": "classify", "Opt_2": "postpone", "Opt_3": "differentiate", "Opt_4": "respect", "Answer": "differentiate", "Opt_1_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_2_def": "to put back in time", "Opt_3_def": "to make different; to see the difference", "Opt_4_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The ____ of the proposal is to deprive people of the liberty to download songs and videos from the internet.", "Opt_1": "technique", "Opt_2": "administration", "Opt_3": "boundary", "Opt_4": "aim", "Answer": "aim", "Opt_1_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_3_def": "limit, extent", "Opt_4_def": "goal or intention"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Most leadership training programs leave out the key question, ____ how leaders actually affect their groups.", "Opt_1": "namely", "Opt_2": "thereby", "Opt_3": "overly", "Opt_4": "generally", "Answer": "namely", "Opt_1_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_2_def": "by doing this", "Opt_3_def": "too", "Opt_4_def": "usually"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "She found, however, that there is no documented process for achieving a ____ response to adversity.", "Opt_1": "precise", "Opt_2": "wise", "Opt_3": "convenient", "Opt_4": "abundant", "Answer": "wise", "Opt_1_def": "exact", "Opt_2_def": "intelligent; sensible", "Opt_3_def": "easy, not causing problems", "Opt_4_def": "existing in large quantities"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "He failed to submit proof that he had completed an approved substance- ____ program as required.", "Opt_1": "insert", "Opt_2": "amend", "Opt_3": "abuse", "Opt_4": "stimulate", "Answer": "abuse", "Opt_1_def": "to put in", "Opt_2_def": "to change (usually to improve something)", "Opt_3_def": "to treat someone or something badly", "Opt_4_def": "to interest, make grow or encourage"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If you are reliable and flexible, enjoy solving tasks independently and are committed to achieving ____ performance, then this is the job for you.", "Opt_1": "loose", "Opt_2": "supplementary", "Opt_3": "public", "Opt_4": "outstanding", "Answer": "outstanding", "Opt_1_def": "not firm or finished", "Opt_2_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_3_def": "open to all; not private", "Opt_4_def": "excellent"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Your good grades in the report ____ my expectations. Well done!", "Opt_1": "exceed", "Opt_2": "depend", "Opt_3": "restrict", "Opt_4": "conform", "Answer": "exceed", "Opt_1_def": "to be more than or better than", "Opt_2_def": "be influenced (by)", "Opt_3_def": "to limit", "Opt_4_def": "to do what is required"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Students will ____ comprehensive analysis of several works and will compile a database of quality literature.", "Opt_1": "undertake", "Opt_2": "drain", "Opt_3": "encourage", "Opt_4": "restore", "Answer": "undertake", "Opt_1_def": "to (plan to) do", "Opt_2_def": "to take away; to get rid of", "Opt_3_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help", "Opt_4_def": "to put back, create again"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This finding may ____ why increasing numbers of people in the United States lack the natural ability to regulate food intake and body weight.", "Opt_1": "adjust", "Opt_2": "explain", "Opt_3": "stipulate", "Opt_4": "discuss", "Answer": "explain", "Opt_1_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)", "Opt_2_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to require", "Opt_4_def": "to talk about"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The committee needs to ____ of both teachers and parents.", "Opt_1": "discover", "Opt_2": "consist", "Opt_3": "classify", "Opt_4": "fail", "Answer": "consist", "Opt_1_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)", "Opt_2_def": "to have in it; to have as part of it", "Opt_3_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The developing world does not create many industrial wastes; ____ it has had little opportunity to develop proper disposal techniques.", "Opt_1": "namely", "Opt_2": "thus", "Opt_3": "greatly", "Opt_4": "eventually", "Answer": "thus", "Opt_1_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_2_def": "so", "Opt_3_def": "very much", "Opt_4_def": "in the end"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The programme will ____ several basic creative thinking techniques and this theme will recur in problem-solving mode in Part 2 of the programme.", "Opt_1": "protest", "Opt_2": "include", "Opt_3": "prohibit", "Opt_4": "subsidize", "Answer": "include", "Opt_1_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_2_def": "to put in; to have in", "Opt_3_def": "to ban, disallow", "Opt_4_def": "to support financially"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The temperature curve shows that the ____ was not steady with time; a fact which could hardly be expected and is also not observed on other continents.", "Opt_1": "increase", "Opt_2": "conduct", "Opt_3": "deny", "Opt_4": "manage", "Answer": "increase", "Opt_1_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_2_def": "to do or perform; to behave", "Opt_3_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct", "Opt_4_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If you want to know whether an ____ is common or not, look it up in Google.", "Opt_1": "deal", "Opt_2": "resident", "Opt_3": "phrase", "Opt_4": "prejudice", "Answer": "phrase", "Opt_1_def": "agreement", "Opt_2_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_3_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure.", "Opt_4_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Vegetable crops are the most important ____ group for small farms in southern states and their importance is expected to increase.", "Opt_1": "commodity", "Opt_2": "belief", "Opt_3": "topic", "Opt_4": "factor", "Answer": "commodity", "Opt_1_def": "a product; something you can buy", "Opt_2_def": "what you think; what you believe in", "Opt_3_def": "area of interest or discussion", "Opt_4_def": "an aspect to be considered"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "We need to put our minds together and decide if we need to collaborate ____ our institutions to provide a new service.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Please remember to inspect any rented vehicle before driving it and note any scratches or other ____ to the vehicle on the rental form.", "Opt_1": "manifest", "Opt_2": "connect", "Opt_3": "damage", "Opt_4": "represent", "Answer": "damage", "Opt_1_def": "show", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or put together", "Opt_3_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_4_def": "to be; to show or indicate"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The ambassador seems to have failed in his duty to correctly ____ the government he serves.", "Opt_1": "communicate", "Opt_2": "inform", "Opt_3": "collapse", "Opt_4": "retreat", "Answer": "inform", "Opt_1_def": "to convey information", "Opt_2_def": "to say, give information", "Opt_3_def": "to fall down completely and heavily; to fail", "Opt_4_def": "to go back"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "You can submit your work at any time prior to the ____ date.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "If your parents want to take you out of school during term time, they must have a ____ reason.", "Opt_1": "legitimate", "Opt_2": "positive", "Opt_3": "average", "Opt_4": "crucial", "Answer": "legitimate", "Opt_1_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_2_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_3_def": "ordinary, typical", "Opt_4_def": "extremely important"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There is no ____ of him passing the course. He has been away too many times this year.", "Opt_1": "deed", "Opt_2": "prospect", "Opt_3": "circumstances", "Opt_4": "decade", "Answer": "prospect", "Opt_1_def": "an action", "Opt_2_def": "chance, likelihood", "Opt_3_def": "situation", "Opt_4_def": "a period of ten years"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The most ____ reason for the bad test scores is that the teacher was new and inexperienced.", "Opt_1": "optional", "Opt_2": "probable", "Opt_3": "commercial", "Opt_4": "harsh", "Answer": "probable", "Opt_1_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want", "Opt_2_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers.", "Opt_3_def": "to do with business", "Opt_4_def": "hard, unfair"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The settlers decided to ____ the settlement and sail back to Cuba.", "Opt_1": "abandon", "Opt_2": "express", "Opt_3": "comprise", "Opt_4": "exploit", "Answer": "abandon", "Opt_1_def": "to leave or give up", "Opt_2_def": "to say or mean", "Opt_3_def": "to be made up of; to include", "Opt_4_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "This review found that some guidelines and standards for reprocessing rigid laryngoscopes are incomplete, inadequate, and not ____ with one another.", "Opt_1": "consistent", "Opt_2": "feasible", "Opt_3": "formal", "Opt_4": "ideal", "Answer": "consistent", "Opt_1_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_2_def": "possible", "Opt_3_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday", "Opt_4_def": "best, optimal"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "You will not get a ____ reply to your email. He is very busy at the moment.", "Opt_1": "scarce", "Opt_2": "royal", "Opt_3": "prompt", "Opt_4": "distinct", "Answer": "prompt", "Opt_1_def": "rare, not abundant", "Opt_2_def": "of kings and queens", "Opt_3_def": "quick; on or before time", "Opt_4_def": "clear and strong"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Every employee must ____ an annual tax declaration to his or her local tax office.", "Opt_1": "intervene", "Opt_2": "clarify", "Opt_3": "descend", "Opt_4": "submit", "Answer": "submit", "Opt_1_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)", "Opt_2_def": "to make something clear, explain", "Opt_3_def": "to go down", "Opt_4_def": "to give; to send"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "How the ____ changed when he entered a room: it was warm, electric, somehow bigger.", "Opt_1": "behalf", "Opt_2": "period", "Opt_3": "atmosphere", "Opt_4": "coincidence", "Answer": "atmosphere", "Opt_1_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of", "Opt_2_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)", "Opt_3_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_4_def": "an uncommon happening of two things"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The developing world does not create many industrial wastes; thus it has had little opportunity to develop ____ disposal techniques.", "Opt_1": "adequate", "Opt_2": "rigid", "Opt_3": "regular", "Opt_4": "proper", "Answer": "proper", "Opt_1_def": "good enough; ok", "Opt_2_def": "strict, unbending", "Opt_3_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal", "Opt_4_def": "correct, appropriate"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "They ____ the food directly to needy families and individuals.", "Opt_1": "distribute", "Opt_2": "add", "Opt_3": "inquire", "Opt_4": "constitute", "Answer": "distribute", "Opt_1_def": "to give out", "Opt_2_def": "to include; to give or say extra", "Opt_3_def": "to ask", "Opt_4_def": "to be; to make up"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Next you need to formulate a search statement so you can ____ a database search.", "Opt_1": "reflect", "Opt_2": "append", "Opt_3": "maintain", "Opt_4": "conduct", "Answer": "conduct", "Opt_1_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_2_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)", "Opt_3_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_4_def": "to do or perform; to behave"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "For this year's mathematics course, you will need to ____ a good graphics calculator.", "Opt_1": "release", "Opt_2": "assure", "Opt_3": "diverge", "Opt_4": "procure", "Answer": "procure", "Opt_1_def": "to let go or let out", "Opt_2_def": "to make sure; to say that something will certainly happen", "Opt_3_def": "to move apart; to be different from", "Opt_4_def": "to get or obtain"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The student said that his dog had eaten his homework. The teacher did not believe him but could not ____ what he said.", "Opt_1": "assess", "Opt_2": "refute", "Opt_3": "constitute", "Opt_4": "persist", "Answer": "refute", "Opt_1_def": "to judge or test", "Opt_2_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny", "Opt_3_def": "to be; to make up", "Opt_4_def": "to continue (often in the face of difficulty)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Almost everyone believes that terrorism should be fought, but there is little agreement about the ____ in which it should be done.", "Opt_1": "battle", "Opt_2": "hierarchy", "Opt_3": "trend", "Opt_4": "manner", "Answer": "manner", "Opt_1_def": "fight, part of a war", "Opt_2_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_3_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "way of doing something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "With her departure we have decided to ____ teaching Spanish this fall as we await the committee report.", "Opt_1": "correspond", "Opt_2": "suspend", "Opt_3": "contain", "Opt_4": "disperse", "Answer": "suspend", "Opt_1_def": "to be related to", "Opt_2_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)", "Opt_3_def": "to have in it; to hold inside", "Opt_4_def": "to spread out; to move apart"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Your final writing must ____ to your research notes, otherwise you risk being accused of plagiarism.", "Opt_1": "deny", "Opt_2": "distinguish", "Opt_3": "correlate", "Opt_4": "retain", "Answer": "correlate", "Opt_1_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct", "Opt_2_def": "to make clear the differences between two things", "Opt_3_def": "to have a close connection", "Opt_4_def": "to keep"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "He was inspired by the dreams and disappointments of those individual schoolteachers who dared to ____ the hierarchy and follow their own visions toward a better future.", "Opt_1": "decade", "Opt_2": "argument", "Opt_3": "demand", "Opt_4": "challenge", "Answer": "challenge", "Opt_1_def": "a period of ten years", "Opt_2_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)", "Opt_3_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_4_def": "difficult situation; problem"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Many of the students were unable to ____ the relevance of the mathematics they had learned and so could not make use of it.", "Opt_1": "reserve", "Opt_2": "undertake", "Opt_3": "append", "Opt_4": "perceive", "Answer": "perceive", "Opt_1_def": "to keep", "Opt_2_def": "to (plan to) do", "Opt_3_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)", "Opt_4_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "As a business person who frequently deals with recent college graduates, I'd say that there has been a ____ deterioration of writing (and speaking) skills.", "Opt_1": "main", "Opt_2": "chief", "Opt_3": "steady", "Opt_4": "sufficient", "Answer": "steady", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm", "Opt_4_def": "enough"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The findings directly ____ the assertion that some verbal areas of the brain are larger in women than in men.", "Opt_1": "contradict", "Opt_2": "contemplate", "Opt_3": "demonstrate", "Opt_4": "allocate", "Answer": "contradict", "Opt_1_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_2_def": "to think about; to consider", "Opt_3_def": "to show", "Opt_4_def": "to give to (to promise to give)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Listening to the people is an ____ aspect of good government.", "Opt_1": "harsh", "Opt_2": "diverse", "Opt_3": "ultimate", "Opt_4": "intrinsic", "Answer": "intrinsic", "Opt_1_def": "hard, unfair", "Opt_2_def": "many and different", "Opt_3_def": "final or most important", "Opt_4_def": "belonging to; inherent in"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "This unnecessary legislation would adversely impact the existing review system that ensures the high quality of scientific ____ in the United States.", "Opt_1": "incentive", "Opt_2": "research", "Opt_3": "event", "Opt_4": "member", "Answer": "research", "Opt_1_def": "reason to do something", "Opt_2_def": "study; the finding of information", "Opt_3_def": "a happening", "Opt_4_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If you ____ against the school's computer use policy, you will not be permitted to use the computer labs.", "Opt_1": "offend", "Opt_2": "encounter", "Opt_3": "revive", "Opt_4": "inhibit", "Answer": "offend", "Opt_1_def": "to go against; to upset", "Opt_2_def": "to meet or experience", "Opt_3_def": "to bring back (to life)", "Opt_4_def": "to prevent or stop"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Lincoln, while receiving a ____ vote among northerners, did not receive a ____ of ALL the popular votes.", "Opt_1": "majority", "Opt_2": "revolution", "Opt_3": "rank", "Opt_4": "concern", "Answer": "majority", "Opt_1_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_2_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_3_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)", "Opt_4_def": "worry, fear"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Some people claim that the ____ of the internet has been to the detriment of students' ability and willingness to read.", "Opt_1": "staff", "Opt_2": "area", "Opt_3": "growth", "Opt_4": "term", "Answer": "growth", "Opt_1_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)", "Opt_2_def": "field, sphere", "Opt_3_def": "development, increase", "Opt_4_def": "a word or expression"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "In many cases, simply stating to the student that the behavior is unacceptable and must not ____ again is sufficient.", "Opt_1": "occur", "Opt_2": "amend", "Opt_3": "remain", "Opt_4": "afford", "Answer": "occur", "Opt_1_def": "to happen; take place", "Opt_2_def": "to change (usually to improve something)", "Opt_3_def": "to stay; still exist", "Opt_4_def": "to be able to pay for something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Although most universities say they place a high value on teaching, faculty often feel that teaching is somehow ____ to the administration.", "Opt_1": "distinct", "Opt_2": "hostile", "Opt_3": "actual", "Opt_4": "invisible", "Answer": "invisible", "Opt_1_def": "clear and strong", "Opt_2_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to", "Opt_3_def": "real", "Opt_4_def": "cannot be seen"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It was ____ of him to criticize the boss in front of all the workers.", "Opt_1": "immense", "Opt_2": "various", "Opt_3": "domestic", "Opt_4": "bold", "Answer": "bold", "Opt_1_def": "very large", "Opt_2_def": "several, of different kinds", "Opt_3_def": "home", "Opt_4_def": "brave"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "This is, once again, not an ____ against bilingual education, because studies have shown that children in well- designed bilingual programs do well.", "Opt_1": "argument", "Opt_2": "coincidence", "Opt_3": "compensation", "Opt_4": "detriment", "Answer": "argument", "Opt_1_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)", "Opt_2_def": "an uncommon happening of two things", "Opt_3_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_4_def": "disadvantage"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Lispeth took to Christianity readily, and did not ____ it when she reached womanhood.", "Opt_1": "enable", "Opt_2": "deteriorate", "Opt_3": "conform", "Opt_4": "abandon", "Answer": "abandon", "Opt_1_def": "to make something or someone able to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to get worse", "Opt_3_def": "to do what is required", "Opt_4_def": "to leave or give up"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Do not ____ all your energy in the first 20 minutes. Remember that the game lasts for half an hour!", "Opt_1": "precede", "Opt_2": "employ", "Opt_3": "publish", "Opt_4": "exhaust", "Answer": "exhaust", "Opt_1_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to give a job to someone; to use", "Opt_3_def": "to make available in paper or online form", "Opt_4_def": "to use up"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "In Germany most students have the chance to gain practical ____ in an office or factory, before deciding what job they would like to do.", "Opt_1": "decision", "Opt_2": "ratio", "Opt_3": "theory", "Opt_4": "experience", "Answer": "experience", "Opt_1_def": "intention to do something, choice", "Opt_2_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount", "Opt_3_def": "idea or hypothesis", "Opt_4_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "At weddings the speeches usually ____ the food.", "Opt_1": "revive", "Opt_2": "precede", "Opt_3": "stipulate", "Opt_4": "trust", "Answer": "precede", "Opt_1_def": "to bring back (to life)", "Opt_2_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to require", "Opt_4_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The company's ____ plan was to close down only one of their factories. Because of continuing bad sales, however, they were forced to close three of them.", "Opt_1": "smooth", "Opt_2": "adjacent", "Opt_3": "original", "Opt_4": "appropriate", "Answer": "original", "Opt_1_def": "easy, unproblematic", "Opt_2_def": "next to", "Opt_3_def": "the first of its kind", "Opt_4_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Lilly initiated a conversation with Smith in an attempt to resolve the conflict, but Smith did not wish to ____ the issues.", "Opt_1": "discuss", "Opt_2": "share", "Opt_3": "attach", "Opt_4": "adjust", "Answer": "discuss", "Opt_1_def": "to talk about", "Opt_2_def": "to exchange; to give", "Opt_3_def": "to put together with", "Opt_4_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government plans to introduce an ____ for long-term unemployed people to start looking for work again.", "Opt_1": "bulk", "Opt_2": "region", "Opt_3": "incentive", "Opt_4": "desire", "Answer": "incentive", "Opt_1_def": "majority; largest part", "Opt_2_def": "part of a place", "Opt_3_def": "reason to do something", "Opt_4_def": "a want or wish for something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government minister expressed ____ at her thoughtless comment about 'lazy incompetent teachers'.", "Opt_1": "occur", "Opt_2": "block", "Opt_3": "replace", "Opt_4": "regret", "Answer": "regret", "Opt_1_def": "to happen; take place", "Opt_2_def": "to not allow; to stop or prevent", "Opt_3_def": "to put in or take the place of ..", "Opt_4_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Those who will be attending the event should try to make it to the Speedway early to ____ the rush hour traffic.", "Opt_1": "avoid", "Opt_2": "allege", "Opt_3": "multiply", "Opt_4": "establish", "Answer": "avoid", "Opt_1_def": "to not do something or go somewhere", "Opt_2_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_3_def": "to increase greatly", "Opt_4_def": "to begin or set up"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "While you may not admit to political pressure, you must be aware of its almost constant presence; and you must ____ it and be prepared to deal with it.", "Opt_1": "exhaust", "Opt_2": "form", "Opt_3": "recognize", "Opt_4": "infer", "Answer": "recognize", "Opt_1_def": "to use up", "Opt_2_def": "to make (into a shape)", "Opt_3_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)", "Opt_4_def": "to come to a conclusion about something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The Bush administration will not back down on pursuing new sanctions against Iran over its nuclear program ____ questions about their effectiveness.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government has taken the wise decision to ____ the public before passing the proposed law.", "Opt_1": "derive", "Opt_2": "consult", "Opt_3": "overlap", "Opt_4": "request", "Answer": "consult", "Opt_1_def": "to come from or get from", "Opt_2_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_3_def": "to have in common; to cover part of", "Opt_4_def": "to ask politely"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "He mentioned what seemed like a huge sum. It was indeed a huge amount for a ____ that had only a skeleton staff and strained budget.", "Opt_1": "minimum", "Opt_2": "industry", "Opt_3": "friction", "Opt_4": "programme", "Answer": "programme", "Opt_1_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_2_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )", "Opt_3_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups", "Opt_4_def": "a course of lessons; a project"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The police ____ give details of whom they have arrested until they know that the person will be charged with a crime.", "Opt_1": "seldom", "Opt_2": "conversely", "Opt_3": "hardly", "Opt_4": "simultaneously", "Answer": "seldom", "Opt_1_def": "rare", "Opt_2_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand", "Opt_3_def": "not very much", "Opt_4_def": "at the same time"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If he was indeed employed by the Grand Duke, that would account for his ____ behaviour.", "Opt_1": "prime", "Opt_2": "enormous", "Opt_3": "odd", "Opt_4": "preliminary", "Answer": "odd", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "very big", "Opt_3_def": "strange, unusual", "Opt_4_def": "first; initial"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "You can take any book ____ this one. I'm reading it.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Do you ever feel like some Asian traditions ____ the need for communication or being able to freely display your emotions?", "Opt_1": "respect", "Opt_2": "suppress", "Opt_3": "enumerate", "Opt_4": "deduce", "Answer": "suppress", "Opt_1_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something", "Opt_2_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen", "Opt_3_def": "to list", "Opt_4_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "China is able to ____ goods cheaply because labour costs are low.", "Opt_1": "implement", "Opt_2": "manufacture", "Opt_3": "halt", "Opt_4": "protect", "Answer": "manufacture", "Opt_1_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)", "Opt_2_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_3_def": "to stop", "Opt_4_def": "to keep something out of danger"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The village system made it almost impossible to ____ the amount of land available for pasture.", "Opt_1": "dismiss", "Opt_2": "manage", "Opt_3": "enlarge", "Opt_4": "cooperate", "Answer": "enlarge", "Opt_1_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant", "Opt_2_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to make larger", "Opt_4_def": "to work (well) with another person"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The final examination shall be designed to cover a period not to ____ two hours.", "Opt_1": "exaggerate", "Opt_2": "cease", "Opt_3": "inform", "Opt_4": "exceed", "Answer": "exceed", "Opt_1_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_2_def": "to stop", "Opt_3_def": "to say, give information", "Opt_4_def": "to be more than or better than"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government plans to offer ____ parenting classes for young, unemployed couples.", "Opt_1": "global", "Opt_2": "ambiguous", "Opt_3": "substantial", "Opt_4": "optional", "Answer": "optional", "Opt_1_def": "world", "Opt_2_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation", "Opt_3_def": "large", "Opt_4_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government raised taxes, deciding to ____ the loud protests in the media.", "Opt_1": "distort", "Opt_2": "ignore", "Opt_3": "encourage", "Opt_4": "master", "Answer": "ignore", "Opt_1_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)", "Opt_2_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)", "Opt_3_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help", "Opt_4_def": "to (gain) control"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "He was also faced with difficult questions about the university's handling of the emergency and whether it did enough to ____ students.", "Opt_1": "require", "Opt_2": "inhibit", "Opt_3": "identify", "Opt_4": "warn", "Answer": "warn", "Opt_1_def": "to need", "Opt_2_def": "to prevent or stop", "Opt_3_def": "to know or say who or what something is", "Opt_4_def": "to notify (of possible danger)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Through appointments and ____ the President was able to drain the Constitution of much of its meaning, with no public reaction.", "Opt_1": "legislation", "Opt_2": "contrary", "Opt_3": "agent", "Opt_4": "liberty", "Answer": "legislation", "Opt_1_def": "governmental rule; law", "Opt_2_def": "opposite", "Opt_3_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_4_def": "freedom"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Unlike normal children she cannot ____ its ordinary meaning to the word \"blue\", so she cannot fully understand basic sentences.", "Opt_1": "afford", "Opt_2": "reserve", "Opt_3": "propose", "Opt_4": "attach", "Answer": "attach", "Opt_1_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_2_def": "to keep", "Opt_3_def": "to suggest", "Opt_4_def": "to put together with"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "In 1986, 23 percent of parents said obedience was the most important ____ they expected from their children.", "Opt_1": "trait", "Opt_2": "bias", "Opt_3": "component", "Opt_4": "occasion", "Answer": "trait", "Opt_1_def": "characteristic; aspect", "Opt_2_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice", "Opt_3_def": "part of; an element of", "Opt_4_def": "time (opportunity)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Military power is not an appropriate ____ to transform the Middle East.", "Opt_1": "compensation", "Opt_2": "lecture", "Opt_3": "phrase", "Opt_4": "tool", "Answer": "tool", "Opt_1_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_2_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure.", "Opt_4_def": "something used to do a job"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Students will need to ____ a spokesperson to speak for their group and come to an agreement about their decision.", "Opt_1": "contain", "Opt_2": "warn", "Opt_3": "elect", "Opt_4": "settle", "Answer": "elect", "Opt_1_def": "to have in it; to hold inside", "Opt_2_def": "to notify (of possible danger)", "Opt_3_def": "to choose by voting", "Opt_4_def": "to solve a problem or dispute"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It would be easy to overlook important biological information that did not ____ itself in visible symptoms or test results.", "Opt_1": "obtain", "Opt_2": "manifest", "Opt_3": "cooperate", "Opt_4": "succeed", "Answer": "manifest", "Opt_1_def": "to get", "Opt_2_def": "show", "Opt_3_def": "to work (well) with another person", "Opt_4_def": "to do well"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The department may admit students of superior promise but ____ preparation, provided that such students correct their deficiencies.", "Opt_1": "similar", "Opt_2": "deficient", "Opt_3": "crucial", "Opt_4": "passive", "Answer": "deficient", "Opt_1_def": "like, almost the same as", "Opt_2_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality", "Opt_3_def": "extremely important", "Opt_4_def": "not active; unresponsive"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It operated below 60%, was generally poorly designed and therefore not ____ considering.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The combination of natural and human systems adds an additional ____ of complexity to the interactions.", "Opt_1": "exponent", "Opt_2": "layer", "Opt_3": "progress", "Opt_4": "sequence", "Answer": "layer", "Opt_1_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion", "Opt_2_def": "level", "Opt_3_def": "improvement or development", "Opt_4_def": "the order in which things are arranged or happen"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Patients are ____ to forget information that is not written down.", "Opt_1": "capable", "Opt_2": "liable", "Opt_3": "urgent", "Opt_4": "uniform", "Answer": "liable", "Opt_1_def": "able", "Opt_2_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening", "Opt_3_def": "very important, must be done immediately", "Opt_4_def": "having the same qualities"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The Regional Oral History Office has moved to a ____ location.", "Opt_1": "smooth", "Opt_2": "temporary", "Opt_3": "independent", "Opt_4": "novel", "Answer": "temporary", "Opt_1_def": "easy, unproblematic", "Opt_2_def": "for a short or limited time", "Opt_3_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else", "Opt_4_def": "new"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "You need to trust your ____ as to whether he is the right man to marry.", "Opt_1": "route", "Opt_2": "instinct", "Opt_3": "strategy", "Opt_4": "interpretation", "Answer": "instinct", "Opt_1_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing", "Opt_2_def": "natural feeling or reaction", "Opt_3_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_4_def": "explanation; assessment"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "This research study will focus on the current practice of web writers and the ____ of the web pages they create.", "Opt_1": "structure", "Opt_2": "domain", "Opt_3": "range", "Opt_4": "obligation", "Answer": "structure", "Opt_1_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_2_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_3_def": "extent, distance between two points", "Opt_4_def": "a requirement to do something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "One of the earliest uses of coffee was actually as a medicine, although there was also a ____ as to whether it was helpful or harmful.", "Opt_1": "generation", "Opt_2": "priority", "Opt_3": "debate", "Opt_4": "habit", "Answer": "debate", "Opt_1_def": "group of people all born around the same time", "Opt_2_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_3_def": "formal discussion", "Opt_4_def": "something you do regularly"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "After listening to the students' assurance, the ____ decided not to block their plan for a sleepover in the school gym.", "Opt_1": "subsequent", "Opt_2": "entire", "Opt_3": "hostile", "Opt_4": "principal", "Answer": "principal", "Opt_1_def": "next, following", "Opt_2_def": "whole, all", "Opt_3_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The filter must ____ out all but about one part in a million of the light that hits it, and must do so all across the spectrum.", "Opt_1": "threaten", "Opt_2": "block", "Opt_3": "encourage", "Opt_4": "reserve", "Answer": "block", "Opt_1_def": "to warn or show signs of danger", "Opt_2_def": "to not allow; to stop or prevent", "Opt_3_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help", "Opt_4_def": "to keep"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Did anyone ____ to solve question 11?", "Opt_1": "inform", "Opt_2": "remain", "Opt_3": "manage", "Opt_4": "regard", "Answer": "manage", "Opt_1_def": "to say, give information", "Opt_2_def": "to stay; still exist", "Opt_3_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government is finding it difficult to break the ____ of poverty and poor school performance.", "Opt_1": "portion", "Opt_2": "support", "Opt_3": "behalf", "Opt_4": "cycle", "Answer": "cycle", "Opt_1_def": "part, amount", "Opt_2_def": "help", "Opt_3_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of", "Opt_4_def": "a complete series of events or processes"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Visit our Student Support page to see how you can set up a fund to give someone the opportunity to ____ higher education at Michigan Tech.", "Opt_1": "spread", "Opt_2": "pursue", "Opt_3": "verify", "Opt_4": "require", "Answer": "pursue", "Opt_1_def": "to move (over a wider area)", "Opt_2_def": "to follow (or do)", "Opt_3_def": "to prove or claim the truth", "Opt_4_def": "to need"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "This is yet another ____ example of the positive partnership between TMH and the FSU College of Medicine.", "Opt_1": "outstanding", "Opt_2": "urban", "Opt_3": "apparent", "Opt_4": "economic", "Answer": "outstanding", "Opt_1_def": "excellent", "Opt_2_def": "of the town or city", "Opt_3_def": "clear; obvious", "Opt_4_def": "financial; to do with money"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The new government has not yet proved itself ____ of making the right decisions in its foreign policy.", "Opt_1": "deficient", "Opt_2": "abnormal", "Opt_3": "external", "Opt_4": "competent", "Answer": "competent", "Opt_1_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality", "Opt_2_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_3_def": "outside", "Opt_4_def": "good at something (often a job)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "From the quality of the writing I can only ____ that someone helped him. His work is usually nowhere near as good.", "Opt_1": "engage", "Opt_2": "infer", "Opt_3": "degenerate", "Opt_4": "reform", "Answer": "infer", "Opt_1_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on", "Opt_2_def": "to come to a conclusion about something", "Opt_3_def": "to get worse", "Opt_4_def": "to change and improve"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Some people ____ that the reasons for invading Iraq were to gain control of its oil.", "Opt_1": "allege", "Opt_2": "accelerate", "Opt_3": "complicate", "Opt_4": "impose", "Answer": "allege", "Opt_1_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_2_def": "to get or make faster", "Opt_3_def": "to make things more complex or difficult", "Opt_4_def": "to force; to require to happen"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The ____ to a new school in a new country is a difficult one for most students.", "Opt_1": "transition", "Opt_2": "task", "Opt_3": "statistic", "Opt_4": "relationship", "Answer": "transition", "Opt_1_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_2_def": "job", "Opt_3_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_4_def": "the way to things are connected"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Megan Wood said although students were more educated on the issues, many did not vote ____ because they forgot to request an application form.", "Opt_1": "especially", "Opt_2": "definitely", "Opt_3": "hence", "Opt_4": "simply", "Answer": "simply", "Opt_1_def": "particularly", "Opt_2_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_3_def": "so, therefore", "Opt_4_def": "completely; just; only"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "While its lack of clarity was seen by some early critics as a clear ____ of error and confusion, it was seen by others as a hallmark of genius.", "Opt_1": "experiment", "Opt_2": "grant", "Opt_3": "symptom", "Opt_4": "labour", "Answer": "symptom", "Opt_1_def": "test", "Opt_2_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization", "Opt_3_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)", "Opt_4_def": "work"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It is ____ that you hand in the essay on time. If you don't, you will fail the course.", "Opt_1": "absent", "Opt_2": "external", "Opt_3": "crucial", "Opt_4": "inherent", "Answer": "crucial", "Opt_1_def": "being not there; missing", "Opt_2_def": "outside", "Opt_3_def": "extremely important", "Opt_4_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If you ____ a book from Amazon, you usually receive it within a few days.", "Opt_1": "term", "Opt_2": "course", "Opt_3": "obligation", "Opt_4": "order", "Answer": "order", "Opt_1_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_2_def": "a subject or period of study", "Opt_3_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_4_def": "sequence, place"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "He rightly concludes that the end of the Cold War failed to ____ significant changes in the Horn of Africa or to improve the mutual security of states.", "Opt_1": "induce", "Opt_2": "disrupt", "Opt_3": "annotate", "Opt_4": "stress", "Answer": "induce", "Opt_1_def": "to make happen; to force", "Opt_2_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage", "Opt_3_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_4_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The class learns that Alzheimer's disease is a deterioration of cells within the brain that leads to ____ of memory.", "Opt_1": "sector", "Opt_2": "cycle", "Opt_3": "loss", "Opt_4": "situation", "Answer": "loss", "Opt_1_def": "part; area", "Opt_2_def": "a complete series of events or processes", "Opt_3_def": "removal or reduction", "Opt_4_def": "circumstances"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "There was a ____ in the cafeteria at lunch today. The oil for cooking French fries ignited and set fire to the wooden ceiling.", "Opt_1": "obligation", "Opt_2": "crisis", "Opt_3": "effort", "Opt_4": "gain", "Answer": "crisis", "Opt_1_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_2_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe", "Opt_3_def": "hard work; attempt", "Opt_4_def": "to get; to increase in .."}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Science and technology are driving explosive growth in the production of new knowledge, often with the power to ____ profound changes in society.", "Opt_1": "analyze", "Opt_2": "collaborate", "Opt_3": "verify", "Opt_4": "induce", "Answer": "induce", "Opt_1_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it", "Opt_2_def": "to work together", "Opt_3_def": "to prove or claim the truth", "Opt_4_def": "to make happen; to force"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "He came to the conclusion that Mexico's constitutions did not last because they simply did not ____ to Mexico's customs and traditions.", "Opt_1": "adapt", "Opt_2": "amend", "Opt_3": "conform", "Opt_4": "appeal", "Answer": "conform", "Opt_1_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)", "Opt_2_def": "to change (usually to improve something)", "Opt_3_def": "to do what is required", "Opt_4_def": "to complain against an official judgment; to make a strong request"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The priests of this institution did not give their answers by inspiration, but occupied themselves chiefly with the ____ of dreams", "Opt_1": "interpretation", "Opt_2": "impulse", "Opt_3": "minimum", "Opt_4": "policy", "Answer": "interpretation", "Opt_1_def": "explanation; assessment", "Opt_2_def": "reason or motivation to do something", "Opt_3_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_4_def": "formal rules"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Oil is becoming more and more scarce. It is ____ that we find new ways of powering cars and industry.", "Opt_1": "vital", "Opt_2": "moderate", "Opt_3": "rational", "Opt_4": "royal", "Answer": "vital", "Opt_1_def": "very important", "Opt_2_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_3_def": "base on reason, not on emotion or instinct", "Opt_4_def": "of kings and queens"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The police could find no ____ of the girl who was kidnapped from her hotel.", "Opt_1": "materials", "Opt_2": "authority", "Opt_3": "trace", "Opt_4": "error", "Answer": "trace", "Opt_1_def": "the things you need to do something", "Opt_2_def": "control (right to control)", "Opt_3_def": "sign; indication; evidence", "Opt_4_def": "a mistake"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "He was not willing to retreat from previous ____ commitments.", "Opt_1": "legal", "Opt_2": "independent", "Opt_3": "valuable", "Opt_4": "obvious", "Answer": "legal", "Opt_1_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)", "Opt_2_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else", "Opt_3_def": "worth a lot of money; important", "Opt_4_def": "clear, evident"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "To what ____ do you believe that the government has made the right decision?", "Opt_1": "degree", "Opt_2": "sphere", "Opt_3": "bond", "Opt_4": "insight", "Answer": "degree", "Opt_1_def": "amount", "Opt_2_def": "area of interest", "Opt_3_def": "link; tie", "Opt_4_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "When morality comes up against ____, it is seldom ____ that loses.", "Opt_1": "impact", "Opt_2": "insight", "Opt_3": "profit", "Opt_4": "layer", "Answer": "profit", "Opt_1_def": "effect", "Opt_2_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_3_def": "money gained", "Opt_4_def": "level"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Students and non-students alike can be criminally charged if they don't comply with police orders to ____ from riot or crowd situations.", "Opt_1": "disperse", "Opt_2": "allocate", "Opt_3": "interfere", "Opt_4": "harm", "Answer": "disperse", "Opt_1_def": "to spread out; to move apart", "Opt_2_def": "to give to (to promise to give)", "Opt_3_def": "to prevent; to harm", "Opt_4_def": "to damage or injure"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The students ____ that I promised to show a DVD on in class today, but I cannot remember doing so.", "Opt_1": "assert", "Opt_2": "commence", "Opt_3": "offend", "Opt_4": "exceed", "Answer": "assert", "Opt_1_def": "to claim, to say strongly", "Opt_2_def": "to start", "Opt_3_def": "to go against; to upset", "Opt_4_def": "to be more than or better than"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The elders in the village are fighting to retain their people's traditions, but the younger ones want to ____ the modern world of computers and mobile phones.", "Opt_1": "appoint", "Opt_2": "join", "Opt_3": "apply", "Opt_4": "reform", "Answer": "join", "Opt_1_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_2_def": "to become a member (of an organization; to get together with others", "Opt_3_def": "to be relevant (to)", "Opt_4_def": "to change and improve"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "One ____ reason for this persistent problem is that Europe is trailing behind the US in labour productivity growth.", "Opt_1": "fortunate", "Opt_2": "crucial", "Opt_3": "chief", "Opt_4": "apparent", "Answer": "crucial", "Opt_1_def": "lucky", "Opt_2_def": "extremely important", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "clear; obvious"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The ____ of the students' time is spent performing experiments, with required one-on-one mentorship by a graduate student, fellow, or faculty member.", "Opt_1": "bulk", "Opt_2": "amount", "Opt_3": "apparatus", "Opt_4": "process", "Answer": "bulk", "Opt_1_def": "majority; largest part", "Opt_2_def": "how much there is of something", "Opt_3_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job", "Opt_4_def": "a series of steps"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "He both provided a message service and the apparatus needed to send and ____ wireless messages.", "Opt_1": "contact", "Opt_2": "employ", "Opt_3": "assert", "Opt_4": "receive", "Answer": "receive", "Opt_1_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)", "Opt_2_def": "to give a job to someone; to use", "Opt_3_def": "to claim, to say strongly", "Opt_4_def": "to get"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "In addition to paying for the required tuition and fees, you will need to procure a variety of materials to ____ this class.", "Opt_1": "legal", "Opt_2": "constant", "Opt_3": "complete", "Opt_4": "identical", "Answer": "complete", "Opt_1_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)", "Opt_2_def": "not changing; long-lasting", "Opt_3_def": "full or finished", "Opt_4_def": "exactly the same"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Game reasoning is simply moral reasoning that occurs in the context of competitive sports, and ____ elsewhere as well.", "Opt_1": "perhaps", "Opt_2": "indeed", "Opt_3": "nevertheless", "Opt_4": "gradually", "Answer": "perhaps", "Opt_1_def": "maybe, possibly", "Opt_2_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_3_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_4_def": "slowly; steadily"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government's ____ is that the bomb was set off by a recent immigrant.", "Opt_1": "code", "Opt_2": "incentive", "Opt_3": "summary", "Opt_4": "theory", "Answer": "theory", "Opt_1_def": "a set of rules", "Opt_2_def": "reason to do something", "Opt_3_def": "a short account of the most important details", "Opt_4_def": "idea or hypothesis"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Please remember to ____ any rented vehicle before driving it and note any scratches or other damage to the vehicle on the rental form.", "Opt_1": "protest", "Opt_2": "reinforce", "Opt_3": "inspect", "Opt_4": "manipulate", "Answer": "inspect", "Opt_1_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_2_def": "to make something stronger", "Opt_3_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_4_def": "to (use and) change"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Racism and ____ continue to be a major problem in our country.", "Opt_1": "alternative", "Opt_2": "prejudice", "Opt_3": "contrary", "Opt_4": "victory", "Answer": "prejudice", "Opt_1_def": "other possibility", "Opt_2_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background", "Opt_3_def": "opposite", "Opt_4_def": "win"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The school is looking for students who would like to do ____ work at the local old people's home.", "Opt_1": "classic", "Opt_2": "compatible", "Opt_3": "consistent", "Opt_4": "voluntary", "Answer": "voluntary", "Opt_1_def": "very good, the best or most used", "Opt_2_def": "able to work with someone or something else", "Opt_3_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_4_def": "done freely; from personal choice"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The main ____ of the committee is to recommend a plan for future development.", "Opt_1": "objective", "Opt_2": "province", "Opt_3": "theory", "Opt_4": "function", "Answer": "function", "Opt_1_def": "aim or goal", "Opt_2_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_3_def": "idea or hypothesis", "Opt_4_def": "job or role"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Students are encouraged to first exhaust all possibilities for Federal and state financial ____ programs before seeking alternative loans.", "Opt_1": "experiment", "Opt_2": "source", "Opt_3": "aid", "Opt_4": "counsel", "Answer": "aid", "Opt_1_def": "test", "Opt_2_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_3_def": "help (often financial help)", "Opt_4_def": "advice; advisor"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The school is located in the wooded ____ to the north west of Frankfurt.", "Opt_1": "guide", "Opt_2": "substitute", "Opt_3": "reluctance", "Opt_4": "region", "Answer": "region", "Opt_1_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)", "Opt_2_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another", "Opt_3_def": "unwillingness; hesitation", "Opt_4_def": "part of a place"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government will today publish its ____ report on crime statistics.", "Opt_1": "inevitable", "Opt_2": "rare", "Opt_3": "annual", "Opt_4": "comprehensive", "Answer": "annual", "Opt_1_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious", "Opt_2_def": "unusual", "Opt_3_def": "yearly", "Opt_4_def": "full, complete"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "I advise you to ____ more carefully for tests.", "Opt_1": "rotate", "Opt_2": "revive", "Opt_3": "assume", "Opt_4": "prepare", "Answer": "prepare", "Opt_1_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_2_def": "to bring back (to life)", "Opt_3_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict", "Opt_4_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "We had disagreed strongly over politics before, and while these arguments did not ____ our friendship in the least, I wished to avoid potential conflict.", "Opt_1": "strain", "Opt_2": "criticize", "Opt_3": "rotate", "Opt_4": "restrict", "Answer": "strain", "Opt_1_def": "to put under stress or make difficult", "Opt_2_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_4_def": "to limit"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This interesting site offers the student of neuroscience access to an ____ amount of information on the discipline.", "Opt_1": "economic", "Opt_2": "accurate", "Opt_3": "immense", "Opt_4": "invisible", "Answer": "immense", "Opt_1_def": "financial; to do with money", "Opt_2_def": "exact, containing no mistakes", "Opt_3_def": "very large", "Opt_4_def": "cannot be seen"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "He was inspired by the dreams and disappointments of those individual schoolteachers who dared to challenge the ____ and follow their own visions toward a better future.", "Opt_1": "hierarchy", "Opt_2": "statistic", "Opt_3": "doubt", "Opt_4": "criterion", "Answer": "hierarchy", "Opt_1_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_2_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_3_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_4_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Some solutions exist to improve the performance of these devices, but ____ there are limitations how accessible they can be made.", "Opt_1": "indeed", "Opt_2": "thus", "Opt_3": "naturally", "Opt_4": "virtually", "Answer": "naturally", "Opt_1_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_2_def": "so", "Opt_3_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_4_def": "almost"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "These drug companies were ____ negligent in that they failed to warn consumers of the potential dangers associated with the use of their products.", "Opt_1": "absolutely", "Opt_2": "thus", "Opt_3": "extremely", "Opt_4": "namely", "Answer": "extremely", "Opt_1_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_2_def": "so", "Opt_3_def": "very", "Opt_4_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The Information Technology Committee has voted in favor of the ____ of requiring all incoming freshmen to have a computer.", "Opt_1": "principle", "Opt_2": "sample", "Opt_3": "feature", "Opt_4": "shortage", "Answer": "principle", "Opt_1_def": "rule", "Opt_2_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection", "Opt_3_def": "part, aspect", "Opt_4_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "In many cases print journals are disappearing as librarians strive to ____ money and shelf space.", "Opt_1": "block", "Opt_2": "collaborate", "Opt_3": "conserve", "Opt_4": "commence", "Answer": "conserve", "Opt_1_def": "to not allow; to stop or prevent", "Opt_2_def": "to work together", "Opt_3_def": "to preserve; to not use", "Opt_4_def": "to start"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The school had similar exam results to last year, with the ____ion ____ that mathematics scores were a little higher.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Recent government IT initiatives focus narrowly on a specific technical problem, like enabling ____ data communication or Web-based transactions.", "Opt_1": "similar", "Opt_2": "utter", "Opt_3": "mobile", "Opt_4": "urban", "Answer": "mobile", "Opt_1_def": "like, almost the same as", "Opt_2_def": "complete, total", "Opt_3_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_4_def": "of the town or city"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "You are recommended to record every ____ detail about each of your customers.", "Opt_1": "main", "Opt_2": "dynamic", "Opt_3": "drastic", "Opt_4": "significant", "Answer": "significant", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "changing; growing; energetic", "Opt_3_def": "severe; great", "Opt_4_def": "important, large"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The need for regulation is quite ____ today but was not apparent before the early years of the 20th century.", "Opt_1": "evident", "Opt_2": "commercial", "Opt_3": "overall", "Opt_4": "complex", "Answer": "evident", "Opt_1_def": "clear", "Opt_2_def": "to do with business", "Opt_3_def": "general", "Opt_4_def": "difficult, complicated"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Give me a ____ explanation of how the accident happened.", "Opt_1": "brief", "Opt_2": "common", "Opt_3": "contemporary", "Opt_4": "previous", "Answer": "brief", "Opt_1_def": "short", "Opt_2_def": "often seen or happening", "Opt_3_def": "of this time, happening now", "Opt_4_def": "the one before"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "While its lack of clarity was seen by some early critics as a clear symptom of ____ and confusion, it was seen by others as a hallmark of genius.", "Opt_1": "administration", "Opt_2": "error", "Opt_3": "point", "Opt_4": "guide", "Answer": "error", "Opt_1_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_2_def": "a mistake", "Opt_3_def": "purpose; reason; value", "Opt_4_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is possible this information was ignored because it was not ____ or because it was simply unavailable.", "Opt_1": "abnormal", "Opt_2": "positive", "Opt_3": "constant", "Opt_4": "capable", "Answer": "positive", "Opt_1_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_2_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_3_def": "not changing; long-lasting", "Opt_4_def": "able"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If the individual knows in advance when he or she wishes to apply for time away from the workplace, the individual should complete the preliminary ____ form.", "Opt_1": "request", "Opt_2": "confine", "Opt_3": "engage", "Opt_4": "produce", "Answer": "request", "Opt_1_def": "to ask politely", "Opt_2_def": "to limit", "Opt_3_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on", "Opt_4_def": "to make or create"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Some animals, such as the tortoise or snail, have an ____ shell rather than an internal skeleton.", "Opt_1": "external", "Opt_2": "prime", "Opt_3": "moderate", "Opt_4": "basic", "Answer": "external", "Opt_1_def": "outside", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_4_def": "first or easy"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The two procedures consistently showed that garlic did not ____ the growth of oral bacteria.", "Opt_1": "entitle", "Opt_2": "consult", "Opt_3": "exchange", "Opt_4": "inhibit", "Answer": "inhibit", "Opt_1_def": "to give the right to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_3_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing", "Opt_4_def": "to prevent or stop"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "TOEFL is not the most ____ part of the application, but it is an unavoidable part, which sometimes can be quite painful and time- consuming.", "Opt_1": "hostile", "Opt_2": "various", "Opt_3": "crucial", "Opt_4": "several", "Answer": "crucial", "Opt_1_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to", "Opt_2_def": "several, of different kinds", "Opt_3_def": "extremely important", "Opt_4_def": "many (about 6 or seven)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Our experience is that small businesses (especially those newly formed) tend to ____ unrealistically low indirect costs.", "Opt_1": "propose", "Opt_2": "publish", "Opt_3": "fluctuate", "Opt_4": "inform", "Answer": "propose", "Opt_1_def": "to suggest", "Opt_2_def": "to make available in paper or online form", "Opt_3_def": "to vary; to rise and fall", "Opt_4_def": "to say, give information"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "He has lost the ____ of being himself. Immigration laws have required him to pretend to be somebody else.", "Opt_1": "contrast", "Opt_2": "description", "Opt_3": "privilege", "Opt_4": "desire", "Answer": "privilege", "Opt_1_def": "difference", "Opt_2_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like", "Opt_3_def": "a right (to do something)", "Opt_4_def": "a want or wish for something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "From my perspective as a teacher and parent, I would say that her difficulties in school are ____ to problems at home.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Each year the school has to import many of its textbooks from the USA or England-Germany needs to import more qualified computer technicians. It has failed to ____ enough of its own.", "Opt_1": "add", "Opt_2": "claim", "Opt_3": "train", "Opt_4": "propose", "Answer": "train", "Opt_1_def": "to include; to give or say extra", "Opt_2_def": "to state to be true", "Opt_3_def": "to teach someone how to do a job", "Opt_4_def": "to suggest"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The writer Emile Zola exposed the ____ to the general public in the literary newspaper L'Aurore (The Dawn) in a famous open letter to the President.", "Opt_1": "episode", "Opt_2": "affair", "Opt_3": "incident", "Opt_4": "objection", "Answer": "affair", "Opt_1_def": "period of time", "Opt_2_def": "an event or series of events", "Opt_3_def": "happening; event", "Opt_4_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "You can't always control what happens to you, but you can always control how you ____ to what happens to you.", "Opt_1": "react", "Opt_2": "forego", "Opt_3": "contemplate", "Opt_4": "retreat", "Answer": "react", "Opt_1_def": "to respond", "Opt_2_def": "to do without; to give up", "Opt_3_def": "to think about; to consider", "Opt_4_def": "to go back"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It is no coincidence that the early proponents of so-called ____ education were socialists.", "Opt_1": "public", "Opt_2": "perpetual", "Opt_3": "significant", "Opt_4": "independent", "Answer": "public", "Opt_1_def": "open to all; not private", "Opt_2_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing", "Opt_3_def": "important, large", "Opt_4_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It is not in employers' interest to get rid of cheap illegal immigrants - only to ____ them of any rights.", "Opt_1": "deprive", "Opt_2": "distribute", "Opt_3": "view", "Opt_4": "reform", "Answer": "deprive", "Opt_1_def": "to take away (the opportunity)", "Opt_2_def": "to give out", "Opt_3_def": "to have an opinion", "Opt_4_def": "to change and improve"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Frankfurt International School has attracted many more German students recently. My ____ is that parents are not happy with the education their children are getting in German public schools.", "Opt_1": "duration", "Opt_2": "debt", "Opt_3": "priority", "Opt_4": "hypothesis", "Answer": "hypothesis", "Opt_1_def": "period of time", "Opt_2_def": "something owed to another person (often money)", "Opt_3_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_4_def": "idea or prediction"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Typically held the 3rd week of February, this is an ____ event that helps College of Fine Arts students explore careers, develop strategies to pursue career and artistic goals successfully.", "Opt_1": "crucial", "Opt_2": "subjective", "Opt_3": "annual", "Opt_4": "temporary", "Answer": "annual", "Opt_1_def": "extremely important", "Opt_2_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_3_def": "yearly", "Opt_4_def": "for a short or limited time"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "A half century ago the conflict over ____ regulation of railroads was the chief issue in Alabama politics.", "Opt_1": "tool", "Opt_2": "state", "Opt_3": "profession", "Opt_4": "diagnosis", "Answer": "state", "Opt_1_def": "something used to do a job", "Opt_2_def": "condition, situation", "Opt_3_def": "job; occupation", "Opt_4_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "You are ____ of much better grades if you make more effort.", "Opt_1": "compulsory", "Opt_2": "annual", "Opt_3": "capable", "Opt_4": "rational", "Answer": "capable", "Opt_1_def": "required, must be done", "Opt_2_def": "yearly", "Opt_3_def": "able", "Opt_4_def": "base on reason, not on emotion or instinct"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Teachers did not migrate because of students behaving badly but ____ because student behavior was not adequately managed.", "Opt_1": "furthermore", "Opt_2": "occasionally", "Opt_3": "rather", "Opt_4": "eventually", "Answer": "rather", "Opt_1_def": "also, in addition", "Opt_2_def": "sometimes", "Opt_3_def": "instead", "Opt_4_def": "in the end"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Although two weeks are dedicated to its development at the end of the semester you should not ____ that this is enough time for the entire project.", "Opt_1": "compile", "Opt_2": "contradict", "Opt_3": "culminate", "Opt_4": "conclude", "Answer": "conclude", "Opt_1_def": "to put together (often in a list", "Opt_2_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_3_def": "to end", "Opt_4_def": "to finish; to make a judgment"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "You will need to explain your ____ as clearly as possible and provide appropriate supporting documentation.", "Opt_1": "authority", "Opt_2": "situation", "Opt_3": "context", "Opt_4": "guarantee", "Answer": "situation", "Opt_1_def": "control (right to control)", "Opt_2_def": "circumstances", "Opt_3_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_4_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "After the deadline, you will need to negotiate an extension with the TA ____ such cases, before taking it up with the professor.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Although his letter did not stipulate Atlanta as the ____ of the new school, the Educational Commission quickly decided the matter.", "Opt_1": "location", "Opt_2": "phenomenon", "Opt_3": "insight", "Opt_4": "sum", "Answer": "location", "Opt_1_def": "place, where something or someone is", "Opt_2_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)", "Opt_3_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_4_def": "an amount of money, total"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "She chose to reject the ____ that there is an increased risk of having a second child with the same disorder.", "Opt_1": "hypothesis", "Opt_2": "shortage", "Opt_3": "situation", "Opt_4": "anomaly", "Answer": "hypothesis", "Opt_1_def": "idea or prediction", "Opt_2_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed", "Opt_3_def": "circumstances", "Opt_4_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It seems natural that we would want to employ nurses from overseas; after all we ____ everything else.", "Opt_1": "amend", "Opt_2": "evolve", "Opt_3": "import", "Opt_4": "improve", "Answer": "import", "Opt_1_def": "to change (usually to improve something)", "Opt_2_def": "to develop (into something better)", "Opt_3_def": "to bring in (to a country)", "Opt_4_def": "to get better"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It is a ____ that Japanese girls are quiet. You should hear them on the bus on a school trip!", "Opt_1": "quality", "Opt_2": "stereotype", "Opt_3": "quantity", "Opt_4": "statistic", "Answer": "stereotype", "Opt_1_def": "worth or value", "Opt_2_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "mathematical number"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The final topic presents the ____ of traditional, sometimes outdated, teaching methods and their effect on the participants' learning.", "Opt_1": "statistic", "Opt_2": "impact", "Opt_3": "forecast", "Opt_4": "rise", "Answer": "impact", "Opt_1_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_2_def": "effect", "Opt_3_def": "prediction", "Opt_4_def": "to go up"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The school wanted to raise money from its ex-students, but the attempt was an ____ failure.", "Opt_1": "adjacent", "Opt_2": "utter", "Opt_3": "convenient", "Opt_4": "actual", "Answer": "utter", "Opt_1_def": "next to", "Opt_2_def": "complete, total", "Opt_3_def": "easy, not causing problems", "Opt_4_def": "real"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Mr. Elliott was at fault for delegating that ____ to a person who lacked the experience to perform the job properly.", "Opt_1": "comment", "Opt_2": "trait", "Opt_3": "function", "Opt_4": "programme", "Answer": "function", "Opt_1_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion", "Opt_2_def": "characteristic; aspect", "Opt_3_def": "job or role", "Opt_4_def": "a course of lessons; a project"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The human mind cannot ____ the true nature of God, nor can the angels.", "Opt_1": "replace", "Opt_2": "predict", "Opt_3": "comprehend", "Opt_4": "incorporate", "Answer": "comprehend", "Opt_1_def": "to put in or take the place of ..", "Opt_2_def": "to say what will happen in the future", "Opt_3_def": "to understand", "Opt_4_def": "to include"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The Internet is an extremely useful ____ to look for housing, shops, restaurants, etc.", "Opt_1": "gap", "Opt_2": "tool", "Opt_3": "expert", "Opt_4": "anomaly", "Answer": "tool", "Opt_1_def": "space, opening or time between", "Opt_2_def": "something used to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_4_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Buying a lunch ticket in ____ will entitle you to a free drink.", "Opt_1": "advance", "Opt_2": "culminate", "Opt_3": "isolate", "Opt_4": "consume", "Answer": "advance", "Opt_1_def": "to go or move forward; to get better", "Opt_2_def": "to end", "Opt_3_def": "to separate something or someone from others", "Opt_4_def": "to use, or use up"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "We do not ____ a unilateral ban on cosmetic testing on animals, nor do we reject the use of animals in biomedical research.", "Opt_1": "lessen", "Opt_2": "contribute", "Opt_3": "assemble", "Opt_4": "advocate", "Answer": "advocate", "Opt_1_def": "to reduce", "Opt_2_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_3_def": "to get, put or bring together", "Opt_4_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The Roman Jewish population did not ____ during Sixtus' reign; indeed, there was always movement of Jews in and out of the region.", "Opt_1": "shrink", "Opt_2": "collaborate", "Opt_3": "approach", "Opt_4": "modify", "Answer": "shrink", "Opt_1_def": "to get smaller", "Opt_2_def": "to work together", "Opt_3_def": "to near; to get closer", "Opt_4_def": "to change"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The current timing left the ____ with only one working week to review the applications.", "Opt_1": "policy", "Opt_2": "structure", "Opt_3": "attribute", "Opt_4": "committee", "Answer": "committee", "Opt_1_def": "formal rules", "Opt_2_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_3_def": "characteristic; property", "Opt_4_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Al Gore absolutely did not deserve the Nobel peace prize. On a personal level, he has not reduced his ____ carbon dioxide emissions.", "Opt_1": "inquire", "Opt_2": "own", "Opt_3": "comprehend", "Opt_4": "promote", "Answer": "own", "Opt_1_def": "to ask", "Opt_2_def": "to have or possess", "Opt_3_def": "to understand", "Opt_4_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "You should not ____ that the test questions this semester will be on the same topics.", "Opt_1": "circulate", "Opt_2": "attempt", "Opt_3": "preserve", "Opt_4": "assume", "Answer": "assume", "Opt_1_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)", "Opt_2_def": "to try", "Opt_3_def": "forward,\" said Michele Gougeon.", "Opt_4_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "To launch the project, a special event will ____ at Stanford University's Center for Design Research at 11am today.", "Opt_1": "commence", "Opt_2": "evaluate", "Opt_3": "compile", "Opt_4": "blame", "Answer": "commence", "Opt_1_def": "to start", "Opt_2_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something", "Opt_3_def": "to put together (often in a list", "Opt_4_def": "to accuse"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "For the second meeting of the Forum, we have arranged a debate between two legal professionals who must ____ with the death penalty regularly.", "Opt_1": "struggle", "Opt_2": "deal", "Opt_3": "administration", "Opt_4": "schedule", "Answer": "struggle", "Opt_1_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_2_def": "agreement", "Opt_3_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_4_def": "timetable"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "They sit there in every meeting but they never ____ their own ideas.", "Opt_1": "contribute", "Opt_2": "identify", "Opt_3": "manage", "Opt_4": "descend", "Answer": "contribute", "Opt_1_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_2_def": "to know or say who or what something is", "Opt_3_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to go down"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "We need to devise a test to ____ the improvement in ESL students' English from one year to the next.", "Opt_1": "create", "Opt_2": "warn", "Opt_3": "measure", "Opt_4": "align", "Answer": "measure", "Opt_1_def": "to make; to use your imagination to make something new", "Opt_2_def": "to notify (of possible danger)", "Opt_3_def": "to find out how much there is of something", "Opt_4_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "This is a controversial ____ that will generate much debate in the classroom, mainly among graduate students.", "Opt_1": "anomaly", "Opt_2": "point", "Opt_3": "evidence", "Opt_4": "substitute", "Answer": "point", "Opt_1_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data", "Opt_2_def": "purpose; reason; value", "Opt_3_def": "proof, signs", "Opt_4_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "In the mid-1930s, when she was back at Vogue as fashion editor, Nast declined to ____ her to editor of the magazine, once again because of the morality issue.", "Opt_1": "measure", "Opt_2": "promote", "Opt_3": "shrink", "Opt_4": "contact", "Answer": "promote", "Opt_1_def": "to find out how much there is of something", "Opt_2_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller", "Opt_4_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Every employee must submit an annual tax declaration to his or her ____ tax office.", "Opt_1": "annual", "Opt_2": "invisible", "Opt_3": "local", "Opt_4": "major", "Answer": "local", "Opt_1_def": "yearly", "Opt_2_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_3_def": "in the area where you live or work", "Opt_4_def": "important, large"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It was given to the grandmother by her grandfather in 1852, when the ____ was a member of the California assembly.", "Opt_1": "practical", "Opt_2": "rigid", "Opt_3": "latter", "Opt_4": "supplementary", "Answer": "latter", "Opt_1_def": "useful; possible", "Opt_2_def": "strict, unbending", "Opt_3_def": "the second of two things mentioned", "Opt_4_def": "extra; additional"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Doctors have not been able to establish the ____ cause of the patient's illness.", "Opt_1": "concise", "Opt_2": "elaborate", "Opt_3": "diverse", "Opt_4": "precise", "Answer": "precise", "Opt_1_def": "short, not detailed", "Opt_2_def": "detailed; complex", "Opt_3_def": "many and different", "Opt_4_def": "exact"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If we want this plan to be a success, we need to ____ our resources very carefully.", "Opt_1": "transmit", "Opt_2": "seek", "Opt_3": "facilitate", "Opt_4": "coordinate", "Answer": "coordinate", "Opt_1_def": "to send or convey", "Opt_2_def": "to look for or want", "Opt_3_def": "to make something easier", "Opt_4_def": "to bring things or people together so that they work well"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Since the human body is not an object that can be disposed of at will, the results of research should be made ____ to the whole scientific community.", "Opt_1": "available", "Opt_2": "main", "Opt_3": "typical", "Opt_4": "original", "Answer": "available", "Opt_1_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "usual", "Opt_4_def": "the first of its kind"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government reports a ____ decrease in unemployment in the last month.", "Opt_1": "reliable", "Opt_2": "complex", "Opt_3": "slight", "Opt_4": "likely", "Answer": "slight", "Opt_1_def": "can be trusted, does not let you down \r\n", "Opt_2_def": "difficult, complicated", "Opt_3_def": "small", "Opt_4_def": "probable"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "There is a ____ of meaning in the story that you have not written about.", "Opt_1": "layer", "Opt_2": "truth", "Opt_3": "materials", "Opt_4": "demand", "Answer": "layer", "Opt_1_def": "level", "Opt_2_def": "actual reason or fact", "Opt_3_def": "the things you need to do something", "Opt_4_def": "a need or desire for"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Science should be about objective facts, not ____ opinions.", "Opt_1": "competent", "Opt_2": "confident", "Opt_3": "diverse", "Opt_4": "subjective", "Answer": "subjective", "Opt_1_def": "good at something (often a job)", "Opt_2_def": "sure that something will happen", "Opt_3_def": "many and different", "Opt_4_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Iraq is ____ in a state of civil war.", "Opt_1": "barely", "Opt_2": "naturally", "Opt_3": "virtually", "Opt_4": "seldom", "Answer": "virtually", "Opt_1_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_2_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_3_def": "almost", "Opt_4_def": "rare"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Parents have ____ over their children until the children leave home.", "Opt_1": "authority", "Opt_2": "device", "Opt_3": "cause", "Opt_4": "component", "Answer": "authority", "Opt_1_def": "control (right to control)", "Opt_2_def": "object; method", "Opt_3_def": "the reason why something happens", "Opt_4_def": "part of; an element of"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "All of those guidelines put together would make it nearly impossible to ____ a piece of art or literature.", "Opt_1": "embody", "Opt_2": "adapt", "Opt_3": "supervise", "Opt_4": "judge", "Answer": "judge", "Opt_1_def": "to be a good example of ..", "Opt_2_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)", "Opt_3_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something", "Opt_4_def": "to give an opinion about someone or something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Do you have a ____ pencil? I forgot to bring mine.", "Opt_1": "preliminary", "Opt_2": "domestic", "Opt_3": "spare", "Opt_4": "pure", "Answer": "spare", "Opt_1_def": "first; initial", "Opt_2_def": "home", "Opt_3_def": "not needed", "Opt_4_def": "complete, 100%"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "He reminds us that ____ teaching methods are part of coming of age in the world of the Japanese performing arts.", "Opt_1": "consistent", "Opt_2": "averse", "Opt_3": "prime", "Opt_4": "harsh", "Answer": "harsh", "Opt_1_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_2_def": "against", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "hard, unfair"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "My ESL teacher has the ____ to talk about his own school days.", "Opt_1": "trend", "Opt_2": "implication", "Opt_3": "propensity", "Opt_4": "skill", "Answer": "propensity", "Opt_1_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "result or consequence", "Opt_3_def": "tendency; desire", "Opt_4_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It is important that the government does not ____ significantly from what it promised during the elections.", "Opt_1": "depart", "Opt_2": "conceal", "Opt_3": "retain", "Opt_4": "specify", "Answer": "depart", "Opt_1_def": "to leave; to be different from", "Opt_2_def": "to hide", "Opt_3_def": "to keep", "Opt_4_def": "to state exactly"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government failed to recognize the ____ of the public's unhappiness with the new law.", "Opt_1": "consequence", "Opt_2": "feature", "Opt_3": "dimension", "Opt_4": "magnitude", "Answer": "dimension", "Opt_1_def": "result", "Opt_2_def": "part, aspect", "Opt_3_def": "importance; amount", "Opt_4_def": "size; amount"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "A popular kind of literature these days is about the lives of ordinary people who are caught up in ____ events such as war or terrorism.", "Opt_1": "neutral", "Opt_2": "extraordinary", "Opt_3": "various", "Opt_4": "radical", "Answer": "extraordinary", "Opt_1_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative", "Opt_2_def": "very unusual", "Opt_3_def": "several, of different kinds", "Opt_4_def": "extreme, strong"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Many of these strategies have already been adopted by the ____ airlines, which operate in an intensely competitive environment.", "Opt_1": "vast", "Opt_2": "immediate", "Opt_3": "remote", "Opt_4": "commercial", "Answer": "commercial", "Opt_1_def": "very large", "Opt_2_def": "first (without delay)", "Opt_3_def": "far, distant, small", "Opt_4_def": "to do with business"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Even though the right hemisphere could not ____ to observers what stimuli it had been presented with, it did show some verbal comprehension.", "Opt_1": "communicate", "Opt_2": "participate", "Opt_3": "modify", "Opt_4": "ignore", "Answer": "communicate", "Opt_1_def": "to convey information", "Opt_2_def": "to take part", "Opt_3_def": "to change", "Opt_4_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "We will not ____ unless some of you not only believe in the Constitution, but are willing to engage in public service.", "Opt_1": "override", "Opt_2": "dictate", "Opt_3": "realize", "Opt_4": "prevail", "Answer": "prevail", "Opt_1_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard", "Opt_2_def": "to tell someone what to do", "Opt_3_def": "to come to know or understand", "Opt_4_def": "to succeed; to overcome"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "She very ____ comes late to class. I hope there is nothing wrong.", "Opt_1": "seldom", "Opt_2": "thus", "Opt_3": "universally", "Opt_4": "naturally", "Answer": "seldom", "Opt_1_def": "rare", "Opt_2_def": "so", "Opt_3_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_4_def": "of course, obviously"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "These two-word verbs present one other problem, ____ not appearing as separate entries in the dictionary.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Some people suspect that the US government knew in advance about the terrorist ____ on the Twin Towers in New York.", "Opt_1": "trace", "Opt_2": "account", "Opt_3": "attack", "Opt_4": "margin", "Answer": "attack", "Opt_1_def": "sign; indication; evidence", "Opt_2_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_3_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage", "Opt_4_def": "amount; distance"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Arming the Bosnian Serbs was regarded as a political ____ than a military issue.", "Opt_1": "rather", "Opt_2": "definitely", "Opt_3": "merely", "Opt_4": "largely", "Answer": "rather", "Opt_1_def": "instead", "Opt_2_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_3_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_4_def": "mostly"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Her frequent absence from school is the ____ reason for her bad grades in the final exams.", "Opt_1": "principal", "Opt_2": "uniform", "Opt_3": "sound", "Opt_4": "frequent", "Answer": "principal", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_3_def": "good; strong", "Opt_4_def": "often"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "A major factor in our ____ is how long it will take.", "Opt_1": "struggle", "Opt_2": "decision", "Opt_3": "background", "Opt_4": "individual", "Answer": "decision", "Opt_1_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_2_def": "intention to do something, choice", "Opt_3_def": "family experiences; circumstances", "Opt_4_def": "one person"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The main reason for not responding to terrorism was not an external issue, but an internal one: the government failed to ____ its duties.", "Opt_1": "fulfill", "Opt_2": "base", "Opt_3": "analyze", "Opt_4": "emphasize", "Answer": "fulfill", "Opt_1_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_2_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_3_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it", "Opt_4_def": "to stress, to say something strongly"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "A thought- provoking ____ suggests we should expect the extinction of intelligent life on Earth soon.", "Opt_1": "category", "Opt_2": "speed", "Opt_3": "obstacle", "Opt_4": "argument", "Answer": "argument", "Opt_1_def": "group of similar items", "Opt_2_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_3_def": "barrier; problem", "Opt_4_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Why, Graeme Newman asks, has reform after reform failed to ____ the spread of crime?", "Opt_1": "modify", "Opt_2": "assemble", "Opt_3": "contribute", "Opt_4": "halt", "Answer": "halt", "Opt_1_def": "to change", "Opt_2_def": "to get, put or bring together", "Opt_3_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_4_def": "to stop"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Most students are ____ about the suggestion to replace the blackboards with whiteboards.", "Opt_1": "neutral", "Opt_2": "previous", "Opt_3": "permanent", "Opt_4": "remote", "Answer": "neutral", "Opt_1_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative", "Opt_2_def": "the one before", "Opt_3_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time", "Opt_4_def": "far, distant, small"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government cannot afford to be ____ about the numbers of young people who fail to find any kind of employment.", "Opt_1": "proper", "Opt_2": "military", "Opt_3": "passive", "Opt_4": "related", "Answer": "passive", "Opt_1_def": "correct, appropriate", "Opt_2_def": "to do with army", "Opt_3_def": "not active; unresponsive", "Opt_4_def": "connected; having something to do with each other"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It's not ____ asking him. He doesn't know enough about computers.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The only ____ of having computers in the classroom is that they are loud and make the room hot.", "Opt_1": "series", "Opt_2": "gap", "Opt_3": "sum", "Opt_4": "drawback", "Answer": "drawback", "Opt_1_def": "a number of things, one after the other", "Opt_2_def": "space, opening or time between", "Opt_3_def": "an amount of money, total", "Opt_4_def": "disadvantage, problem"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The additional time is necessary to ____ him to make a sound decision on an Alaska natural gas transportation system.", "Opt_1": "indicate", "Opt_2": "overlap", "Opt_3": "enable", "Opt_4": "specify", "Answer": "enable", "Opt_1_def": "to show or convey", "Opt_2_def": "to have in common; to cover part of", "Opt_3_def": "to make something or someone able to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to state exactly"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "One of the major goals of Women's Studies over the past 25 years has been to ____ the work of women writers from past times.", "Opt_1": "modify", "Opt_2": "imply", "Opt_3": "recover", "Opt_4": "attract", "Answer": "recover", "Opt_1_def": "to change", "Opt_2_def": "to mean; to give to understand", "Opt_3_def": "to get back", "Opt_4_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Curiously absent from the report is any mention of the type of action that the State would have taken ____ the diverse sources of TCE.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The Board may presume that those actions created a hostile or abusive work ____ which harms the efficiency of the service.", "Opt_1": "context", "Opt_2": "environment", "Opt_3": "display", "Opt_4": "demand", "Answer": "environment", "Opt_1_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_2_def": "the world around us", "Opt_3_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration", "Opt_4_def": "a need or desire for"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "To remain eligible for financial aid, recipients are required to show satisfactory ____ toward a degree according to the guidelines listed below.", "Opt_1": "progress", "Opt_2": "sample", "Opt_3": "property", "Opt_4": "task", "Answer": "progress", "Opt_1_def": "improvement or development", "Opt_2_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection", "Opt_3_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home", "Opt_4_def": "job"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Looking up all the key words in an important ____ should be considered a background check for all literary analysis.", "Opt_1": "defeat", "Opt_2": "revolution", "Opt_3": "extent", "Opt_4": "passage", "Answer": "passage", "Opt_1_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)", "Opt_2_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_3_def": "size, amount", "Opt_4_def": "a piece of written or spoken text"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Howard has many chances to ____ into a better father and husband, but he fails to do so.", "Opt_1": "attain", "Opt_2": "behave", "Opt_3": "discuss", "Opt_4": "evolve", "Answer": "evolve", "Opt_1_def": "to get, achieve", "Opt_2_def": "to act or do things in a certain way", "Opt_3_def": "to talk about", "Opt_4_def": "to develop (into something better)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The course will ____ the knowledge base regarding the finance of community education programs.", "Opt_1": "claim", "Opt_2": "cease", "Opt_3": "develop", "Opt_4": "insert", "Answer": "develop", "Opt_1_def": "to state to be true", "Opt_2_def": "to stop", "Opt_3_def": "to grow or improve", "Opt_4_def": "to put in"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "With regret, we have had to cancel the upcoming program on \"The Nervous System\" ____ to an unavoidable change in schedules.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Many undergraduates have little ____ in organizing tasks and making good use of time.", "Opt_1": "opinion", "Opt_2": "experience", "Opt_3": "status", "Opt_4": "environment", "Answer": "experience", "Opt_1_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_3_def": "position, standing", "Opt_4_def": "the world around us"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The explanation for this ____ decision lies in the immediate circumstances surrounding the creation of the United Nations.", "Opt_1": "entire", "Opt_2": "medium", "Opt_3": "extraordinary", "Opt_4": "substantial", "Answer": "extraordinary", "Opt_1_def": "whole, all", "Opt_2_def": "in the middle", "Opt_3_def": "very unusual", "Opt_4_def": "large"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "However, continuous and systematic research on the ____ did not emerge until after World War II.", "Opt_1": "alternative", "Opt_2": "series", "Opt_3": "disaster", "Opt_4": "term", "Answer": "disaster", "Opt_1_def": "other possibility", "Opt_2_def": "a number of things, one after the other", "Opt_3_def": "a huge problem or failure", "Opt_4_def": "a word or expression"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Your supervisor has been provided with the above information and should be able to ____ any questions you may have.", "Opt_1": "accompany", "Opt_2": "consider", "Opt_3": "entitle", "Opt_4": "clarify", "Answer": "clarify", "Opt_1_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together", "Opt_2_def": "to think", "Opt_3_def": "to give the right to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to make something clear, explain"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Why have these countries failed to develop ____ receiving billions of dollars in assistance?", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The ____ of this study is to determine whether antioxidants (Vitamins C and E) reduce the frequency of serious illness.", "Opt_1": "legislation", "Opt_2": "drawback", "Opt_3": "battle", "Opt_4": "purpose", "Answer": "purpose", "Opt_1_def": "governmental rule; law", "Opt_2_def": "disadvantage, problem", "Opt_3_def": "fight, part of a war", "Opt_4_def": "reason, goal"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "We ____ outside counsel to work on particular matters when considerations such as cost and highly specialized subject matter make it appropriate to do so.", "Opt_1": "ignore", "Opt_2": "engage", "Opt_3": "reduce", "Opt_4": "review", "Answer": "engage", "Opt_1_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)", "Opt_2_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on", "Opt_3_def": "to make smaller or shorter", "Opt_4_def": "to check over (and make changes)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "She began to ____ that being overlooked by her supervisor was not a temporary problem.", "Opt_1": "notice", "Opt_2": "sustain", "Opt_3": "survive", "Opt_4": "remove", "Answer": "notice", "Opt_1_def": "to see or realize", "Opt_2_def": "to keep going; to maintain", "Opt_3_def": "to not die", "Opt_4_def": "to take away"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Dairy farmers have led the latest in a long series of protests by agricultural associations, ____ the record high prices for farm products.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The ____ of weight change through pregnancy was similar across the 3 projects.", "Opt_1": "notion", "Opt_2": "pattern", "Opt_3": "location", "Opt_4": "victory", "Answer": "pattern", "Opt_1_def": "idea; concept", "Opt_2_def": "clear and consistent behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "place, where something or someone is", "Opt_4_def": "win"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The Bible laid down some rules for the humane ____ of slaves but did not condemn the practice.", "Opt_1": "treatment", "Opt_2": "substitute", "Opt_3": "district", "Opt_4": "ignorance", "Answer": "treatment", "Opt_1_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)", "Opt_2_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another", "Opt_3_def": "region of a city", "Opt_4_def": "lack of knowledge"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The ____ between the workers and the management improved when flexible working time was introduced.", "Opt_1": "asset", "Opt_2": "implication", "Opt_3": "atmosphere", "Opt_4": "bias", "Answer": "atmosphere", "Opt_1_def": "advantage", "Opt_2_def": "result or consequence", "Opt_3_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_4_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Students need to inquire with the department offering the master's degree to ____ the correct credential courses are taken.", "Opt_1": "ensure", "Opt_2": "consider", "Opt_3": "yield", "Opt_4": "dismiss", "Answer": "ensure", "Opt_1_def": "to make sure (of)", "Opt_2_def": "to think", "Opt_3_def": "to produce", "Opt_4_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government is planning to spend a ____ amount of money on new hospitals next year.", "Opt_1": "essential", "Opt_2": "strict", "Opt_3": "substantial", "Opt_4": "ordinary", "Answer": "substantial", "Opt_1_def": "very important", "Opt_2_def": "hard, not changeable", "Opt_3_def": "large", "Opt_4_def": "usual, typical, every day"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "All children below the age of 16 have the obligation to ____ school.", "Opt_1": "convince", "Opt_2": "descend", "Opt_3": "procure", "Opt_4": "attend", "Answer": "attend", "Opt_1_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something", "Opt_2_def": "to go down", "Opt_3_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_4_def": "to go to, to be present at"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The department must ensure that all students and faculty members have access to a ____ range of learning resources.", "Opt_1": "smooth", "Opt_2": "essential", "Opt_3": "preliminary", "Opt_4": "broad", "Answer": "broad", "Opt_1_def": "easy, unproblematic", "Opt_2_def": "very important", "Opt_3_def": "first; initial", "Opt_4_def": "wide, extensive"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The ____ of the proposal is to deprive people of the liberty to download songs and videos from the internet.", "Opt_1": "aim", "Opt_2": "fragment", "Opt_3": "institution", "Opt_4": "design", "Answer": "aim", "Opt_1_def": "goal or intention", "Opt_2_def": "part of something", "Opt_3_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_4_def": "planning (drawing)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "His research helped establish that identical DNA sequences may ____ differently depending on context and condition.", "Opt_1": "behave", "Opt_2": "manifest", "Opt_3": "ignore", "Opt_4": "arise", "Answer": "behave", "Opt_1_def": "to act or do things in a certain way", "Opt_2_def": "show", "Opt_3_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)", "Opt_4_def": "to happen"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government plans to offer ____ parenting classes for young, unemployed couples.", "Opt_1": "optional", "Opt_2": "several", "Opt_3": "average", "Opt_4": "novel", "Answer": "optional", "Opt_1_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want", "Opt_2_def": "many (about 6 or seven)", "Opt_3_def": "ordinary, typical", "Opt_4_def": "new"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "More than 70 percent of the surveyed firms said that the lack of housing was not a ____ on their ability to expand.", "Opt_1": "image", "Opt_2": "constraint", "Opt_3": "contrary", "Opt_4": "property", "Answer": "constraint", "Opt_1_def": "picture", "Opt_2_def": "to hold back; to prevent", "Opt_3_def": "opposite", "Opt_4_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "No matter how good the lawyer's intuition and ability to express himself or herself, the lawyer will not succeed unless he or she can ____ logically.", "Opt_1": "succeed", "Opt_2": "purchase", "Opt_3": "analyze", "Opt_4": "inhibit", "Answer": "analyze", "Opt_1_def": "to do well", "Opt_2_def": "to buy", "Opt_3_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it", "Opt_4_def": "to prevent or stop"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The students decided to unite in their ____ to fight bullying in the school.", "Opt_1": "clarify", "Opt_2": "align", "Opt_3": "manifest", "Opt_4": "attempt", "Answer": "attempt", "Opt_1_def": "to make something clear, explain", "Opt_2_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar", "Opt_3_def": "show", "Opt_4_def": "to try"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The new team coach is an ____ of the view: No pain, no gain!", "Opt_1": "exponent", "Opt_2": "contrary", "Opt_3": "benefit", "Opt_4": "extract", "Answer": "exponent", "Opt_1_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion", "Opt_2_def": "opposite", "Opt_3_def": "advantage", "Opt_4_def": "to remove; to take out and use"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The gap between Russia's dominant military power and our ____ inferior power could not be bridged overnight.", "Opt_1": "transform", "Opt_2": "own", "Opt_3": "examine", "Opt_4": "prepare", "Answer": "own", "Opt_1_def": "to change (often completely)", "Opt_2_def": "to have or possess", "Opt_3_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_4_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "We ____ the right to refuse alcohol service to anyone who cannot provide proper identification.", "Opt_1": "reserve", "Opt_2": "detect", "Opt_3": "prove", "Opt_4": "assist", "Answer": "reserve", "Opt_1_def": "to keep", "Opt_2_def": "to see, find or notice", "Opt_3_def": "to show to be true", "Opt_4_def": "to help"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "I can't ____ this beetle; I'll have to ask the science teacher what it is.", "Opt_1": "rotate", "Opt_2": "possess", "Opt_3": "identify", "Opt_4": "allocate", "Answer": "identify", "Opt_1_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_2_def": "to have or own", "Opt_3_def": "to know or say who or what something is", "Opt_4_def": "to give to (to promise to give)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "University staff will notice the new look and feel because information will be presented on Web pages ____ of on bulletin boards.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "In tomorrow's TV broadcast the government will ____ its intention to reduce taxes during its time in office.", "Opt_1": "import", "Opt_2": "declare", "Opt_3": "reduce", "Opt_4": "specify", "Answer": "declare", "Opt_1_def": "to bring in (to a country)", "Opt_2_def": "to state", "Opt_3_def": "to make smaller or shorter", "Opt_4_def": "to state exactly"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "When attempting to select a food ____ for an on-campus event, please be sure to ask the following questions.", "Opt_1": "magnitude", "Opt_2": "sphere", "Opt_3": "service", "Opt_4": "point", "Answer": "service", "Opt_1_def": "size; amount", "Opt_2_def": "area of interest", "Opt_3_def": "work done for others; help", "Opt_4_def": "purpose; reason; value"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Because of the increase in the price of oil the company was unable to adhere to its plans to ____ new workers.", "Opt_1": "mention", "Opt_2": "collaborate", "Opt_3": "employ", "Opt_4": "qualify", "Answer": "employ", "Opt_1_def": "to say; state", "Opt_2_def": "to work together", "Opt_3_def": "to give a job to someone; to use", "Opt_4_def": "to become eligible"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "At weddings the speeches usually ____ the food.", "Opt_1": "halt", "Opt_2": "transmit", "Opt_3": "precede", "Opt_4": "utilize", "Answer": "precede", "Opt_1_def": "to stop", "Opt_2_def": "to send or convey", "Opt_3_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to use"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "There was little ____ that the government's plans to increase taxes would be very unpopular.", "Opt_1": "notion", "Opt_2": "doubt", "Opt_3": "committee", "Opt_4": "element", "Answer": "doubt", "Opt_1_def": "idea; concept", "Opt_2_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_3_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue", "Opt_4_def": "aspect, part"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government predicts that oil prices will not ____ as much this year as last year.", "Opt_1": "vary", "Opt_2": "community", "Opt_3": "agent", "Opt_4": "opinion", "Answer": "vary", "Opt_1_def": "to change or be different", "Opt_2_def": "a group of people", "Opt_3_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_4_def": "view; what you think about someone or something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Since that time two major surveys were conducted with an attempt to define the ____ of the problem.", "Opt_1": "scope", "Opt_2": "outline", "Opt_3": "code", "Opt_4": "revolution", "Answer": "scope", "Opt_1_def": "extent, range", "Opt_2_def": "plan or summary", "Opt_3_def": "a set of rules", "Opt_4_def": "a time of great change"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "In order to make up a missed exam, you must ____ written evidence within 48 hours of the exam which shows that you had a legitimate reason to do so.", "Opt_1": "underlie", "Opt_2": "manufacture", "Opt_3": "contemplate", "Opt_4": "produce", "Answer": "produce", "Opt_1_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something", "Opt_2_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_3_def": "to think about; to consider", "Opt_4_def": "to make or create"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The U.S. firms selling steel in India must compete against the firms from not ____ India but Europe, Japan, Korea and China as well.", "Opt_1": "especially", "Opt_2": "simultaneously", "Opt_3": "therefore", "Opt_4": "merely", "Answer": "merely", "Opt_1_def": "particularly", "Opt_2_def": "at the same time", "Opt_3_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_4_def": "only, just, simply"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Photoshop provides you with techniques used to adjust the ____ of graphics and photographs.", "Opt_1": "region", "Opt_2": "staff", "Opt_3": "category", "Opt_4": "quality", "Answer": "quality", "Opt_1_def": "part of a place", "Opt_2_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)", "Opt_3_def": "group of similar items", "Opt_4_def": "worth or value"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "All the ESL student's teachers can ____ influence the speed at which he or she learns English.", "Opt_1": "indirectly", "Opt_2": "conversely", "Opt_3": "nevertheless", "Opt_4": "gradually", "Answer": "indirectly", "Opt_1_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_2_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand", "Opt_3_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_4_def": "slowly; steadily"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Much of the literature reviewed by the ____ failed to specify in sufficient detail the definition of a medication error used in the study.", "Opt_1": "sphere", "Opt_2": "equipment", "Opt_3": "committee", "Opt_4": "order", "Answer": "committee", "Opt_1_def": "area of interest", "Opt_2_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)", "Opt_3_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue", "Opt_4_def": "sequence, place"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Some teachers believe that it is better to teach language to a class with students of ____ ability.", "Opt_1": "homogeneous", "Opt_2": "identical", "Opt_3": "public", "Opt_4": "flexible", "Answer": "homogeneous", "Opt_1_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics", "Opt_2_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_3_def": "open to all; not private", "Opt_4_def": "can be changed or bent"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Twins born from the same egg are called ____ twins. They look exactly the same. Fraternal twins look a little different from each other.", "Opt_1": "identical", "Opt_2": "ambiguous", "Opt_3": "valuable", "Opt_4": "legal", "Answer": "identical", "Opt_1_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_2_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation", "Opt_3_def": "worth a lot of money; important", "Opt_4_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The court concluded that the order did not depart from the ____ requirements of law.", "Opt_1": "essential", "Opt_2": "invisible", "Opt_3": "temporary", "Opt_4": "equivalent", "Answer": "essential", "Opt_1_def": "very important", "Opt_2_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_3_def": "for a short or limited time", "Opt_4_def": "equal to; the same as"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "In the face of the success of industrialization, individuals must ____ and form institutions that would be in line with this task.", "Opt_1": "threaten", "Opt_2": "expel", "Opt_3": "unite", "Opt_4": "respect", "Answer": "unite", "Opt_1_def": "to warn or show signs of danger", "Opt_2_def": "to drive or push out", "Opt_3_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_4_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "You should follow the ____ that the doctor has given you.", "Opt_1": "directions", "Opt_2": "extract", "Opt_3": "concept", "Opt_4": "component", "Answer": "directions", "Opt_1_def": "instructions", "Opt_2_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_3_def": "idea; understanding", "Opt_4_def": "part of; an element of"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The candidate must ____ clear written and verbal communication skills, and must be willing to work in a team project environment.", "Opt_1": "detail", "Opt_2": "aim", "Opt_3": "category", "Opt_4": "command", "Answer": "command", "Opt_1_def": "a small piece of information", "Opt_2_def": "goal or intention", "Opt_3_def": "group of similar items", "Opt_4_def": "control"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Through much of the War, the U.S. and its Allies could not enforce a fully ____ blockade against Germany.", "Opt_1": "elementary", "Opt_2": "effective", "Opt_3": "evident", "Opt_4": "public", "Answer": "effective", "Opt_1_def": "easy", "Opt_2_def": "good, working well", "Opt_3_def": "clear", "Opt_4_def": "open to all; not private"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "In this class, we will examine the ____ about the risks generated by the war on terror.", "Opt_1": "duration", "Opt_2": "license", "Opt_3": "controversy", "Opt_4": "summary", "Answer": "controversy", "Opt_1_def": "period of time", "Opt_2_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)", "Opt_3_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions", "Opt_4_def": "a short account of the most important details"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The conflict ended with a rebellion ____ the East India Company in 1857, and the firm eventually was nationalized.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The more alert you are to the ____ words used and the explicit claims made in ads, the more aware you will become of your own use of words and ideas.", "Opt_1": "automatic", "Opt_2": "broad", "Opt_3": "key", "Opt_4": "necessary", "Answer": "key", "Opt_1_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually", "Opt_2_def": "wide, extensive", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "needed; very important"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government plans to raise the money they ____ to poor countries in the Third World.", "Opt_1": "contain", "Opt_2": "donate", "Opt_3": "incorporate", "Opt_4": "exist", "Answer": "donate", "Opt_1_def": "to have in it; to hold inside", "Opt_2_def": "to give (usually money)", "Opt_3_def": "to include", "Opt_4_def": "to be alive, to be in the world"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The profession of social work is based on the values of service, social and ____ justice, dignity and worth of the person, importance of human relationships, and integrity and competence in practice.", "Opt_1": "vague", "Opt_2": "equivalent", "Opt_3": "distinct", "Opt_4": "economic", "Answer": "economic", "Opt_1_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_2_def": "equal to; the same as", "Opt_3_def": "clear and strong", "Opt_4_def": "financial; to do with money"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Picasso's ____ to draw found expression in a variety of forms.", "Opt_1": "impulse", "Opt_2": "portion", "Opt_3": "debate", "Opt_4": "ability", "Answer": "impulse", "Opt_1_def": "reason or motivation to do something", "Opt_2_def": "part, amount", "Opt_3_def": "formal discussion", "Opt_4_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government cannot afford to be ____ about the numbers of young people who fail to find any kind of employment.", "Opt_1": "scarce", "Opt_2": "confident", "Opt_3": "dynamic", "Opt_4": "passive", "Answer": "passive", "Opt_1_def": "rare, not abundant", "Opt_2_def": "sure that something will happen", "Opt_3_def": "changing; growing; energetic", "Opt_4_def": "not active; unresponsive"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "While addiction and drugs are serious problems in society that require a humane approach, there is no room for nonsense if we want to ____ success.", "Opt_1": "approve", "Opt_2": "behave", "Opt_3": "publish", "Opt_4": "achieve", "Answer": "achieve", "Opt_1_def": "to agree to", "Opt_2_def": "to act or do things in a certain way", "Opt_3_def": "to make available in paper or online form", "Opt_4_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The women did not ____ emotionally to the comedy, but the men did, Filipowicz concludes.", "Opt_1": "react", "Opt_2": "denote", "Opt_3": "block", "Opt_4": "solve", "Answer": "react", "Opt_1_def": "to respond", "Opt_2_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_3_def": "to not allow; to stop or prevent", "Opt_4_def": "to find an answer"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Because there was the threat of losing funding if they failed to participate, there was a strong ____ to do so.", "Opt_1": "doubt", "Opt_2": "legislation", "Opt_3": "incentive", "Opt_4": "bulk", "Answer": "incentive", "Opt_1_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_2_def": "governmental rule; law", "Opt_3_def": "reason to do something", "Opt_4_def": "majority; largest part"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is known that organizations do not ____ readily or easily; many organizations that change do so in ways that are neither successful nor effective.", "Opt_1": "assert", "Opt_2": "adapt", "Opt_3": "verify", "Opt_4": "settle", "Answer": "adapt", "Opt_1_def": "to claim, to say strongly", "Opt_2_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)", "Opt_3_def": "to prove or claim the truth", "Opt_4_def": "to solve a problem or dispute"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "There is really no ____ in arguing which approach is better.", "Opt_1": "point", "Opt_2": "pattern", "Opt_3": "symbol", "Opt_4": "motive", "Answer": "point", "Opt_1_def": "purpose; reason; value", "Opt_2_def": "clear and consistent behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea", "Opt_4_def": "reason"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Survey show that women in American don't recognize their most ____ health risk.", "Opt_1": "local", "Opt_2": "serious", "Opt_3": "eligible", "Opt_4": "complete", "Answer": "serious", "Opt_1_def": "in the area where you live or work", "Opt_2_def": "severe, large", "Opt_3_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something", "Opt_4_def": "full or finished"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The father stated he was from the neighbourhood of Bandon, where he had been unable to ____ any employment.", "Opt_1": "drain", "Opt_2": "modify", "Opt_3": "procure", "Opt_4": "cooperate", "Answer": "procure", "Opt_1_def": "to take away; to get rid of", "Opt_2_def": "to change", "Opt_3_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_4_def": "to work (well) with another person"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "People who suffer from hay fever cannot have real flowers in their house. They have ____ ones instead.", "Opt_1": "automatic", "Opt_2": "artificial", "Opt_3": "drastic", "Opt_4": "medium", "Answer": "artificial", "Opt_1_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually", "Opt_2_def": "not real or natural", "Opt_3_def": "severe; great", "Opt_4_def": "in the middle"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Further analysis suggested that the ____ was worse for women than men.", "Opt_1": "outcome", "Opt_2": "episode", "Opt_3": "fallacy", "Opt_4": "administration", "Answer": "outcome", "Opt_1_def": "result", "Opt_2_def": "period of time", "Opt_3_def": "mistake; false belief", "Opt_4_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "You need to ____ on your admissions application that you will have 24 credits completed at the time of attendance.", "Opt_1": "precede", "Opt_2": "exaggerate", "Opt_3": "indicate", "Opt_4": "spread", "Answer": "indicate", "Opt_1_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_3_def": "to show or convey", "Opt_4_def": "to move (over a wider area)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "There was little ____ that the government's plans to increase taxes would be very unpopular.", "Opt_1": "degree", "Opt_2": "skill", "Opt_3": "doubt", "Opt_4": "hierarchy", "Answer": "doubt", "Opt_1_def": "amount", "Opt_2_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)", "Opt_3_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_4_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The two procedures consistently showed that garlic did not ____ the growth of oral bacteria.", "Opt_1": "inhibit", "Opt_2": "examine", "Opt_3": "consider", "Opt_4": "arise", "Answer": "inhibit", "Opt_1_def": "to prevent or stop", "Opt_2_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_3_def": "to think", "Opt_4_def": "to happen"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "His father's ideas were ____ and out of time. They were traditional views that were losing much of their appeal.", "Opt_1": "obsolete", "Opt_2": "identical", "Opt_3": "absent", "Opt_4": "appropriate", "Answer": "obsolete", "Opt_1_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date", "Opt_2_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_3_def": "being not there; missing", "Opt_4_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "That's probably the most fatuous ____ I've read on this website.", "Opt_1": "education", "Opt_2": "conflict", "Opt_3": "passage", "Opt_4": "comment", "Answer": "comment", "Opt_1_def": "schooling", "Opt_2_def": "problem, struggle or battle", "Opt_3_def": "a piece of written or spoken text", "Opt_4_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The school have employed some guards to make the campus more ____ against unannounced visitors.", "Opt_1": "voluntary", "Opt_2": "vital", "Opt_3": "secure", "Opt_4": "reliable", "Answer": "secure", "Opt_1_def": "done freely; from personal choice", "Opt_2_def": "very important", "Opt_3_def": "safe", "Opt_4_def": "can be trusted, does not let you down \r\n"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "He wants to get a job in the engineering ____ when he leaves school.", "Opt_1": "assignment", "Opt_2": "transition", "Opt_3": "phrase", "Opt_4": "industry", "Answer": "industry", "Opt_1_def": "a task; the giving of a task", "Opt_2_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_3_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure.", "Opt_4_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The word 'gay' did not come to ____ 'homosexual' until quite recently.", "Opt_1": "ignore", "Opt_2": "interfere", "Opt_3": "refute", "Opt_4": "denote", "Answer": "denote", "Opt_1_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)", "Opt_2_def": "to prevent; to harm", "Opt_3_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny", "Opt_4_def": "to mean; to be a sign of"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Many people say that he does not ____ the qualities to become president of this country.", "Opt_1": "mention", "Opt_2": "conform", "Opt_3": "prove", "Opt_4": "possess", "Answer": "possess", "Opt_1_def": "to say; state", "Opt_2_def": "to do what is required", "Opt_3_def": "to show to be true", "Opt_4_def": "to have or own"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "There were many sane but ____ reasons why he gave up his well-paid job.", "Opt_1": "complex", "Opt_2": "familiar", "Opt_3": "temporary", "Opt_4": "capable", "Answer": "complex", "Opt_1_def": "difficult, complicated", "Opt_2_def": "known; well-known", "Opt_3_def": "for a short or limited time", "Opt_4_def": "able"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Students who get in the athletic teams enjoy a high ____ in the school community.", "Opt_1": "version", "Opt_2": "prestige", "Opt_3": "legislation", "Opt_4": "design", "Answer": "prestige", "Opt_1_def": "form", "Opt_2_def": "fame and respect", "Opt_3_def": "governmental rule; law", "Opt_4_def": "planning (drawing)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "An employee is entitled to no ____ for the first seven calendar days of disability unless the disability continues for more than 21 days.", "Opt_1": "precaution", "Opt_2": "state", "Opt_3": "reply", "Opt_4": "compensation", "Answer": "compensation", "Opt_1_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_2_def": "condition, situation", "Opt_3_def": "an answer", "Opt_4_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "I cannot ____ you to listen, but I will ask you to leave the room if you talk while I do.", "Opt_1": "compel", "Opt_2": "adapt", "Opt_3": "compile", "Opt_4": "express", "Answer": "compel", "Opt_1_def": "to force or make happen", "Opt_2_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)", "Opt_3_def": "to put together (often in a list", "Opt_4_def": "to say or mean"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This page contains a ____ outline to be used as a guide for the creation of a strong outline.", "Opt_1": "remedy", "Opt_2": "sample", "Opt_3": "comparison", "Opt_4": "shortage", "Answer": "sample", "Opt_1_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_2_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection", "Opt_3_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different", "Opt_4_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Instead of quick results, Cronbach (1963) believed that consistent experiences ____ improve performance over time.", "Opt_1": "simultaneously", "Opt_2": "absolutely", "Opt_3": "gradually", "Opt_4": "dramatically", "Answer": "gradually", "Opt_1_def": "at the same time", "Opt_2_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_3_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_4_def": "very strongly, significantly"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The ____ was tasked to review the tests and criteria used to determine visual disability for purposes of eligibility for health Insurance benefits.", "Opt_1": "technique", "Opt_2": "transition", "Opt_3": "committee", "Opt_4": "penalty", "Answer": "committee", "Opt_1_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_3_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue", "Opt_4_def": "negative consequence; punishment"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Infinity is an ____ idea that many students find difficult to understand.", "Opt_1": "abundant", "Opt_2": "compatible", "Opt_3": "anonymous", "Opt_4": "abstract", "Answer": "abstract", "Opt_1_def": "existing in large quantities", "Opt_2_def": "able to work with someone or something else", "Opt_3_def": "having no name or known author", "Opt_4_def": "not specific or concrete"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government blamed its ____ in the elections on failure to communicate its policies clearly enough.", "Opt_1": "defeat", "Opt_2": "symptom", "Opt_3": "expense", "Opt_4": "contract", "Answer": "defeat", "Opt_1_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)", "Opt_2_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)", "Opt_3_def": "cost", "Opt_4_def": "a written agreement, binding in law"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "She has continued ____ me with her hard work and positive attitude.", "Opt_1": "retire", "Opt_2": "impress", "Opt_3": "assist", "Opt_4": "fulfill", "Answer": "impress", "Opt_1_def": "to stop working", "Opt_2_def": "to create a favourable reaction", "Opt_3_def": "to help", "Opt_4_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The school can recommend that parents ____ by email, but they cannot insist on it.", "Opt_1": "affect", "Opt_2": "risk", "Opt_3": "communicate", "Opt_4": "supervise", "Answer": "communicate", "Opt_1_def": "to have an influence on", "Opt_2_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure", "Opt_3_def": "to convey information", "Opt_4_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This research study will focus on the ____ practice of web writers and the structure of the web pages they create.", "Opt_1": "explicit", "Opt_2": "current", "Opt_3": "rational", "Opt_4": "major", "Answer": "current", "Opt_1_def": "clearly and openly expressed", "Opt_2_def": "happening now", "Opt_3_def": "base on reason, not on emotion or instinct", "Opt_4_def": "important, large"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The most significant risk ____ in predicting whether a person will commit a violent crime in the future is whether the person has previous offenses.", "Opt_1": "assent", "Opt_2": "impulse", "Opt_3": "factor", "Opt_4": "fault", "Answer": "factor", "Opt_1_def": "agreement", "Opt_2_def": "reason or motivation to do something", "Opt_3_def": "an aspect to be considered", "Opt_4_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Students receive feedback from the teacher on their ____ on the interpretative task before they start on the next one.", "Opt_1": "occasion", "Opt_2": "experiment", "Opt_3": "majority", "Opt_4": "performance", "Answer": "performance", "Opt_1_def": "time (opportunity)", "Opt_2_def": "test", "Opt_3_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_4_def": "action or achievement"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It is scheduled to begin at 3:30 p.m. A decision to ____ or postpone the match will be made later in the day, if necessary.", "Opt_1": "cancel", "Opt_2": "broadcast", "Opt_3": "gather", "Opt_4": "remove", "Answer": "cancel", "Opt_1_def": "to cut or stop from happening", "Opt_2_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)", "Opt_3_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_4_def": "to take away"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Although the agreement was compulsory rather than voluntary, it led to substantial ____ reforms along French lines.", "Opt_1": "ancient", "Opt_2": "adequate", "Opt_3": "sole", "Opt_4": "military", "Answer": "military", "Opt_1_def": "very old", "Opt_2_def": "good enough; ok", "Opt_3_def": "only", "Opt_4_def": "to do with army"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If we ____ that the dimension of a hydrogen atom is about 0.2 nm, then the corresponding confinement energy is about 38 eV.", "Opt_1": "prepare", "Opt_2": "assume", "Opt_3": "specify", "Opt_4": "enumerate", "Answer": "assume", "Opt_1_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)", "Opt_2_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict", "Opt_3_def": "to state exactly", "Opt_4_def": "to list"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Upon completion of the course, students will be able to ____ how grammar and usage errors can interfere with meaning.", "Opt_1": "discern", "Opt_2": "invest", "Opt_3": "associate", "Opt_4": "include", "Answer": "discern", "Opt_1_def": "to see; to perceive", "Opt_2_def": "to put money into something", "Opt_3_def": "to link to; to make a connection to", "Opt_4_def": "to put in; to have in"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "My goal this ____ is to improve my mathematics and science grades.", "Opt_1": "desire", "Opt_2": "term", "Opt_3": "task", "Opt_4": "sequence", "Answer": "term", "Opt_1_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_2_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_3_def": "job", "Opt_4_def": "the order in which things are arranged or happen"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The business has decided to ____ a large reorganization in the attempt to increase profits.", "Opt_1": "accept", "Opt_2": "regulate", "Opt_3": "retire", "Opt_4": "undergo", "Answer": "undergo", "Opt_1_def": "to agree (to have)", "Opt_2_def": "to control", "Opt_3_def": "to stop working", "Opt_4_def": "to receive or experience"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "All the forms below can be electronically filled and submitted with the exception of Form B, which must ____ personal copies of material.", "Opt_1": "collaborate", "Opt_2": "conceal", "Opt_3": "accompany", "Opt_4": "precede", "Answer": "accompany", "Opt_1_def": "to work together", "Opt_2_def": "to hide", "Opt_3_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together", "Opt_4_def": "to go or be before someone or something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government has come under ____ to reduce the tax on petrol because of the high cost of oil.", "Opt_1": "interpretation", "Opt_2": "province", "Opt_3": "challenge", "Opt_4": "pressure", "Answer": "pressure", "Opt_1_def": "explanation; assessment", "Opt_2_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_3_def": "difficult situation; problem", "Opt_4_def": "force; influence; stress"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Access to the data network is both an essential ____ for university life and work, and a valuable privilege.", "Opt_1": "tool", "Opt_2": "profit", "Opt_3": "surface", "Opt_4": "interior", "Answer": "tool", "Opt_1_def": "something used to do a job", "Opt_2_def": "money gained", "Opt_3_def": "the outside layer of an object", "Opt_4_def": "inside"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "About a quarter of the elementary and secondary students typically did not ____ with the teacher at all during class.", "Opt_1": "exchange", "Opt_2": "interact", "Opt_3": "rotate", "Opt_4": "abandon", "Answer": "interact", "Opt_1_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing", "Opt_2_def": "to react, to affect and be affected", "Opt_3_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_4_def": "to leave or give up"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Children in Experiment 2 did not ____ any evidence of recognizing the familiarized words in the passages.", "Opt_1": "outcome", "Opt_2": "exhibit", "Opt_3": "finance", "Opt_4": "region", "Answer": "exhibit", "Opt_1_def": "result", "Opt_2_def": "to show", "Opt_3_def": "to do with money and payment", "Opt_4_def": "part of a place"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Doctors ____ people to restrict the number of eggs they eat to 2-3 per week.", "Opt_1": "adhere", "Opt_2": "occur", "Opt_3": "convert", "Opt_4": "advise", "Answer": "advise", "Opt_1_def": "to keep to; to follow", "Opt_2_def": "to happen; take place", "Opt_3_def": "to change from one thing to another", "Opt_4_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Princeton University computer scientist Edward Felton has decided not to ____ a paper on how his research team broke the code of copyright protection.", "Opt_1": "enhance", "Opt_2": "publish", "Opt_3": "restrict", "Opt_4": "criticize", "Answer": "publish", "Opt_1_def": "to make something better", "Opt_2_def": "to make available in paper or online form", "Opt_3_def": "to limit", "Opt_4_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It is virtually impossible to predict which infants in the latter group will not ____ without support.", "Opt_1": "expel", "Opt_2": "survive", "Opt_3": "accuse", "Opt_4": "assess", "Answer": "survive", "Opt_1_def": "to drive or push out", "Opt_2_def": "to not die", "Opt_3_def": "to blame", "Opt_4_def": "to judge or test"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "In the Spring semester, CIS faculty plans to ____ three new courses in high demand.", "Opt_1": "eliminate", "Opt_2": "react", "Opt_3": "implement", "Opt_4": "join", "Answer": "implement", "Opt_1_def": "to dispose of", "Opt_2_def": "to respond", "Opt_3_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)", "Opt_4_def": "to become a member (of an organization; to get together with others"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If you saved a file to a library PC running Windows ____ to a crash or being logged out, you should be able to recover it.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If you cannot obtain such a statement, you must verify that you have contacted your employer and that the employer was unable to ____ you with the refund.", "Opt_1": "construct", "Opt_2": "assemble", "Opt_3": "displace", "Opt_4": "assist", "Answer": "assist", "Opt_1_def": "to make", "Opt_2_def": "to get, put or bring together", "Opt_3_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "to help"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Economics is the allocation of ____ resources among competing ends.", "Opt_1": "scarce", "Opt_2": "constant", "Opt_3": "intense", "Opt_4": "various", "Answer": "scarce", "Opt_1_def": "rare, not abundant", "Opt_2_def": "not changing; long-lasting", "Opt_3_def": "strong, extreme", "Opt_4_def": "several, of different kinds"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The purpose of this tutorial is to give you an idea of the ____ of events leading up to graduation.", "Opt_1": "profession", "Opt_2": "territory", "Opt_3": "directions", "Opt_4": "sequence", "Answer": "sequence", "Opt_1_def": "job; occupation", "Opt_2_def": "land; area (of interest)", "Opt_3_def": "instructions", "Opt_4_def": "the order in which things are arranged or happen"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "His lungs were filled in an instant with a great ____ of driven air which he could not expel.", "Opt_1": "expert", "Opt_2": "propensity", "Opt_3": "distance", "Opt_4": "volume", "Answer": "volume", "Opt_1_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_2_def": "tendency; desire", "Opt_3_def": "how far it is from one place to another", "Opt_4_def": "amount"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The new government plans to ____ the best possible health service for all of its citizens.", "Opt_1": "deliver", "Opt_2": "construct", "Opt_3": "attract", "Opt_4": "exhaust", "Answer": "deliver", "Opt_1_def": "to provide (often by bringing to people)", "Opt_2_def": "to make", "Opt_3_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like", "Opt_4_def": "to use up"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Many large companies ____ people to analyze a trend such as the way people spend their money on holiday, etc.", "Opt_1": "lessen", "Opt_2": "fade", "Opt_3": "abandon", "Opt_4": "employ", "Answer": "employ", "Opt_1_def": "to reduce", "Opt_2_def": "to disappear slowly", "Opt_3_def": "to leave or give up", "Opt_4_def": "to give a job to someone; to use"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Some people think it was no ____ that there was a terror alarm two days before the election.", "Opt_1": "boundary", "Opt_2": "coincidence", "Opt_3": "tool", "Opt_4": "guide", "Answer": "coincidence", "Opt_1_def": "limit, extent", "Opt_2_def": "an uncommon happening of two things", "Opt_3_def": "something used to do a job", "Opt_4_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "There were complications with the pregnancy, so she had to ____ starting school for a semester.", "Opt_1": "label", "Opt_2": "postpone", "Opt_3": "ignore", "Opt_4": "appoint", "Answer": "postpone", "Opt_1_def": "to give a name to someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to put back in time", "Opt_3_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)", "Opt_4_def": "to give a job to someone"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "A primary ____ of the system is to facilitate the sharing of information with others.", "Opt_1": "function", "Opt_2": "authority", "Opt_3": "phrase", "Opt_4": "entity", "Answer": "function", "Opt_1_def": "job or role", "Opt_2_def": "control (right to control)", "Opt_3_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure.", "Opt_4_def": "thing; body; organization"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Above all, World War II was an ____ of American history in which more American people bonded together in a common cause than ever before or ever since.", "Opt_1": "education", "Opt_2": "episode", "Opt_3": "lack", "Opt_4": "choice", "Answer": "episode", "Opt_1_def": "schooling", "Opt_2_def": "period of time", "Opt_3_def": "absence of a thing", "Opt_4_def": "decision, selection"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "There is no ____ of you having paid for the trip. Are you sure?", "Opt_1": "opportunity", "Opt_2": "record", "Opt_3": "duration", "Opt_4": "amount", "Answer": "record", "Opt_1_def": "chance", "Opt_2_def": "evidence; documentation", "Opt_3_def": "period of time", "Opt_4_def": "how much there is of something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "A few years ago a robot was lowered to the seabed to ____ some objects from the wreck of the Titanic.", "Opt_1": "assist", "Opt_2": "accumulate", "Opt_3": "stress", "Opt_4": "recover", "Answer": "recover", "Opt_1_def": "to help", "Opt_2_def": "to grow; to gather together", "Opt_3_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important", "Opt_4_def": "to get back"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "A feeling prevailed that there were no rules at all on a campus that, only a few years earlier, prided itself on the implementation of ____ regulations.", "Opt_1": "ancient", "Opt_2": "liable", "Opt_3": "aware", "Opt_4": "strict", "Answer": "strict", "Opt_1_def": "very old", "Opt_2_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening", "Opt_3_def": "knowing", "Opt_4_def": "hard, not changeable"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Most people do not ____ politicians who make promises everyone knows cannot be kept.", "Opt_1": "suppose", "Opt_2": "respect", "Opt_3": "impose", "Opt_4": "drain", "Answer": "respect", "Opt_1_def": "to think, imagine", "Opt_2_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something", "Opt_3_def": "to force; to require to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to take away; to get rid of"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It is important that the government's proposals do not ____ the development of small businesses.", "Opt_1": "inhibit", "Opt_2": "facilitate", "Opt_3": "produce", "Opt_4": "unite", "Answer": "inhibit", "Opt_1_def": "to prevent or stop", "Opt_2_def": "to make something easier", "Opt_3_def": "to make or create", "Opt_4_def": "to bring or get together"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "You can take any book ____ this one. I'm reading it.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The company was in a very strong ____ after winning a million dollar contract to build its machines.", "Opt_1": "condition", "Opt_2": "revolution", "Opt_3": "plenty", "Opt_4": "structure", "Answer": "condition", "Opt_1_def": "state", "Opt_2_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_3_def": "many, lots of", "Opt_4_def": "the way something is made or organized"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Everyone has the right to a ____ of living adequate for the health and well-being of himself and of his family, including food, clothing, and shelter.", "Opt_1": "atmosphere", "Opt_2": "standard", "Opt_3": "defect", "Opt_4": "range", "Answer": "standard", "Opt_1_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_2_def": "quality", "Opt_3_def": "problem; mistake", "Opt_4_def": "extent, distance between two points"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Please write a ____ summary of the causes of the first world war. Write no more than 300 words.", "Opt_1": "brief", "Opt_2": "former", "Opt_3": "invisible", "Opt_4": "secure", "Answer": "brief", "Opt_1_def": "short", "Opt_2_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two", "Opt_3_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_4_def": "safe"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "In this particular poem, Dalton, while asking what woman's sphere is, also advises man on woman's potential and her ____ place in life.", "Opt_1": "proper", "Opt_2": "obvious", "Opt_3": "complete", "Opt_4": "hostile", "Answer": "proper", "Opt_1_def": "correct, appropriate", "Opt_2_def": "clear, evident", "Opt_3_def": "full or finished", "Opt_4_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Please ____ after class. I need to talk to you.", "Opt_1": "deny", "Opt_2": "exert", "Opt_3": "remain", "Opt_4": "exchange", "Answer": "remain", "Opt_1_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct", "Opt_2_def": "to use", "Opt_3_def": "to stay; still exist", "Opt_4_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "From the outset of the gulf crisis, President George Bush stated that it was not his intention to ____ the Iraqi people.", "Opt_1": "resist", "Opt_2": "mention", "Opt_3": "insist", "Opt_4": "harm", "Answer": "harm", "Opt_1_def": "to fight against", "Opt_2_def": "to say; state", "Opt_3_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim", "Opt_4_def": "to damage or injure"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The hypothesis put forward in this paper depends in no degree upon the completeness of our knowledge of the former ____ of the organic world.", "Opt_1": "trend", "Opt_2": "cause", "Opt_3": "ignorance", "Opt_4": "condition", "Answer": "condition", "Opt_1_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "the reason why something happens", "Opt_3_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_4_def": "state"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The most serious ____ to implementing the Convention in Venezuela was clearly the poverty facing a large proportion of the population.", "Opt_1": "obstacle", "Opt_2": "site", "Opt_3": "privilege", "Opt_4": "factor", "Answer": "obstacle", "Opt_1_def": "barrier; problem", "Opt_2_def": "place", "Opt_3_def": "a right (to do something)", "Opt_4_def": "an aspect to be considered"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Repeat this ____ until only a small amount of pressure is released when it is vented.", "Opt_1": "factor", "Opt_2": "outcome", "Opt_3": "opinion", "Opt_4": "procedure", "Answer": "procedure", "Opt_1_def": "an aspect to be considered", "Opt_2_def": "result", "Opt_3_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "the way to do something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government has given \ufffd\ufffd10 million to fight AidS in Africa, but some people believe that this ____ is not sufficient.", "Opt_1": "method", "Opt_2": "amount", "Opt_3": "location", "Opt_4": "society", "Answer": "amount", "Opt_1_def": "a way of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "how much there is of something", "Opt_3_def": "place, where something or someone is", "Opt_4_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This is a controversial point that will ____ much debate in the classroom, mainly among graduate students.", "Opt_1": "generate", "Opt_2": "confront", "Opt_3": "correspond", "Opt_4": "justify", "Answer": "generate", "Opt_1_def": "to make or produce", "Opt_2_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)", "Opt_3_def": "to be related to", "Opt_4_def": "to give a reason for doing something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The university plans to ____ a fund so that poorer students can attend.", "Opt_1": "establish", "Opt_2": "undergo", "Opt_3": "enlarge", "Opt_4": "judge", "Answer": "establish", "Opt_1_def": "to begin or set up", "Opt_2_def": "to receive or experience", "Opt_3_def": "to make larger", "Opt_4_def": "to give an opinion about someone or something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Doctors ____ that the better way to get and stay healthy is to eat lots of fruit and vegetables and take regular exercise.", "Opt_1": "threaten", "Opt_2": "store", "Opt_3": "formulate", "Opt_4": "advise", "Answer": "advise", "Opt_1_def": "to warn or show signs of danger", "Opt_2_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later", "Opt_3_def": "to express", "Opt_4_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Over the course of her journey in the program she has come a great distance from her primary focus as an ____ for FEMA.", "Opt_1": "profession", "Opt_2": "remedy", "Opt_3": "agent", "Opt_4": "relationship", "Answer": "agent", "Opt_1_def": "job; occupation", "Opt_2_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_3_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_4_def": "the way to things are connected"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The best ____ of your essay is the fact that it was very easy to follow your line of argument.", "Opt_1": "feature", "Opt_2": "labour", "Opt_3": "objection", "Opt_4": "disaster", "Answer": "feature", "Opt_1_def": "part, aspect", "Opt_2_def": "work", "Opt_3_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval", "Opt_4_def": "a huge problem or failure"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Many large companies are trying to ____ operations in China. This is the key market of the future.", "Opt_1": "strain", "Opt_2": "establish", "Opt_3": "prefer", "Opt_4": "react", "Answer": "establish", "Opt_1_def": "to put under stress or make difficult", "Opt_2_def": "to begin or set up", "Opt_3_def": "to like better", "Opt_4_def": "to respond"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government has passed laws to give equal rights to minority groups, but it can do nothing to remove the ____ that exists inside some people's heads.", "Opt_1": "prejudice", "Opt_2": "attribute", "Opt_3": "site", "Opt_4": "detail", "Answer": "prejudice", "Opt_1_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background", "Opt_2_def": "characteristic; property", "Opt_3_def": "place", "Opt_4_def": "a small piece of information"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "She has made ____ good progress this year, but I still think she could have done better if she had tried harder.", "Opt_1": "approximately", "Opt_2": "absolutely", "Opt_3": "fairly", "Opt_4": "simply", "Answer": "fairly", "Opt_1_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_2_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_3_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_4_def": "completely; just; only"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The teachers are not ____ in favour of the school's plan to introduce flexible working times.", "Opt_1": "thus", "Opt_2": "thereby", "Opt_3": "recently", "Opt_4": "universally", "Answer": "universally", "Opt_1_def": "so", "Opt_2_def": "by doing this", "Opt_3_def": "in the near past", "Opt_4_def": "all over the world; by everyone"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is difficult to ____ the importance of the internet.", "Opt_1": "halt", "Opt_2": "deprive", "Opt_3": "exaggerate", "Opt_4": "neglect", "Answer": "exaggerate", "Opt_1_def": "to stop", "Opt_2_def": "to take away (the opportunity)", "Opt_3_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_4_def": "to not think about or care for"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If your exam is closed book, you will want to prepare an ____ that will assist you in studying until the day of the exam.", "Opt_1": "outline", "Opt_2": "debate", "Opt_3": "decade", "Opt_4": "service", "Answer": "outline", "Opt_1_def": "plan or summary", "Opt_2_def": "formal discussion", "Opt_3_def": "a period of ten years", "Opt_4_def": "work done for others; help"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "He has a strong ____ against religion since suffering badly as a child in a strictly religious school.", "Opt_1": "debt", "Opt_2": "exponent", "Opt_3": "insight", "Opt_4": "bias", "Answer": "bias", "Opt_1_def": "something owed to another person (often money)", "Opt_2_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion", "Opt_3_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_4_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Some subjects in our school have a higher ____ than others. Everyone wants to take science, but few want to study a second language.", "Opt_1": "priority", "Opt_2": "commodity", "Opt_3": "status", "Opt_4": "gap", "Answer": "status", "Opt_1_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_2_def": "a product; something you can buy", "Opt_3_def": "position, standing", "Opt_4_def": "space, opening or time between"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Most older cultures seem to ____ volcanoes as a natural part of life and adjust their habits accordingly.", "Opt_1": "create", "Opt_2": "constitute", "Opt_3": "accept", "Opt_4": "determine", "Answer": "accept", "Opt_1_def": "to make; to use your imagination to make something new", "Opt_2_def": "to be; to make up", "Opt_3_def": "to agree (to have)", "Opt_4_def": "to find out; to establish or identify; state"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The College will take no ____ for any actions taken by students who have been drinking, on or off campus.", "Opt_1": "service", "Opt_2": "institution", "Opt_3": "scope", "Opt_4": "responsibility", "Answer": "responsibility", "Opt_1_def": "work done for others; help", "Opt_2_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_3_def": "extent, range", "Opt_4_def": "job, duty to do something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "You have not got these words in the right order. In German the main verb must be the second ____ in the sentence.", "Opt_1": "diagnosis", "Opt_2": "performance", "Opt_3": "course", "Opt_4": "element", "Answer": "element", "Opt_1_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)", "Opt_2_def": "action or achievement", "Opt_3_def": "a subject or period of study", "Opt_4_def": "aspect, part"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Choose active, ____ verbs to invigorate your scientific or engineering professional papers, thesis, and reports.", "Opt_1": "mental", "Opt_2": "conscious", "Opt_3": "equivalent", "Opt_4": "precise", "Answer": "precise", "Opt_1_def": "of the brain or mind", "Opt_2_def": "aware, knowing", "Opt_3_def": "equal to; the same as", "Opt_4_def": "exact"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Throughout the day, with a brief interval for lunch, he stared at the history project which was ____ the next morning.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Please ____ your disk, shut the disk drive and then click on 'Save'.", "Opt_1": "advise", "Opt_2": "provoke", "Opt_3": "perceive", "Opt_4": "insert", "Answer": "insert", "Opt_1_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice", "Opt_2_def": "to cause to happen", "Opt_3_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think", "Opt_4_def": "to put in"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "This document explains how to ____ password protection from your Web site.", "Opt_1": "presume", "Opt_2": "insist", "Opt_3": "suffer", "Opt_4": "remove", "Answer": "remove", "Opt_1_def": "to believe, assume", "Opt_2_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim", "Opt_3_def": "to experience something bad or painful", "Opt_4_def": "to take away"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "China won't take strong action against Iran's nuclear program because China just made a ____ to buy lots of Iranian oil.", "Opt_1": "demand", "Opt_2": "deal", "Opt_3": "agent", "Opt_4": "diagnosis", "Answer": "deal", "Opt_1_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_2_def": "agreement", "Opt_3_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_4_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Research into heart disease has revealed a clear pattern: those who smoke too much, drink too much and do not ____ enough are the most likely to suffer from it.", "Opt_1": "attribute", "Opt_2": "impulse", "Opt_3": "exercise", "Opt_4": "income", "Answer": "exercise", "Opt_1_def": "characteristic; property", "Opt_2_def": "reason or motivation to do something", "Opt_3_def": "a piece of work, activity", "Opt_4_def": "money earned"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "London is becoming more and more unpleasant. The government needs to drastically increase the ____ for dropping litter.", "Opt_1": "penalty", "Opt_2": "decision", "Opt_3": "figure", "Opt_4": "friction", "Answer": "penalty", "Opt_1_def": "negative consequence; punishment", "Opt_2_def": "intention to do something, choice", "Opt_3_def": "number", "Opt_4_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This ____ is not rare: 99 percent of patients experience a phantom pain after an amputation.", "Opt_1": "site", "Opt_2": "finance", "Opt_3": "passage", "Opt_4": "phenomenon", "Answer": "phenomenon", "Opt_1_def": "place", "Opt_2_def": "to do with money and payment", "Opt_3_def": "a piece of written or spoken text", "Opt_4_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "According to him migrants and refugees do not ____ enough in Dutch society.", "Opt_1": "integrate", "Opt_2": "disturb", "Opt_3": "reserve", "Opt_4": "commence", "Answer": "integrate", "Opt_1_def": "to fit into a new situation", "Opt_2_def": "to interrupt, stop from working", "Opt_3_def": "to keep", "Opt_4_def": "to start"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "He is an American citizen which obviously puts him in a different ____ from the kinds of individuals that the president has suggested might be suitable.", "Opt_1": "deal", "Opt_2": "victory", "Opt_3": "category", "Opt_4": "individual", "Answer": "category", "Opt_1_def": "agreement", "Opt_2_def": "win", "Opt_3_def": "group of similar items", "Opt_4_def": "one person"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "San Francisco's justice reform program is ____ alive, says a UC Berkeley report.", "Opt_1": "definitely", "Opt_2": "barely", "Opt_3": "conversely", "Opt_4": "fairly", "Answer": "barely", "Opt_1_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_2_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_3_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand", "Opt_4_def": "quite, somewhat"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The forecast was for travel volume to ____ by 1 percent to 2 percent compared to last year.", "Opt_1": "increase", "Opt_2": "omit", "Opt_3": "associate", "Opt_4": "sustain", "Answer": "increase", "Opt_1_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_2_def": "to leave something out or not do something", "Opt_3_def": "to link to; to make a connection to", "Opt_4_def": "to keep going; to maintain"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Our aim was to ____ whether the association between HPV infection and cervical cancer is consistent worldwide.", "Opt_1": "recover", "Opt_2": "determine", "Opt_3": "prepare", "Opt_4": "confront", "Answer": "determine", "Opt_1_def": "to get back", "Opt_2_def": "to find out; to establish or identify; state", "Opt_3_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)", "Opt_4_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The sports hall is on the school grounds but it doesn't ____ to the school.", "Opt_1": "belong", "Opt_2": "overcome", "Opt_3": "acknowledge", "Opt_4": "regret", "Answer": "belong", "Opt_1_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone", "Opt_2_def": "to conquer, defeat", "Opt_3_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to", "Opt_4_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Unlike other animals, humans have no ____ for survival; we often choose to do things that may be detrimental to our health.", "Opt_1": "instinct", "Opt_2": "design", "Opt_3": "belief", "Opt_4": "category", "Answer": "instinct", "Opt_1_def": "natural feeling or reaction", "Opt_2_def": "planning (drawing)", "Opt_3_def": "what you think; what you believe in", "Opt_4_def": "group of similar items"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Today the World Bank, which is ____ responsible for the disaster of the last thirty years, acknowledges that the standards for human development are falling in Africa.", "Opt_1": "rather", "Opt_2": "hardly", "Opt_3": "largely", "Opt_4": "thereby", "Answer": "largely", "Opt_1_def": "instead", "Opt_2_def": "not very much", "Opt_3_def": "mostly", "Opt_4_def": "by doing this"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "She is going to fail the course unless there is a ____ improvement in her efforts.", "Opt_1": "physical", "Opt_2": "drastic", "Opt_3": "ancient", "Opt_4": "harsh", "Answer": "drastic", "Opt_1_def": "of the body", "Opt_2_def": "severe; great", "Opt_3_def": "very old", "Opt_4_def": "hard, unfair"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government has come under ____ to reduce the tax on petrol because of the high cost of oil.", "Opt_1": "interpretation", "Opt_2": "pressure", "Opt_3": "challenge", "Opt_4": "effort", "Answer": "pressure", "Opt_1_def": "explanation; assessment", "Opt_2_def": "force; influence; stress", "Opt_3_def": "difficult situation; problem", "Opt_4_def": "hard work; attempt"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Because there was the threat of losing funding if they failed to participate, there was a strong ____ to do so.", "Opt_1": "process", "Opt_2": "incentive", "Opt_3": "design", "Opt_4": "gain", "Answer": "incentive", "Opt_1_def": "a series of steps", "Opt_2_def": "reason to do something", "Opt_3_def": "planning (drawing)", "Opt_4_def": "to get; to increase in .."}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Her ____ absence from school is the principal reason for her bad grades in the final exams.", "Opt_1": "frequent", "Opt_2": "classic", "Opt_3": "overall", "Opt_4": "firm", "Answer": "frequent", "Opt_1_def": "often", "Opt_2_def": "very good, the best or most used", "Opt_3_def": "general", "Opt_4_def": "strong, cannot be changed"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Please ____ me from the trip list. I will not be able to go.", "Opt_1": "differentiate", "Opt_2": "assure", "Opt_3": "fulfill", "Opt_4": "omit", "Answer": "omit", "Opt_1_def": "to make different; to see the difference", "Opt_2_def": "to make sure; to say that something will certainly happen", "Opt_3_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_4_def": "to leave something out or not do something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "We southerners, and especially we white southerners, ____ a huge debt to valiant civil rights leaders like Martin Luther King.", "Opt_1": "formulate", "Opt_2": "owe", "Opt_3": "generate", "Opt_4": "suffer", "Answer": "owe", "Opt_1_def": "to express", "Opt_2_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)", "Opt_3_def": "to make or produce", "Opt_4_def": "to experience something bad or painful"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "If we reflect just a little more, we will see that ____ is hardly the right adjective.", "Opt_1": "discrete", "Opt_2": "major", "Opt_3": "random", "Opt_4": "initial", "Answer": "random", "Opt_1_def": "separate", "Opt_2_def": "important, large", "Opt_3_def": "by chance; without any sequence", "Opt_4_def": "starting, first"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There is not an ____ supply of oil and natural gas.", "Opt_1": "abnormal", "Opt_2": "infinite", "Opt_3": "initial", "Opt_4": "previous", "Answer": "infinite", "Opt_1_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_2_def": "without an end", "Opt_3_def": "starting, first", "Opt_4_def": "the one before"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The ____ of evaluation used will be determined by the instructor but will generally include a combination (or all) of the following: homework, quizzes, exams, and a comprehensive final exam.", "Opt_1": "transition", "Opt_2": "description", "Opt_3": "method", "Opt_4": "location", "Answer": "method", "Opt_1_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_2_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like", "Opt_3_def": "a way of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "place, where something or someone is"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "There is no ____ about it - the seafloor of Baku harbor is virtually dead.", "Opt_1": "symptom", "Opt_2": "component", "Opt_3": "doubt", "Opt_4": "debate", "Answer": "doubt", "Opt_1_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)", "Opt_2_def": "part of; an element of", "Opt_3_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_4_def": "formal discussion"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "House prices in England have continued to ____ in value every year for the past century.", "Opt_1": "constraint", "Opt_2": "debate", "Opt_3": "gain", "Opt_4": "figure", "Answer": "gain", "Opt_1_def": "to hold back; to prevent", "Opt_2_def": "formal discussion", "Opt_3_def": "to get; to increase in ..", "Opt_4_def": "number"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Most countries have a code by which parents can decide if a film is ____ for their children.", "Opt_1": "forthcoming", "Opt_2": "suitable", "Opt_3": "likely", "Opt_4": "complete", "Answer": "suitable", "Opt_1_def": "coming soon", "Opt_2_def": "good for a particular job or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "probable", "Opt_4_def": "full or finished"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Lack of knowledge is not a suitable reason for failure to ____ with regulations.", "Opt_1": "procure", "Opt_2": "owe", "Opt_3": "retire", "Opt_4": "comply", "Answer": "comply", "Opt_1_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_2_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)", "Opt_3_def": "to stop working", "Opt_4_def": "to do what someone asks or orders"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The first ____ change in the business model came with Henry Ford's move toward standardization and applying the concepts of a production line to the car.", "Opt_1": "optional", "Opt_2": "radical", "Opt_3": "local", "Opt_4": "trivial", "Answer": "radical", "Opt_1_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want", "Opt_2_def": "extreme, strong", "Opt_3_def": "in the area where you live or work", "Opt_4_def": "not important"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It is very ____ for a student to learn English so quickly. But she has!", "Opt_1": "rare", "Opt_2": "inevitable", "Opt_3": "broad", "Opt_4": "scarce", "Answer": "rare", "Opt_1_def": "unusual", "Opt_2_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious", "Opt_3_def": "wide, extensive", "Opt_4_def": "rare, not abundant"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "A group of artists who were working and teaching in the Boston area had a ____ idea: to create a new kind of school for professional education in the visual arts.", "Opt_1": "main", "Opt_2": "bold", "Opt_3": "drastic", "Opt_4": "adjacent", "Answer": "bold", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "brave", "Opt_3_def": "severe; great", "Opt_4_def": "next to"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "These tips do not relieve you of the ____ to read and follow the Instruction Booklet which is ONLY available on line this year!", "Opt_1": "stereotype", "Opt_2": "obligation", "Opt_3": "standard", "Opt_4": "commodity", "Answer": "obligation", "Opt_1_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)", "Opt_2_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_3_def": "quality", "Opt_4_def": "a product; something you can buy"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Future research would need to ensure that participants did not engage in any other activities immediately ____ to the study at hand.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "That was not a very ____ thing to do.", "Opt_1": "temporary", "Opt_2": "key", "Opt_3": "wise", "Opt_4": "typical", "Answer": "wise", "Opt_1_def": "for a short or limited time", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "intelligent; sensible", "Opt_4_def": "usual"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If we learn to communicate effectively with others and are willing to risk sharing our own feelings and ____ other's feelings, many rewards will await us.", "Opt_1": "respect", "Opt_2": "avoid", "Opt_3": "exceed", "Opt_4": "dispose", "Answer": "respect", "Opt_1_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something", "Opt_2_def": "to not do something or go somewhere", "Opt_3_def": "to be more than or better than", "Opt_4_def": "to get rid of"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "An employee is entitled to no ____ for the first seven calendar days of disability unless the disability continues for more than 21 days.", "Opt_1": "compensation", "Opt_2": "principle", "Opt_3": "cycle", "Opt_4": "constraint", "Answer": "compensation", "Opt_1_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_2_def": "rule", "Opt_3_def": "a complete series of events or processes", "Opt_4_def": "to hold back; to prevent"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Some beach systems showed significant ____ of sand in the period from 1964.", "Opt_1": "revolution", "Opt_2": "circumstances", "Opt_3": "structure", "Opt_4": "loss", "Answer": "loss", "Opt_1_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_2_def": "situation", "Opt_3_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_4_def": "removal or reduction"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Children in Experiment 2 did not ____ any evidence of recognizing the familiarized words in the passages.", "Opt_1": "exhibit", "Opt_2": "defect", "Opt_3": "aspect", "Opt_4": "drawback", "Answer": "exhibit", "Opt_1_def": "to show", "Opt_2_def": "problem; mistake", "Opt_3_def": "environment that lifts people up,\" says Jain.", "Opt_4_def": "disadvantage, problem"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "On the back of this ____ or on a separate sheet, write a thorough statement describing yourself, your interests, and why you have applied.", "Opt_1": "dismiss", "Opt_2": "tend", "Opt_3": "form", "Opt_4": "utilize", "Answer": "form", "Opt_1_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant", "Opt_2_def": "to often behave in a certain way", "Opt_3_def": "to make (into a shape)", "Opt_4_def": "to use"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The pictures presented aspects of the objects they could not ____ from the equations alone.", "Opt_1": "motivate", "Opt_2": "deduce", "Opt_3": "suspect", "Opt_4": "oppose", "Answer": "deduce", "Opt_1_def": "to get someone interested enough to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to believe", "Opt_4_def": "to be against or fight against something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "On the back of this form or on a separate sheet, write a ____ statement describing yourself, your interests, and why you have applied.", "Opt_1": "global", "Opt_2": "sound", "Opt_3": "odd", "Opt_4": "thorough", "Answer": "thorough", "Opt_1_def": "world", "Opt_2_def": "good; strong", "Opt_3_def": "strange, unusual", "Opt_4_def": "complete and careful"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Please write a brief ____ of the causes of the first world war. Write no more than 300 words.", "Opt_1": "summary", "Opt_2": "concept", "Opt_3": "mechanism", "Opt_4": "limit", "Answer": "summary", "Opt_1_def": "a short account of the most important details", "Opt_2_def": "idea; understanding", "Opt_3_def": "procedure, process", "Opt_4_def": "extent, boundary"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "In a ____ between the school and the parents, it is usually the school that will prevail.", "Opt_1": "duration", "Opt_2": "dispute", "Opt_3": "prejudice", "Opt_4": "code", "Answer": "dispute", "Opt_1_def": "period of time", "Opt_2_def": "argument; conflict", "Opt_3_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background", "Opt_4_def": "a set of rules"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "There are ____ areas under the sea that have not yet been explored.", "Opt_1": "vast", "Opt_2": "characteristic", "Opt_3": "instant", "Opt_4": "straightforward", "Answer": "vast", "Opt_1_def": "very large", "Opt_2_def": "typical", "Opt_3_def": "immediate", "Opt_4_def": "easy"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "This famous ____ will assure her place in the history of sport.", "Opt_1": "victory", "Opt_2": "growth", "Opt_3": "ignorance", "Opt_4": "speed", "Answer": "victory", "Opt_1_def": "win", "Opt_2_def": "development, increase", "Opt_3_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_4_def": "how quickly something moves or changes"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "With his difficult family ____ it is not really surprising that he's having trouble in school.", "Opt_1": "factor", "Opt_2": "aid", "Opt_3": "prospect", "Opt_4": "circumstances", "Answer": "circumstances", "Opt_1_def": "an aspect to be considered", "Opt_2_def": "help (often financial help)", "Opt_3_def": "chance, likelihood", "Opt_4_def": "situation"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It will help to ____ the nuclear powers from developing more advanced and more dangerous weapons.", "Opt_1": "enhance", "Opt_2": "prevent", "Opt_3": "assert", "Opt_4": "accelerate", "Answer": "prevent", "Opt_1_def": "to make something better", "Opt_2_def": "to stop from doing or happening", "Opt_3_def": "to claim, to say strongly", "Opt_4_def": "to get or make faster"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The satellite photographs seem to ____ that North Korea is moving much of its army to the border with China.", "Opt_1": "shrink", "Opt_2": "regulate", "Opt_3": "signify", "Opt_4": "maintain", "Answer": "signify", "Opt_1_def": "to get smaller", "Opt_2_def": "to control", "Opt_3_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_4_def": "to claim or state"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The combination of natural and human systems adds an additional ____ of complexity to the interactions.", "Opt_1": "progress", "Opt_2": "layer", "Opt_3": "hierarchy", "Opt_4": "image", "Answer": "layer", "Opt_1_def": "improvement or development", "Opt_2_def": "level", "Opt_3_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_4_def": "picture"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The expulsion of a student for smoking in the toilets caused a big ____ in the school.", "Opt_1": "figure", "Opt_2": "controversy", "Opt_3": "method", "Opt_4": "circumstances", "Answer": "controversy", "Opt_1_def": "number", "Opt_2_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions", "Opt_3_def": "a way of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "situation"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government announced that it was pleased with the ____ fall in unemployment during its term in office.", "Opt_1": "exact", "Opt_2": "competent", "Opt_3": "steady", "Opt_4": "royal", "Answer": "steady", "Opt_1_def": "precise, opposite of approximate", "Opt_2_def": "good at something (often a job)", "Opt_3_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm", "Opt_4_def": "of kings and queens"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Bright flashing lights ____ headaches in some people.", "Opt_1": "distort", "Opt_2": "culminate", "Opt_3": "focus", "Opt_4": "trigger", "Answer": "trigger", "Opt_1_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)", "Opt_2_def": "to end", "Opt_3_def": "to direct attention (on an issue)", "Opt_4_def": "to (cause to) start"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government intends to found a new organization to help young people find ____ jobs.", "Opt_1": "suitable", "Opt_2": "optional", "Opt_3": "profound", "Opt_4": "eligible", "Answer": "suitable", "Opt_1_def": "good for a particular job or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want", "Opt_3_def": "deep; great; serious", "Opt_4_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "What do western Louisville and the Appalachian region have in common ____ being two of the poorest areas in Kentucky?", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government predictably tried to ____ the report, and when it was released, attacked its author.", "Opt_1": "employ", "Opt_2": "suppress", "Opt_3": "explore", "Opt_4": "realize", "Answer": "suppress", "Opt_1_def": "to give a job to someone; to use", "Opt_2_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen", "Opt_3_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)", "Opt_4_def": "to come to know or understand"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If we reflect just a little more, we will see that ____ is hardly the right adjective.", "Opt_1": "random", "Opt_2": "ambiguous", "Opt_3": "neutral", "Opt_4": "passive", "Answer": "random", "Opt_1_def": "by chance; without any sequence", "Opt_2_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation", "Opt_3_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative", "Opt_4_def": "not active; unresponsive"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "There were complications with the pregnancy, so she had to ____ starting school for a semester.", "Opt_1": "compile", "Opt_2": "postpone", "Opt_3": "exhaust", "Opt_4": "invest", "Answer": "postpone", "Opt_1_def": "to put together (often in a list", "Opt_2_def": "to put back in time", "Opt_3_def": "to use up", "Opt_4_def": "to put money into something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The syllabus must ____ how attendance and participation affect, if at all, the student's course grade.", "Opt_1": "impose", "Opt_2": "ensure", "Opt_3": "clarify", "Opt_4": "attempt", "Answer": "clarify", "Opt_1_def": "to force; to require to happen", "Opt_2_def": "to make sure (of)", "Opt_3_def": "to make something clear, explain", "Opt_4_def": "to try"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The student must also have a ____ address within the 22 South Texas county area.", "Opt_1": "genuine", "Opt_2": "compulsory", "Opt_3": "permanent", "Opt_4": "dynamic", "Answer": "permanent", "Opt_1_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_2_def": "required, must be done", "Opt_3_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time", "Opt_4_def": "changing; growing; energetic"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It is extremely important that you ____ a strong motive to return to your country after you complete your studies.", "Opt_1": "threaten", "Opt_2": "establish", "Opt_3": "proceed", "Opt_4": "engage", "Answer": "establish", "Opt_1_def": "to warn or show signs of danger", "Opt_2_def": "to begin or set up", "Opt_3_def": "to go forward (and do ..)", "Opt_4_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "You may have learned the steps of the scientific method but, in your preparation, failed to ____ each step with an example.", "Opt_1": "combine", "Opt_2": "illustrate", "Opt_3": "engage", "Opt_4": "inform", "Answer": "illustrate", "Opt_1_def": "to put or go together", "Opt_2_def": "to show; to make clear", "Opt_3_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on", "Opt_4_def": "to say, give information"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "As each hydrogen only has one electron to share in the formation of chemical bonds, it is impossible to ____ more than two hydrogen atoms to each other.", "Opt_1": "master", "Opt_2": "connect", "Opt_3": "accuse", "Opt_4": "enter", "Answer": "connect", "Opt_1_def": "to (gain) control", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or put together", "Opt_3_def": "to blame", "Opt_4_def": "to go in or put in"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is not always possible to distinguish a cause of a ____ from a consequence of that ____.", "Opt_1": "cause", "Opt_2": "license", "Opt_3": "treatment", "Opt_4": "conflict", "Answer": "conflict", "Opt_1_def": "the reason why something happens", "Opt_2_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)", "Opt_3_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)", "Opt_4_def": "problem, struggle or battle"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Thorough testing based on the test strategies and test plans created during the design phase will ____ that the clients receive the products they need.", "Opt_1": "contact", "Opt_2": "assure", "Opt_3": "integrate", "Opt_4": "fade", "Answer": "assure", "Opt_1_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)", "Opt_2_def": "to make sure; to say that something will certainly happen", "Opt_3_def": "to fit into a new situation", "Opt_4_def": "to disappear slowly"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Overpraising a person's ____ achievements can be just as discriminatory as undervaluing them.", "Opt_1": "moderate", "Opt_2": "urban", "Opt_3": "anonymous", "Opt_4": "logical", "Answer": "moderate", "Opt_1_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_2_def": "of the town or city", "Opt_3_def": "having no name or known author", "Opt_4_def": "making sense"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "He had to ____ the fact that teaching was not the right job for him.", "Opt_1": "contact", "Opt_2": "transmit", "Opt_3": "contain", "Opt_4": "acknowledge", "Answer": "acknowledge", "Opt_1_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)", "Opt_2_def": "to send or convey", "Opt_3_def": "to have in it; to hold inside", "Opt_4_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Some people ____ poor immigrants - employing them as house cleaners for very low pay.", "Opt_1": "advise", "Opt_2": "evolve", "Opt_3": "broadcast", "Opt_4": "exploit", "Answer": "exploit", "Opt_1_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice", "Opt_2_def": "to develop (into something better)", "Opt_3_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)", "Opt_4_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Its plot centers on how the ____ between two female \"mates\" is almost broken because both love the same man.", "Opt_1": "category", "Opt_2": "bond", "Opt_3": "fallacy", "Opt_4": "statistic", "Answer": "bond", "Opt_1_def": "group of similar items", "Opt_2_def": "link; tie", "Opt_3_def": "mistake; false belief", "Opt_4_def": "mathematical number"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Sorry but low-cut T-shirts are not ____ clothes for school.", "Opt_1": "abstract", "Opt_2": "capable", "Opt_3": "appropriate", "Opt_4": "invisible", "Answer": "appropriate", "Opt_1_def": "not specific or concrete", "Opt_2_def": "able", "Opt_3_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable", "Opt_4_def": "cannot be seen"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "There is English expression which claims: All roads lead to Rome. This means that there is more than one ____ to fame and success in life.", "Opt_1": "target", "Opt_2": "sum", "Opt_3": "image", "Opt_4": "route", "Answer": "route", "Opt_1_def": "aim, goal", "Opt_2_def": "an amount of money, total", "Opt_3_def": "picture", "Opt_4_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "European governments strongly ____ the kidnapping of a German aid worker in Afghanistan.", "Opt_1": "condemn", "Opt_2": "trade", "Opt_3": "confirm", "Opt_4": "enforce", "Answer": "condemn", "Opt_1_def": "to express strong disapproval", "Opt_2_def": "to exchange products or services", "Opt_3_def": "to agree that something is correct", "Opt_4_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The best proof of this is that the institutional unity provided for by the Treaty of Maastricht did not ____ for even one year after the treaty was ratified.", "Opt_1": "adapt", "Opt_2": "qualify", "Opt_3": "survive", "Opt_4": "join", "Answer": "survive", "Opt_1_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)", "Opt_2_def": "to become eligible", "Opt_3_def": "to not die", "Opt_4_def": "to become a member (of an organization; to get together with others"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "In this class, we will ____ the controversy about the risks generated by the war on terror.", "Opt_1": "migrate", "Opt_2": "compel", "Opt_3": "prevent", "Opt_4": "examine", "Answer": "examine", "Opt_1_def": "to go to another place", "Opt_2_def": "to force or make happen", "Opt_3_def": "to stop from doing or happening", "Opt_4_def": "to look at carefully"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government will never win the ____ against drug-taking.", "Opt_1": "rise", "Opt_2": "concern", "Opt_3": "battle", "Opt_4": "contrary", "Answer": "battle", "Opt_1_def": "to go up", "Opt_2_def": "worry, fear", "Opt_3_def": "fight, part of a war", "Opt_4_def": "opposite"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The ____ to peace and prosperity in the region can only commence when the civic authority is brought back in.", "Opt_1": "survey", "Opt_2": "resident", "Opt_3": "period", "Opt_4": "journey", "Answer": "journey", "Opt_1_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data", "Opt_2_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_3_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)", "Opt_4_def": "a long trip to a different place"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "You are ____ going to fail the course unless you start working harder.", "Opt_1": "recently", "Opt_2": "indirectly", "Opt_3": "conversely", "Opt_4": "definitely", "Answer": "definitely", "Opt_1_def": "in the near past", "Opt_2_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_3_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand", "Opt_4_def": "certainly; without doubt"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The online instructor must incorporate the best practices of traditional teaching without the ____ of face-to-face interaction.", "Opt_1": "error", "Opt_2": "condition", "Opt_3": "motive", "Opt_4": "benefit", "Answer": "benefit", "Opt_1_def": "a mistake", "Opt_2_def": "state", "Opt_3_def": "reason", "Opt_4_def": "advantage"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Stated simply, this ____ means that averaged over large enough distances, one part of the Universe looks approximately like any other part.", "Opt_1": "progress", "Opt_2": "principle", "Opt_3": "location", "Opt_4": "contrary", "Answer": "principle", "Opt_1_def": "improvement or development", "Opt_2_def": "rule", "Opt_3_def": "place, where something or someone is", "Opt_4_def": "opposite"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It is the ____ of every teacher to be prepared for class and to do everything he or she can to help the students learn.", "Opt_1": "lecture", "Opt_2": "procedure", "Opt_3": "duty", "Opt_4": "entity", "Answer": "duty", "Opt_1_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "the way to do something", "Opt_3_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do", "Opt_4_def": "thing; body; organization"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The army sent 2,000 of its soldiers to ____ clothing to the refugees driven out of their homes by fighting.", "Opt_1": "expand", "Opt_2": "label", "Opt_3": "explain", "Opt_4": "distribute", "Answer": "distribute", "Opt_1_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas", "Opt_2_def": "to give a name to someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to give out"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "There is no point having a law if the police are not willing to ____ it.", "Opt_1": "afford", "Opt_2": "enforce", "Opt_3": "expose", "Opt_4": "sustain", "Answer": "enforce", "Opt_1_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_2_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)", "Opt_3_def": "to uncover, reveal", "Opt_4_def": "to keep going; to maintain"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The school cafeteria has made the ____ decision not to offer hamburgers, hot dogs and French fries to the younger students .", "Opt_1": "final", "Opt_2": "basic", "Opt_3": "faint", "Opt_4": "sane", "Answer": "sane", "Opt_1_def": "last", "Opt_2_def": "first or easy", "Opt_3_def": "not strong", "Opt_4_def": "reasonable; not mad"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Its plot centers on how the ____ between two female \"mates\" is almost broken because both love the same man.", "Opt_1": "career", "Opt_2": "range", "Opt_3": "expert", "Opt_4": "bond", "Answer": "bond", "Opt_1_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_2_def": "extent, distance between two points", "Opt_3_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_4_def": "link; tie"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Some students claim that they can ____ watch TV and do their homework.", "Opt_1": "furthermore", "Opt_2": "approximately", "Opt_3": "greatly", "Opt_4": "simultaneously", "Answer": "simultaneously", "Opt_1_def": "also, in addition", "Opt_2_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_3_def": "very much", "Opt_4_def": "at the same time"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Some students claim that they can ____ watch TV and do their homework.", "Opt_1": "hence", "Opt_2": "furthermore", "Opt_3": "simultaneously", "Opt_4": "especially", "Answer": "simultaneously", "Opt_1_def": "so, therefore", "Opt_2_def": "also, in addition", "Opt_3_def": "at the same time", "Opt_4_def": "particularly"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The grade will be amended but the ____ grade will remain on the record with an appropriate notation.", "Opt_1": "positive", "Opt_2": "former", "Opt_3": "rare", "Opt_4": "obsolete", "Answer": "former", "Opt_1_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_2_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two", "Opt_3_def": "unusual", "Opt_4_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If your exam is closed book, you will want to ____ an outline that will assist you in studying until the day of the exam.", "Opt_1": "address", "Opt_2": "insist", "Opt_3": "integrate", "Opt_4": "prepare", "Answer": "prepare", "Opt_1_def": "to give attention to (an issue)", "Opt_2_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim", "Opt_3_def": "to fit into a new situation", "Opt_4_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "I need to ____ the importance of meeting the project deadlines.", "Opt_1": "spread", "Opt_2": "emphasize", "Opt_3": "forego", "Opt_4": "deviate", "Answer": "emphasize", "Opt_1_def": "to move (over a wider area)", "Opt_2_def": "to stress, to say something strongly", "Opt_3_def": "to do without; to give up", "Opt_4_def": "to be different"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The minister gave an ____ answer when asked if the government intended to raise taxes.", "Opt_1": "anonymous", "Opt_2": "ambiguous", "Opt_3": "common", "Opt_4": "distinct", "Answer": "ambiguous", "Opt_1_def": "having no name or known author", "Opt_2_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation", "Opt_3_def": "often seen or happening", "Opt_4_def": "clear and strong"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Difficult financial times must not force us to ____ the integration of teaching and research.", "Opt_1": "abandon", "Opt_2": "remove", "Opt_3": "invent", "Opt_4": "clarify", "Answer": "abandon", "Opt_1_def": "to leave or give up", "Opt_2_def": "to take away", "Opt_3_def": "to create (often a new object)", "Opt_4_def": "to make something clear, explain"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Some students will ____ that advertising does not \"mean\" anything; they may feel that ads have little effect on the way people think and act.", "Opt_1": "fail", "Opt_2": "declare", "Opt_3": "accelerate", "Opt_4": "insist", "Answer": "insist", "Opt_1_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly", "Opt_2_def": "to state", "Opt_3_def": "to get or make faster", "Opt_4_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "We should avoid the error of assuming that we will ever be able to ____ the causes of his behaviour.", "Opt_1": "investigate", "Opt_2": "obtain", "Opt_3": "comprehend", "Opt_4": "assert", "Answer": "comprehend", "Opt_1_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened", "Opt_2_def": "to get", "Opt_3_def": "to understand", "Opt_4_def": "to claim, to say strongly"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Our preliminary surveys did not differentiate between different types of questions, so we were unable to ____ this issue.", "Opt_1": "associate", "Opt_2": "recover", "Opt_3": "exceed", "Opt_4": "explore", "Answer": "explore", "Opt_1_def": "to link to; to make a connection to", "Opt_2_def": "to get back", "Opt_3_def": "to be more than or better than", "Opt_4_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Everyone should join together to ____ the environment.", "Opt_1": "tend", "Opt_2": "address", "Opt_3": "adopt", "Opt_4": "protect", "Answer": "protect", "Opt_1_def": "to often behave in a certain way", "Opt_2_def": "to give attention to (an issue)", "Opt_3_def": "to take in; to start", "Opt_4_def": "to keep something out of danger"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "There is no trace of an ____ idea in this essay.", "Opt_1": "concise", "Opt_2": "original", "Opt_3": "relevant", "Opt_4": "secure", "Answer": "original", "Opt_1_def": "short, not detailed", "Opt_2_def": "the first of its kind", "Opt_3_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration", "Opt_4_def": "safe"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Giuliani's leadership during New York City's darkest hours of the September 11th terrorist attacks earned him global ____ and admiration.", "Opt_1": "disperse", "Opt_2": "manage", "Opt_3": "praise", "Opt_4": "force", "Answer": "praise", "Opt_1_def": "to spread out; to move apart", "Opt_2_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to express approval about something someone has done", "Opt_4_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Upon completion of the course, students will be able to ____ how grammar and usage errors can interfere with meaning.", "Opt_1": "deny", "Opt_2": "cease", "Opt_3": "discern", "Opt_4": "respect", "Answer": "discern", "Opt_1_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct", "Opt_2_def": "to stop", "Opt_3_def": "to see; to perceive", "Opt_4_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Yoo Jong-pil, spokesman of the DP, claimed Roh wanted to further ____ himself from the previous government and humiliate the DP.", "Opt_1": "protest", "Opt_2": "promote", "Opt_3": "distinguish", "Opt_4": "maintain", "Answer": "distinguish", "Opt_1_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_2_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job", "Opt_3_def": "to make clear the differences between two things", "Opt_4_def": "to claim or state"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "In Germany most students have the chance to gain ____ experience in an office or factory, before deciding what job they would like to do.", "Opt_1": "characteristic", "Opt_2": "practical", "Opt_3": "appropriate", "Opt_4": "positive", "Answer": "practical", "Opt_1_def": "typical", "Opt_2_def": "useful; possible", "Opt_3_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable", "Opt_4_def": "good; optimistic"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The political system must not be allowed to ____ into unlimited majority rule, which could result in the erosion of individual liberty.", "Opt_1": "define", "Opt_2": "confront", "Opt_3": "deduce", "Opt_4": "degenerate", "Answer": "degenerate", "Opt_1_def": "to state what something is or means", "Opt_2_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)", "Opt_3_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to get worse"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Aschoff's trip failed because he was unable to ____ his concept against the competitive approach favored by German and Russian scientists.", "Opt_1": "achieve", "Opt_2": "defend", "Opt_3": "compete", "Opt_4": "behave", "Answer": "defend", "Opt_1_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)", "Opt_2_def": "to give reasons for", "Opt_3_def": "to try and win against someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to act or do things in a certain way"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Although consultation between students in solving problems is encouraged, ____ answers will be considered plagiarized.", "Opt_1": "ideal", "Opt_2": "average", "Opt_3": "bold", "Opt_4": "identical", "Answer": "identical", "Opt_1_def": "best, optimal", "Opt_2_def": "ordinary, typical", "Opt_3_def": "brave", "Opt_4_def": "exactly the same"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Supplementary reading ____ will be mailed to each participant at least two weeks before the broadcast.", "Opt_1": "extract", "Opt_2": "materials", "Opt_3": "ratio", "Opt_4": "event", "Answer": "materials", "Opt_1_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_2_def": "the things you need to do something", "Opt_3_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount", "Opt_4_def": "a happening"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The revolutionary ____ must come from those basic human needs that are failed by capitalism.", "Opt_1": "bulk", "Opt_2": "impulse", "Opt_3": "intention", "Opt_4": "shortage", "Answer": "impulse", "Opt_1_def": "majority; largest part", "Opt_2_def": "reason or motivation to do something", "Opt_3_def": "plan, aim", "Opt_4_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "We have a painting at home that's very valuable. It must be ____ more than a million dollars!", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The commercial ____ of Frankfurt is to the south east of the city center.", "Opt_1": "area", "Opt_2": "quantity", "Opt_3": "conflict", "Opt_4": "means", "Answer": "area", "Opt_1_def": "field, sphere", "Opt_2_def": "amount", "Opt_3_def": "problem, struggle or battle", "Opt_4_def": "way"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Almost everyone believes that terrorism should be fought, but there is little agreement about the ____ in which it should be done.", "Opt_1": "bulk", "Opt_2": "manner", "Opt_3": "skill", "Opt_4": "exhibit", "Answer": "manner", "Opt_1_def": "majority; largest part", "Opt_2_def": "way of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)", "Opt_4_def": "to show"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "You have one last ____ to show that you can work hard and behave properly. If you don't take it, you will be asked to leave the school.", "Opt_1": "opportunity", "Opt_2": "scale", "Opt_3": "community", "Opt_4": "region", "Answer": "opportunity", "Opt_1_def": "chance", "Opt_2_def": "extent", "Opt_3_def": "a group of people", "Opt_4_def": "part of a place"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The company was heavily in ____ after investing a lot of money in new machinery.", "Opt_1": "field", "Opt_2": "debt", "Opt_3": "facilities", "Opt_4": "procedure", "Answer": "debt", "Opt_1_def": "area of interest or study", "Opt_2_def": "something owed to another person (often money)", "Opt_3_def": "buildings and other places that can be used by people", "Opt_4_def": "the way to do something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Yoo Jong-pil, spokesman of the DP, claimed Roh wanted to further ____ himself from the previous government and humiliate the DP.", "Opt_1": "classify", "Opt_2": "examine", "Opt_3": "distinguish", "Opt_4": "depart", "Answer": "distinguish", "Opt_1_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_2_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_3_def": "to make clear the differences between two things", "Opt_4_def": "to leave; to be different from"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The conflict ended with a rebellion against the East India Company in 1857, and the ____ eventually was nationalized.", "Opt_1": "spontaneous", "Opt_2": "intrinsic", "Opt_3": "suitable", "Opt_4": "firm", "Answer": "firm", "Opt_1_def": "happening without warning or planning", "Opt_2_def": "belonging to; inherent in", "Opt_3_def": "good for a particular job or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "strong, cannot be changed"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Unfortunately, heroines of this sort are not ____ in oral tales, and do not exist at all in any of the Grimm tales.", "Opt_1": "wise", "Opt_2": "numerous", "Opt_3": "external", "Opt_4": "ancient", "Answer": "numerous", "Opt_1_def": "intelligent; sensible", "Opt_2_def": "very many", "Opt_3_def": "outside", "Opt_4_def": "very old"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "This is an important finding that has implications for the ____ and treatment of children with PTSD.", "Opt_1": "diagnosis", "Opt_2": "limit", "Opt_3": "resident", "Opt_4": "region", "Answer": "diagnosis", "Opt_1_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)", "Opt_2_def": "extent, boundary", "Opt_3_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_4_def": "part of a place"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Above all, World War II was an ____ of American history in which more American people bonded together in a common cause than ever before or ever since.", "Opt_1": "property", "Opt_2": "tradition", "Opt_3": "episode", "Opt_4": "deed", "Answer": "episode", "Opt_1_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home", "Opt_2_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things", "Opt_3_def": "period of time", "Opt_4_def": "an action"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Curiously absent from the report is any mention of the type of action that the State would have taken against the ____ sources of TCE.", "Opt_1": "utter", "Opt_2": "diverse", "Opt_3": "massive", "Opt_4": "imaginary", "Answer": "diverse", "Opt_1_def": "complete, total", "Opt_2_def": "many and different", "Opt_3_def": "very large", "Opt_4_def": "not real; from the imagination"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The ____ of the students' time is spent performing experiments, with required one-on-one mentorship by a graduate student, fellow, or faculty member.", "Opt_1": "statement", "Opt_2": "comment", "Opt_3": "bulk", "Opt_4": "gain", "Answer": "bulk", "Opt_1_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)", "Opt_2_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion", "Opt_3_def": "majority; largest part", "Opt_4_def": "to get; to increase in .."}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "He did not manage to develop a particularly good ____ in his own life until he was able to stop worrying about what others thought of him.", "Opt_1": "feature", "Opt_2": "diagnosis", "Opt_3": "balance", "Opt_4": "revenue", "Answer": "balance", "Opt_1_def": "part, aspect", "Opt_2_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)", "Opt_3_def": "equalness", "Opt_4_def": "money, income"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Some scientists believe that genetically modified food can ____ people's health.", "Opt_1": "realize", "Opt_2": "destroy", "Opt_3": "praise", "Opt_4": "harm", "Answer": "harm", "Opt_1_def": "to come to know or understand", "Opt_2_def": "to break or damage completely", "Opt_3_def": "to express approval about something someone has done", "Opt_4_def": "to damage or injure"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "A snowstorm failed to ____ soccer practice on the Inlet early last week.", "Opt_1": "abandon", "Opt_2": "displace", "Opt_3": "gather", "Opt_4": "interrupt", "Answer": "interrupt", "Opt_1_def": "to leave or give up", "Opt_2_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_4_def": "to stop something from happening"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Miller's path to UCSC was far from smooth, but her ____ and determination kept her moving toward her goal.", "Opt_1": "implement", "Opt_2": "focus", "Opt_3": "stipulate", "Opt_4": "block", "Answer": "focus", "Opt_1_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)", "Opt_2_def": "to direct attention (on an issue)", "Opt_3_def": "to require", "Opt_4_def": "to not allow; to stop or prevent"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The bank didn't think that her idea would ____ enough money so they refused to finance it.", "Opt_1": "generate", "Opt_2": "fulfill", "Opt_3": "deteriorate", "Opt_4": "suppress", "Answer": "generate", "Opt_1_def": "to make or produce", "Opt_2_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_3_def": "to get worse", "Opt_4_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The unemployment figures ____ that the recent changes in tax have been successful.", "Opt_1": "afford", "Opt_2": "indicate", "Opt_3": "provoke", "Opt_4": "identify", "Answer": "indicate", "Opt_1_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_2_def": "to show or convey", "Opt_3_def": "to cause to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to know or say who or what something is"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The powerful hold that the empire of Egypt had on Palestine at this time would not have permitted the rise of a significant ____ such as Israel.", "Opt_1": "topic", "Opt_2": "conflict", "Opt_3": "implication", "Opt_4": "entity", "Answer": "entity", "Opt_1_def": "area of interest or discussion", "Opt_2_def": "problem, struggle or battle", "Opt_3_def": "result or consequence", "Opt_4_def": "thing; body; organization"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Fire Chief Anthony Yenzer said the ____ cause of the fire was determined shortly afterwards through interviews with the two male students.", "Opt_1": "probable", "Opt_2": "consistent", "Opt_3": "reasonable", "Opt_4": "rare", "Answer": "probable", "Opt_1_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers.", "Opt_2_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_3_def": "acceptable, quite good", "Opt_4_def": "unusual"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Although we did train the faculty in the revised teaching methods, in hindsight our training was not ____ enough to prepare them for the new course.", "Opt_1": "credible", "Opt_2": "wise", "Opt_3": "distinct", "Opt_4": "thorough", "Answer": "thorough", "Opt_1_def": "believable", "Opt_2_def": "intelligent; sensible", "Opt_3_def": "clear and strong", "Opt_4_def": "complete and careful"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government plans to offer ____ parenting classes for young, unemployed couples.", "Opt_1": "major", "Opt_2": "compulsory", "Opt_3": "optional", "Opt_4": "absent", "Answer": "optional", "Opt_1_def": "important, large", "Opt_2_def": "required, must be done", "Opt_3_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want", "Opt_4_def": "being not there; missing"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If you ____ the globe by 360\ufffdX, you will return to your starting point.", "Opt_1": "adjust", "Opt_2": "rotate", "Opt_3": "commit", "Opt_4": "repeat", "Answer": "rotate", "Opt_1_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)", "Opt_2_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_3_def": "to do (often an offense)", "Opt_4_def": "to do or say again"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is not clear to me how you can ____ make cannabis legal and expect the consumption of it to go down.", "Opt_1": "extremely", "Opt_2": "simultaneously", "Opt_3": "approximately", "Opt_4": "namely", "Answer": "simultaneously", "Opt_1_def": "very", "Opt_2_def": "at the same time", "Opt_3_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_4_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Check your ____ to be sure that class times do not overlap.", "Opt_1": "guide", "Opt_2": "schedule", "Opt_3": "counsel", "Opt_4": "dispute", "Answer": "schedule", "Opt_1_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)", "Opt_2_def": "timetable", "Opt_3_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_4_def": "argument; conflict"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It is not the government's ____ to tell people how they should live and what they should spend their money on.", "Opt_1": "responsibility", "Opt_2": "sample", "Opt_3": "power", "Opt_4": "instinct", "Answer": "responsibility", "Opt_1_def": "job, duty to do something", "Opt_2_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection", "Opt_3_def": "the right or authority to do something", "Opt_4_def": "natural feeling or reaction"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is difficult to ____ the government's decision to invade Iraq.", "Opt_1": "defend", "Opt_2": "classify", "Opt_3": "assume", "Opt_4": "transmit", "Answer": "defend", "Opt_1_def": "to give reasons for", "Opt_2_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_3_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict", "Opt_4_def": "to send or convey"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The main ____ of this ESL course is to improve students' ability in academic writing.", "Opt_1": "objective", "Opt_2": "defeat", "Opt_3": "diagram", "Opt_4": "consequence", "Answer": "objective", "Opt_1_def": "aim or goal", "Opt_2_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)", "Opt_3_def": "a type of picture or chart", "Opt_4_def": "result"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government has taken the wise decision to consult the ____ before passing the proposed law.", "Opt_1": "credible", "Opt_2": "former", "Opt_3": "public", "Opt_4": "obvious", "Answer": "public", "Opt_1_def": "believable", "Opt_2_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two", "Opt_3_def": "open to all; not private", "Opt_4_def": "clear, evident"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The ____ information provides details on the spiking neuron model used in this work.", "Opt_1": "supplementary", "Opt_2": "prime", "Opt_3": "rapid", "Opt_4": "capable", "Answer": "supplementary", "Opt_1_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "quick", "Opt_4_def": "able"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The strategy used for the ____ campaign was somewhat different.", "Opt_1": "major", "Opt_2": "actual", "Opt_3": "explicit", "Opt_4": "extraordinary", "Answer": "actual", "Opt_1_def": "important, large", "Opt_2_def": "real", "Opt_3_def": "clearly and openly expressed", "Opt_4_def": "very unusual"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Most people ____ to drive to huge out-of-town stores than use their local shops which are often much more expensive.", "Opt_1": "deduce", "Opt_2": "prefer", "Opt_3": "allocate", "Opt_4": "prosper", "Answer": "prefer", "Opt_1_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to like better", "Opt_3_def": "to give to (to promise to give)", "Opt_4_def": "to do well; to become rich"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "There was ____ applause from the audience when the speaker mentioned Mandela's name.", "Opt_1": "ideal", "Opt_2": "spontaneous", "Opt_3": "obsolete", "Opt_4": "firm", "Answer": "spontaneous", "Opt_1_def": "best, optimal", "Opt_2_def": "happening without warning or planning", "Opt_3_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date", "Opt_4_def": "strong, cannot be changed"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "My father's company is going to ____ our move to Germany by employing an agent to help us find a house here.", "Opt_1": "affect", "Opt_2": "persuade", "Opt_3": "facilitate", "Opt_4": "own", "Answer": "facilitate", "Opt_1_def": "to have an influence on", "Opt_2_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something", "Opt_3_def": "to make something easier", "Opt_4_def": "to have or possess"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "When morality comes up ____ profit, it is seldom profit that loses.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "A ____ example of ambiguity is the sentence: \"I do not like visiting aunts.\"", "Opt_1": "fortunate", "Opt_2": "classic", "Opt_3": "proper", "Opt_4": "comprehensive", "Answer": "classic", "Opt_1_def": "lucky", "Opt_2_def": "very good, the best or most used", "Opt_3_def": "correct, appropriate", "Opt_4_def": "full, complete"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Melting glaciers will ____ Alpine ski resorts within 45 years, says report.", "Opt_1": "defend", "Opt_2": "revise", "Opt_3": "destroy", "Opt_4": "increase", "Answer": "destroy", "Opt_1_def": "to give reasons for", "Opt_2_def": "to change (in order to improve)", "Opt_3_def": "to break or damage completely", "Opt_4_def": "to get bigger"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Although there are a number of credible strategies for trying to retain employees, money appears to be the most powerful retention ____ with regard to top performers.", "Opt_1": "exercise", "Opt_2": "bond", "Opt_3": "principle", "Opt_4": "tool", "Answer": "tool", "Opt_1_def": "a piece of work, activity", "Opt_2_def": "link; tie", "Opt_3_def": "rule", "Opt_4_def": "something used to do a job"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Poor results in end of year tests often ____ that the teacher has not taught the course very well.", "Opt_1": "regulate", "Opt_2": "survive", "Opt_3": "signify", "Opt_4": "dispose", "Answer": "signify", "Opt_1_def": "to control", "Opt_2_def": "to not die", "Opt_3_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_4_def": "to get rid of"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "I don't think she realises the magnitude of the ____ she has set herself.", "Opt_1": "priority", "Opt_2": "method", "Opt_3": "programme", "Opt_4": "task", "Answer": "task", "Opt_1_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_2_def": "a way of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_4_def": "job"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Students who take the class are expected to choose a contemporary problem they would like to address and ____ with each other in researching it.", "Opt_1": "devote", "Opt_2": "enable", "Opt_3": "collaborate", "Opt_4": "arise", "Answer": "collaborate", "Opt_1_def": "to give (time) to", "Opt_2_def": "to make something or someone able to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to work together", "Opt_4_def": "to happen"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "I think the new teacher will do very well. She has a lot of ____ with students whose first language is not English.", "Opt_1": "rank", "Opt_2": "fallacy", "Opt_3": "experience", "Opt_4": "task", "Answer": "experience", "Opt_1_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)", "Opt_2_def": "mistake; false belief", "Opt_3_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_4_def": "job"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Teachers can ____ that students get a minimum of 8 hours sleep per night, but they cannot dictate it.", "Opt_1": "suggest", "Opt_2": "persist", "Opt_3": "warn", "Opt_4": "oppose", "Answer": "suggest", "Opt_1_def": "to say an idea; to recommend", "Opt_2_def": "to continue (often in the face of difficulty)", "Opt_3_def": "to notify (of possible danger)", "Opt_4_def": "to be against or fight against something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "These interviews are part of an intense ____ to discover our internal best practices and high points.", "Opt_1": "schedule", "Opt_2": "context", "Opt_3": "result", "Opt_4": "effort", "Answer": "effort", "Opt_1_def": "timetable", "Opt_2_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_3_def": "outcome, effect", "Opt_4_def": "hard work; attempt"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The U.S. government likely approached China on this matter ____ to the announcement of sanctions, but did not receive a satisfactory response.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government made the prompt decision to kill all cows in the ____ before the disease could spread.", "Opt_1": "instance", "Opt_2": "desire", "Opt_3": "profit", "Opt_4": "area", "Answer": "area", "Opt_1_def": "example", "Opt_2_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_3_def": "money gained", "Opt_4_def": "field, sphere"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "For some people God is an ____ that influences every aspect of their life.", "Opt_1": "concern", "Opt_2": "entity", "Opt_3": "property", "Opt_4": "format", "Answer": "entity", "Opt_1_def": "worry, fear", "Opt_2_def": "thing; body; organization", "Opt_3_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home", "Opt_4_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The essay asks students to complete ____ tasks, giving the students numerous examples of human rights cases.", "Opt_1": "several", "Opt_2": "profound", "Opt_3": "tough", "Opt_4": "previous", "Answer": "several", "Opt_1_def": "many (about 6 or seven)", "Opt_2_def": "deep; great; serious", "Opt_3_def": "difficult, strong", "Opt_4_def": "the one before"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The two departments have failed to collaborate and ____ their efforts in implementing the laws and regulations on the use of wetland areas.", "Opt_1": "accompany", "Opt_2": "advocate", "Opt_3": "explain", "Opt_4": "coordinate", "Answer": "coordinate", "Opt_1_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together", "Opt_2_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to bring things or people together so that they work well"}]]